Ahjussi!
Oh, Se Ri!
What brings you here at this hour?
I'm here to see my dad.
He's still here at work, right?
Yes. I think CEO is still in the office.
- Why don't you go upstairs?
- Okay. Thank you!
What the heck is this?
It was a good night's sleep in a while.
Kid, it's morning now. You better go back.
Hey, kid. It's time for you to go back...
[My Chilling Roommate]
Hey! Why are you coming now?
You are late for work.
Why am I late? It's still 30
minutes before the opening time.
If you come later than
me, then you are late.
Also, you are a part-timer. Don't you think you
should come in an hour before the cafe opens?
Isn't that abusing power as an employer?
You mean the employer lady.
Don't you know the paycheck has the power?
I don't know. Please don't talk to me.
I'm exhausted.
What is this?
Drink this and get yourself together.
Lady Hwang, can you just do one thing?
Either be a devil or an angel
and don't make me confused.
The doubleness like Janus
is my femme fatale charm.
Sure, it is.
By the way, couldn't you sleep again?
No, I think I did sleep last night.
But I just had an awful dream.
An awful dream?
Is it that dream again?
Yes. It's always the same.
It's a real problem. That's why I said
you should stay with me at my house.
If you stay with me, you'll be tired.
It's better for me to be
the only one who's tired.
Forget about it. I hope
there are a lot of customers.
- When did we ever have a lot of customers?
- What did you say?
[119 Ambulance]
What's going on?
Was there an accident?
By the way, where did they go without me?
I don't even have my wallet with me.
Excuse me! This seat is reserved.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, okay.
Did you take a reservation for today?
What? No.
Then, what was it?
He's here.
Oh, it's your customer.
May I take your order?
I'm sorry? Oh, I'm waiting for someone.
When that person comes,
I'll order it together.
You've been coming here every day lately.
Are you waiting for someone?
How did you know that?
It's because you looked excited.
Oh, right...
Is my nervousness showing too much?
No, not at all! You look great.
It'll go well.
Thank you.
No matter how often I see that,
I can never get used to it.
It's giving me goosebumps!
Welcome.
- Please, have a seat here.
- Excuse me?
Oh, okay. Thank you.
When you decide on the menu, let me know.
Yes, I will.
Hey, what's going on? What is it?
The man who's sitting over there.
He doesn't know that he's dead yet.
Oh...
The majority of the ghosts
don't know that they are dead.
That's why they try to achieve what they've wanted
to do, so they keep appearing in the same place.
They are trying to accomplish their wish
they couldn't do when they were alive.
Can you stop saying that? I've
heard more than ten times already.
Did I say that many times?
Sales in the year's first half decreased by
about 15 percent compared to the previous year.
We are planning to open 15 new
branches in the year's second half.
And to increase sales,
our stores are planning to
provide a full delivery service.
Also, we plan to develop various
beverages by researching consumer trends.
What young people like these days...
So, did you find it?
Yes, we are currently developing
multiple different products...
No, no.
I'm talking about Ji Chan.
The head of the Sales
department, Song Ji Chan.
Did you find where he is?
Unfortunately, not yet...
But we are searching
for him in various ways.
Don't you think we should call the police
if he went missing for over 48 hours?
The thing is... What if it ends as nothing
but a happening when we call the police?
Either if it's just a happening
or what, find him now.
Board of Directors.
If we sit here like now, will
the Head Manager come back?
Will he!?
Can't you hear me? Get
the heck out of here now!
These old geezers are out of their minds...
Ji Min!
Wait, sir!
Am I...?
Yes.
I see.
What the heck is this?
Who are you?
What the heck was that? Where did she go?
What is this, really? Seriously...
What is it?
Managing Director Song.
Have you found him yet?
No, not yet, Chairman.
Is that so.
Please don't worry too much. We are searching
everywhere, so we'll find him soon.
I lost my oldest son like
that, and now Ji Chan as well.
We don't have any evidence yet,
so please don't feel despair.
You're right.
But I'm glad you are next to me.
I'll do anything to find him.
I'll find him, no matter what.
Okay.
Thank you, Ji Eun.
I'll find him, Uncle.
So you are saying,
I'm dead right now?
Yes.
What the heck are you saying? I'm dead?
I'm totally fine right now.
Ghosts don't know that they
became ghosts at first. So...
What kind of bullshit is that?
What? Ghost? Me?
I'm saying, right now, you are...
Stop it! What kind of gibberish is that?
- I mean, listen to me!
- My goodness.
Wait! Excuse me!
I guess he has a place to go?
What? I'm a ghost?
It's annoying.
Hey, don't try to pull bullshit!
She's insane.
Baby, are you okay?
I'm sorry.
Yes, I'm fine.
- I guess you are very hungry. Your legs got weak.
- Excuse me.
- Do you think so?
- Let's go for dinner right now.
- I said I was sorry.
- I'm so hungry!
- What should we eat?
- Excuse me...!
Hey, hey!
Hey, can't you hear me?!
What the heck was that?
My goodness!
Why did you come in so quietly?
You totally surprised me.
Did something happen?
- So...
- I'm dead, right?
Yes.
I think we can safely say so.
I'm sorry. I wasn't laughing at you.
- But how can you see me?
- Pardon?
How can you see me?
Who are you? Are you a shaman?
I don't think so.
What can I do to make other people see me?
I still have so many things to do.
Don't you think it's a shame
for me to die like this?
Well, sure.
What should I do?
What can I do to make other people see me?
Well, I got to go.
How can you just leave?
Tell me what I should do!
- Let me go.
- It's a shame for me to die like this, isn't it?
What should I do? Tell me something!
It hurts!
I'm sorry.
Let's talk again tomorrow.
I have to close the cafe.
What's wrong with you?
How can you follow me all the way here?
Why are you saying it like that?
I'm not trying to do anything to you,
but you are the only one I can talk to.
That's your problem.
If you are here, what am I supposed to do?
You? Just do what you normally do.
I'll just stay here quietly.
I'm not talking about that.
It's like talking to a wall. I'll
just stay here for the time being!
For the time being? Why are
you deciding that on your own?
What? Why are you suddenly
talking informally to me?
You've been talking informally to me from the
beginning. You were rude from the start.
You have zero manners.
We really don't see things eye to eye.
- What I'm saying is...
- Whatever. Just get out of here!
Get out of my house!
- Wait, one second...
- I said, get out!
Wait for a second!
Listen, I have no place to go!
What did you just say?
I said...
I have no place to go.
[Secretary]
Yes, what is it?
Managing Director, the thing is...
I get it. Please continue
to report it to me.
Ji Chan... Where are you?
Anyway, it's not okay.
Why not? Also, you said I'm a ghost.
Then, isn't it up to me?
I think you don't understand it. I'm...
Anyway, I'm not going anywhere.
I don't have a place to go or home.
- On top of that...
- On top of that, what?
I don't remember anything.
What?
I'm saying I don't remember anything.
Why I was there, or who I was.
I can't remember it.
This is driving me crazy.
You're lying to me right now, aren't you?
It's driving me crazy, too!
So let me stay here for a while.
Also, don't worry!
You are totally not my type.
What?
I'm exhausted!
It's funny you can still
be sleepy when you're dead.
I wonder if you can sleep fine at all.
What? What did you say?
You'll regret that you
decided to stay here.
What did you say?
She's not even looking back.
What the heck is going on?
No! Don't come to me!
Where am I?
Why am I here?
Who's that?
Excuse me, hello?
Was it a dream?
Wait, why is my body not moving?
Why is my chest feel so heavy?
My goodness! Who the heck are you?
It seems like that young boy is
yelling at this old grandma, right?
Why do you care? He's so cute
even when he's screaming!
You're so cute!
What's cute about him?
He's pretty like a girl.
Shut your mouth up. How dare you say that
when you look like you're not fully made?
Hey, what? What's wrong with my face?
When I was younger, so many women...
Who are these crazy people?
Hey, what's... Wait, where did she go?
Hey, Jung Se Ri!
Oh, my... Oh, my!
Hey, Jung Se Ri. Hey!
What is it?
Why is she sleeping out here?
Hey. Hey!
- Stop it!
- Oh, goodness.
Oh, my.
It must be exhausting for you.
She must be tired since she's going
through living hell every day.
Poor thing.
Does she live like this
with ghosts every day?
Don't worry about it, handsome Oppa.
That's her life, so she's used to it.
Oppa, my foot. You're at least
fifty years older than him.
You really don't have a conscience.
Anybody who's handsome is Oppa to me.
Do you want to die by my hand?
Am I going to die again? Hey, try it.
Go ahead and kill me.
- Go ahead and kill me.
- It's making me furious!
Be quiet!
Go fight somewhere else, or talk quietly.
That ghost with no eyes
is still very vivid to me.
It's giving me goosebumps.
I'm getting starving now.
But why am I getting hungry?
Does ghost also have to eat?
You surprised me!
Tell me about the ghost that you saw.
What? What ghost?
Yes, ma'am?
The ghost that you saw in your dream.
Tell me about it.
Oh, that ghost.
I don't remember clearly, but
I was walking on a street.
But then, suddenly, a ghost
with no eyeballs popped up.
And then?
What did she say? She said something
like, "It's not a place for you to be!"
Anyway, I've never seen something
that grotesque in my life.
Eyeballs. Are you sure it was
the ghost with no eyeballs?
Excuse me?
I'm asking, are you sure it
was the ghost with no eyeballs!
What is she saying? Why
can't I hear her clearly?
I guess this boy just became a ghost.
I'm sorry?
Are you sure you saw the
ghost with no eyeballs?
Yes! It was a female
ghost with no eyeballs.
- Right!
- Yes, it was a ghost with no eyeballs.
It was a ghost with no eyeballs.
Did you see that ghost?
I'm asking if you saw her.
- That's right. The ghost!
- Yes, yes.
- The ghost?
- I saw her.
Grandma? Are you talking about me?
The ghost.
What are you two doing?
Because of you, she woke up!
She barely slept.
What? It seems like he's
saying something to me, right?
Anyway, I'll get going first.
What's going on?
What? It's nothing.
You don't have to worry about it.
He's a good-looking guy, but his
personality is not that great.
It came out, right?
W-What are you talking about it?
That woman is back.
Why is she not coming? What
time does she think it is!
- Is she sick?
- Hey, why are you coming so late?
I'm sorry. I had to talk.
Talk? With whom?
Is it with a ghost again?
Don't you think so?
What kind of ghost is it this time?
A grandpa? A child?
Whoever it is, it's the same.
If you have to see it, I hope
it's a handsome young man's ghost.
Even though it's your friend's cafe,
how can you come this late to work?
What is it? Why are you
looking at me like that?
- Follow me.
- What?
Just follow me.
Why? Hey!
Is this the right place?
I think this is the correct place.
But why did you bring me here?
Look around carefully.
Do you remember anything?
What?
What do you mean what? Look around
carefully. You might remember something.
What are you saying? I
can't hear your voice!
What? What are you saying suddenly?
What's going on? I can't hear you!
Stop joking around.
Seriously, what is she saying?
It's frustrating.
- Hey!
- My goodness!
You are a ghost.
I'm sorry?
Did you see it? That's how you do it.
What? I can hear it clearly again!
Grandma!
It's okay. We have to solve it quickly.
This is amazing!
Can I do this to anybody?
Anyway, please think about it.
Do you remember anything more?
I don't know. When I woke up, I was here.
And as I walked, I went to that cafe.
How did you come to the cafe?
Cafe... I'm not sure.
Somehow, it looked like a familiar brand.
Well, it's a franchise cafe.
Anyway, I don't remember
anything at the moment.
So...
What was it? Why did that happen?
The time you can possess someone
else's body is not that long.
What? I can hear clearly again!
Why is this happening?
It is a common phenomenon for spirits who
have just been separated from their bodies.
It's a bit unstable.
But it's really fascinating.
Can I do this to anybody?
Let's not bother anybody else
and talk about it over there.
It's hot.
Are you hot?
Yes, it's hot. Isn't it strange if
you don't feel hot in this weather?
Is that so?
What is it?
What the heck are you doing?
Did you just hit me?
Does it hurt?
Of course, it hurts! What nonsense
are you saying after hitting me?
If you feel the pain, it's weird.
What's weird for me to say
it hurts when it hurts?
Listen to me carefully.
You may not be dead.
Ghosts can't touch living humans.
Of course, it's possible when
you become an evil spirit.
Anyway, ghosts can't feel something
like hot or cold temperature.
Also, you just felt the pain.
So I think you might be still alive.
Also, I think it has a connection with
the demon that came out in your dream.
So you have to regain your
memory as soon as possible.
That way, you can go
back to your place to be.
I must have surprised you.
But still, it's good news.
Anyway, I'll get going first.
What the heck did she say?
I couldn't hear anything after
"Listen to me carefully!"
- What was that?
- Is it you again?
Who are you? Are you a pickpocket ghost?
No, you already stole
it, so are you a robber?
What the heck...!
Why are there so many?
It's surrounded by ghosts. It's freaky.
Hey, you better keep your stuff...
- Hey.
- I-I'm sorry!
What are you doing? Do you
want to die by my hand!
I mean, why do you come out like that?
- Are you a pervert!
- It's not like that...!
- So why did you...!
- Get out.
Get out of here, right now. Right now!
- Get out of here!
- So why are you coming out like that!
Get the heck out of here!
Get out of here, right now!
I was helping you at the thought of you.
Also, you are not my type!
My type is someone with
big eyes, a sharp nose,
tall, and looks good with long hair.
Wait, what?
Ah, come on...
Welcome.
Are you the owner?
No, I'm not.
Did the owner not be here today?
Yes, she went out for a bit today.
How can I help you?
She's the Managing Director
from the headquarter.
What's going on? Is there a problem?
No, nothing. She's the Managing
Director from the headquarter.
Is that so? But what about it?
- Are you the owner?
- Yes, what's going on?
Didn't a person come here from
the headquarter a few days ago?
From the headquarter? Nobody came. When
did headquarter worry about branches?
What's wrong with this woman's tone?
I don't know about the person from the headquarter, but
hurry up and go. You guys are in the way of the business.
- Seriously, what the...
- Please stop it.
Let's go.
Come out now.
What are you talking about it suddenly?
Come out now when I'm talking nicely.
Come out... to where?
One, two...
I get it! I'll come out.
I guess you are very tired.
Why don't you go inside and have some rest?
You're right. I really don't feel great.
Please take care of the store for a bit.
What the heck are you doing right now?
Why are you mad about it?
You seemed in trouble,
so I tried to save you.
Do you know how hard it is to the
person when you get into their body?
I get it! You really have a temper.
- Hey!
- Hey?
Yes, I called you "hey." What
are you going to do about it?
Can you please stop shouting?
If you keep screaming, you will
get wrinkles around here like this.
What the heck is wrong with that person?
What are you so angry about?
He says you'll get wrinkles here like this!
Unni!
Se Ri, do you want me to go and punch him?
It's fine.
Let it slide just once.
Why do I have to?
Over there.
Look over there!
What about it?
What are you doing over here?
What is it?
How did you know I was here?
Why are you sitting here looking sad?
What? Why are you being
nice to me suddenly?
You were talking informally to me before.
What's wrong with me speaking informally?
You always talk rudely to me.
What? Why are you calling
me informally again?
Speaking of it, let's
straighten out our ages.
How old are you?
Me? What about you?
I asked you first.
Why don't we take our
IDs out at the same time?
What ID do I have when I'm a ghost?
So I'm asking you. How old are you?
I don't know. It's not important.
You were always getting angry at me.
But why did you come to see me?
Well, I'm just thankful to you.
What?
I forgot about my birthday as well.
How did you know about it?
What do you mean how did I know? I figured because
your friend was making such a fuss about it.
Oh, because of Eun Hye.
It would've been nicer if
we had met before I died.
It's too bad.
Excuse me?
I'm saying it would've been more
fun if we had met before I died.
Who died?
Who died? Are you kidding me?
I talked about it at such length.
Did you already forget about it?
What? Talked about what?
I said you might not have died.
No, I'm sure you didn't die.
What?
Please! Remember it, please!
Please, remember it!
Remember it, please...
Please...
♫ Everything is the same ♫
♫ But only me, without anyone knowing ♫
♫ As if I came back after
living in a different world ♫
♫ Even the morning
sunshine looks unfamiliar ♫
♫ Only because you are not here ♫
♫ Now it's time to wake up.
Now it's time to wake up ♫
It's okay.
You don't have to rush.
We can do it slowly.
♫ The dream called you, the dream
that I don't want to wake up from ♫
♫ I'll let you go just that much ♫
♫ I'll say goodbye a little by little ♫
♫ By looking at my phone
that's not ringing ♫
♫ And while longing for
you who disappeared ♫
♫ When painful tears fall down ♫
It's okay, it's okay.
♫ Only faded memories remain ♫
Slamming brake, a crosswalk, and a minivan.
Car accident and a syringe.
If you look at the situation,
it sounds like a car accident.
But what is this syringe for?
Excuse me, customer. Are
you not going to work?
Why don't you drink this?
Wow, you're totally ignoring me now.
It's Colombian Supremo coffee.
- Supremo?
- Yes, it's Supremo coffee. What about it?
How did you know that?
What?
How did you know this coffee is
made with Supremo coffee beans?
I'm not sure.
Excuse me.
Yes, sir!
Hey, you better get back to work
before I hire another barista.
You are really... I get it!
How did it go with what I ordered?
I executed immaculately.
You never know, so please
check it one more time.
Yes, sir.
Are you not going to get on?
What about Ji Chan?
Not yet.
Are you looking for him at all?
Of course, very much!
I'm looking for him very much!
It's not like you don't
want to find him, is it?
Me? Why would I?
If it's not, it's fine.
What's that discomforting answer?
That girl is not okay as well.
You are going to make the ground sink.
How did you know I was here?
I just saw you while I was passing by.
Is that so.
But why are you keep sighing?
Nothing special.
It's kind of ridiculous
that I can't remember.
And I feel pathetic about myself right now.
Sometimes, it's happier when
you don't remember anything.
What?
I have a day I clearly remember,
which I don't want to recall.
My family was wealthy before.
My dad was running a company called A1.
What is this? Are you bragging
about your wealthy family suddenly?
Just listen to me. I usually don't talk
about this, but I'm telling you specially.
So what happened after that?
Was it when I was ten years old?
My dad's company went bankrupt.
My mom killed herself because of it.
And my dad passed away soon
after because of that shock.
I still remember that day vividly.
It keeps coming out in my dream as well.
Anyway, it all started on that day.
That's when I began to
see ghosts around me.
Is that so.
But what's more upsetting is that my dad's company went
bankrupt because of his friend, who he trusted the most.
What?
I don't know more in detail.
But it's said that he intentionally played around
with stocks to take over my dad's company's share.
What kind of bastard is that?
Don't you have to catch
them and put them in jail?
It's really infuriating!
What is it?
Thank you.
What about it?
Thank you for cursing them for me.
Hey, it's okay for you to curse them.
Anybody who did something to
be cursed should be cursed.
Okay, repeat after me.
Hey, you bastards. Go to hell! Try it.
Hey, you bastards. Go to hell.
What are you doing? You
have to say it stronger.
Hey, you bastards! You all go to hell!
Try it again.
Hey, you bastards. Go to hell!
Can you do it again?
Hey, you bastards! Go to hell!
Yes! There you go.
- Okay, one more time.
- Can you show it to me again?
Hey, you bastards. Go to hell!
Hey, you bastards! Go to hell!
Yes, you are good at it! Try it louder.
Is he not home?
Hello?
What? Did he go somewhere?
Song Ji Chan.
Hey, rude boy!
Rude boy?
Where did he go?
Where have you been without telling me?
Don't come to me!
Jung Se Ri, are you okay?
Yes...
Jung Se Ri! Wake up!
Jung Se Ri. Jung Se Ri!
Please wake up. Jung Se Ri?
Her body temperature dropped tremendously.
This often happens when a
spirit fails to possess.
What can I do for her?
Stay by her side.
♫ It feels like I dreamt
a very long dream ♫
♫ When I open my eyes, you aren't there ♫
♫ It comes to me as a distant memory,
but also clear as if it was yesterday ♫
♫ As if I dreamt a very nice dream ♫
♫ Now it's time to wake up ♫
♫ It's time to say goodbye to you ♫
♫ It's scary to forget everything,
but it's painful to hold onto you ♫
♫ The dream called you, the dream
that I don't want to wake up from ♫
♫ I'll let you go just that much ♫
♫ I'll say goodbye a little by little ♫
Thank you.
Jung Se Ri.
Is she dead?
She's still breathing.
Can you hear us?
Why are you all looking at me like that?
Thank goodness. She's alive.
God, Buddha, thank you all so much!
What happened? Why have I lied down here?
Do you not remember?
It's already been two days. We
thought you were going to die.
That evil spirit was trying to... Ouch!
- What's wrong with you?
- Be quiet!
But why is he sleeping here?
That rude boy has been protecting you for
two days straight and fell asleep now.
Grandma, he's not a rude boy.
Okay, let's let Se Ri have some rest.
Let's all go out of the room.
Okay. Have some rest, Jung Se Ri.
Oh, at that time...
Yes, what is it?
We found him.
Is he... alive?
This is your sister. Your sister is here!
Please, open your eyes.
What happened to you?
I'm so sorry we found you late.
I'm really sorry.
Ma'am, please calm down
and listen to the doctor.
How is he right now?
Fortunately, it's not life-threatening,
but he's still in a coma.
We are doing our best, but
we have to wait and see...
He'll wake up. My brother will.
Please take great care of him.
We'll do our best.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
Ji Min.
Ji Min, it's nice to walk together.
But this neighborhood is in the
opposite direction of Ji Min's house.
Wait, Ji Min. Let's go together!
J-Ji Min?
Ji Min!
Ji Min, wake up. Please, Ji Min!
- Grandma.
- What?
How long will you just wait
and stare at it from here?
Let's just borrow her body for a second.
- Shall we?
- Yes.
What? Me?
- Don't you know respecting your elder?
- Respect your elder.
Then why don't you go inside...
Oh, I found him!
VIP ward, Song Ji Chan.
[Personal Information of Patients]
Okay.
Am I already drunk?
W-Who are you...?
Please don't come to me...!
What was it? Was it a dream...?
Who are you?!
Take me inside of you.
Who are you!
Why are you doing this to me?
Take me in.
No, no...!
You can get what you want.
What are you talking about right now?
I'll let you have what you want.
What I want?
Yes. What you want.
What I want...
What I want...?
The things that I want...
What? What is it?
Respect your elder.
Again? No, I don't want to!
It feels like I'm getting ten years
older when I possess someone's body!
Is ten years an issue when you can disappear
forever? Stop talking nonsense and go!
No, this time I really don't want to!
Why don't you send him instead?
Hey, you should go.
Why all of a sudden bring me into this?
You two should figure it out.
- You go this time.
- No, you go!
You weren't doing anything. You go!
I'll go inside.
Who's this new face that
appeared out of the blue?
He's not a new face. He comes to the cafe
sometimes. You know, that pure-love guy.
I have worked here before, so I know
the company's layout well. Let me do it.
Will you?
I just need to go in and get Song
Ji Chan's information, right?
Yes, that's right. Okay.
I'll be back.
Something's suspicious about him.
What brings you here?
You look very relaxed.
No, I'm busy. I'm just cooling
my head off for a second.
Is that so?
Oh, that's right. I saw you bought stocks.
W-What?
Why are you so shocked? It's not
like you did something illegal.
Nothing. I'm just a bit surprised.
Since you suddenly talk
about stocks out of nowhere.
I'll cut to the point. Give me that stock.
What?
Why do you keep making me say it twice?
What's up with your confidence?
Do you want to be disappeared
as well like Ji Chan?
J-Ji Chan?
What? It sounds like you
did something to Ji Chan.
Hey, hey! It hurts!
It hurts... It hurts!
What's this?
Until this week.
Sign this, and put it on my desk.
What the heck is this thing?
[Stock Transfer Agreement]
Stock transfer agreement...?
What should we do?
I feel bad for our
prince, Ji Chan, as well.
But what should we do with our poor Se Ri?
Let's reveal everything.
If we reveal everything, how
will you deal with the aftermath?
Revealing everything? About what?
Are you saying you'll transfer your
stocks to Managing Director Song?
Yes, including all of my shares.
But why all of a sudden?
Ji Eun completely changed.
She was crushing my wrist like a Hulk...!
It was horrifying! It still hurts.
Should I tag a person to her?
A person?
Why don't you put a tail on her
first and see who made her do so?
Thinking of Managing Director Song's personality,
she would've not decided on it alone.
Right?
I'll send a trustworthy person right away.
Okay, let's do so. Hurry up and go.
Yes, I'll hurry up and go.
So you're saying he's the youngest son of
the KS Group's Chairman Song Young Sik.
Yes.
And you know who's the KS Group.
It's the company that illegally acquired
your father's company, A1 Group.
Because of that guy, your
mother took her own life away.
And your father passed away from the
stress. They are your arch enemy.
That terrible bastard.
What did I say before?
I told you I had bad feelings
for that punk from the beginning!
But our prince doesn't even know who he is!
Also, he didn't do anything!
I knew it. I knew it from when he
was saying Supremo coffee and stuff.
- It's not like that...
- Stop it!
Se Ri.
You know that evil spirit has
come to you recently, right?
When evil spirits can't possess any human
body, they eat spirits like us to survive.
You've been sleeping
well these days, right?
It's because of the evil spirit
that other ghosts can't come.
It's not certain yet.
But I think Ji Chan has
the power of exorcising.
The power of exorcising?
There were no spirits in history that
could fight against evil spirits.
But you also saw it.
If Ji Chan can put the evil
spirit into a corner that much,
he definitely has the energy of exorcism.
So we have to trust Ji Chan on this.
But there's no guarantee that the rude punk will
win the fight with the evil spirit, isn't it?
If that happens...!
You use this.
What is this?
It's called "Spirit box," which
I got from an exorcist who died.
It's a box that can put spirits in it.
When it opens, it sucks in
entire spirits around it.
So if I open it, I go into the box, too.
In the worst-case scenario,
you open this box, Se Ri.
I have a question.
What happens to Song Ji Chan if he
loses the fight with the evil spirit?
Well, if he loses the fight, then...
He'll disappear forever.
Including his soul.
Exorcism?
Hasn't it come in yet?
Okay.
Look at this bastard. He
lost his sense of fear.
Managing Director.
I think someone's following us.
Who is it? Who made you follow me?
I don't know...!
Is it Song Ji Seok?
I only got an order to follow you.
Sir, he's not picking up the phone.
I asked him to tail her,
but he went off the grid!
He must be still following her right now...!
He's following her, but what?!
Ji Chan... Did you find Ji Chan?
Not yet, sir...
I'm sure Ji Eun took him away.
I'm sure the two are
excited together right now.
[Stock Transfer Agreement]
It wasn't easy for me to get these stocks, and
now she wants them for free? That's nonsense!
Call him again and ask him how it went!
Yes, sir.
What? Where is that sound coming from?
What? You...
What is this?
I think you'll know better.
I don't know! How do I know about this?
This is just...
I guess you have a lot in mind these days.
N-No, it's not like that.
It says transfer, so I was
going to write as giving up.
Why don't you two have a conversation?
I'll let you have some privacy.
Where do you think you are going?
Pardon?
I'm asking, where are you going?
I was just going to close the door for you.
You were going to give up, not transfer.
Yes, that's right. Giving up
is the correct word, isn't it?
If I transfer it to you, the tax is heavy.
And shareholders will gossip about
it that it's insider trading.
So if I simply give up, you can...
Now that I heard of it,
giving up is correct.
Right? Giving up is correct.
You'll die anyway, so it doesn't matter
if you give it up or transfer it to me.
Hey... Why are you saying
it so scary like that?
I was going to transfer it
to you as soon as possible.
But this punk said you took Ji
Chan away and scheming stuff.
No! I just did it because the
Vice President ordered me!
What, you bastard? You said we
should tag a person to her first.
You made me do so!
Are you out of your mind!
Be quiet.
You.
Yes, Managing Director.
- Kill him.
- I'm sorry?
Hey, you!
I said, kill him.
How can I do that to the Vice President...?
Wait, Director Kang... Director Kang!
Welcome...
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Thank goodness the wounds
didn't hit the critical spots.
Let me see.
The burn is also not that bad, so
you'll be okay if you rest a few days.
Where have you been?
Who did this to you?
Were you worried about me?
Of course, I was worried about you.
How can I not worry?
How can I not be worried about you when
you were gone after seeing you every day?
It hurts!
What hurts when you are a ghost?
Also, you need to get punished more.
My goodness! I went to the company.
The company?
KS Group.
Did your memory come back...?
Not all of them, but a
little bit came back.
How much do you remember?
The fact that I was working in the company,
and I had an older brother and a sister.
Then why did you get these wounds?
What? I just fell and tumbled.
What?
I'm a bit tired. I think I need to rest.
Yes, he's right.
He should have some rest.
Why don't we leave him alone?
Get out!
Get out of my body now!
Please! Get out!
Are you afraid?
There's nothing for you to be scared of.
You...
You are the one who made a choice.
You can't take it back anymore.
Please get out of me now.
I don't need anything anymore. I
don't need anything, so please leave!
Now, I'm the one who's making the decision.
What?
You have no choice.
No, no...
♫ It feels like I dreamt
a very long dream ♫
♫ When I open my eyes, you aren't there ♫
I'm sorry, Jung Se Ri.
I guess the one who made you
miserable is me, after all.
♫ As if I dreamt a very nice dream ♫
I'll bring everything
back to you from now on.
I'll give your father's company back.
And I'll bring back your bright smile, too.
I'll bring you back to the happy time.
I'll get back everything.
Thank you, Jung Se Ri.
♫ Now it's time to wake up ♫
♫ It's time to say goodbye to you ♫
♫ It's scary to forget everything,
but it's painful to hold onto you ♫
♫ The dream called you, the dream
that I don't want to wake up from ♫
♫ I'll let you go just that much ♫
♫ I'll say goodbye a little by little ♫
What made you come to work this early?
I guess the sun will rise in the west.
That's what I have to say. Why are you
making coffee this early in the morning?
Have a seat over there.
Eat this.
Thank you for the food.
Song Ji Chan.
It was too obvious.
Hello! You haven't visited in a while.
I guess you were busy.
Yes, a little bit.
- Se Ri.
- Yes?
Somebody came to see you outside.
To see me?
Yes.
Who would that be? Excuse me for a second.
What is it? Who came to see me?
Hey...!
What's wrong? Why are you in such a hurry?
- Se Ri got...!
- What happened to Jung Se Ri?
Se Ri got abducted by bad people!
What?
Why is she not picking up her phone?
If she comes, I'm really
going to fire her this time.
It's so frustrating. You have the
location tracking on her, you stupid girl!
If she doesn't pick up her phone, you have
to track her location and call the police!
It's so frustrating. It's driving me crazy!
- Excuse me.
- Yes!
It's Incheon.
Hey, you!
Seriously, he's so impatient.
He'll be all right, won't he?
- Let's hurry up and go, too.
- Go where?
Of course, we are going to Incheon!
What are you doing? Aren't you coming?
Well, I'm not feeling that great.
- Are you not coming?
- Coming!
Who are you?
You can leave the room.
W-What is it?
Who are you to do this to me?
Didn't we meet before?
We met once in the cafe.
Don't you remember?
Are you the older sister of Song Ji Chan?
Yes. Your memory isn't that bad.
But why would you do this to me?
Why do you think I brought you here?
You are...
No, not yet!
It's not the time for you to come out yet!
Give me what I want first. Then
I'll give you what you want!
Are you crazy? Do you know what
kind of thing you have done?
It doesn't matter!
What?
If I can get what I want, I
don't care about any other thing!
You are out of your mind.
Song Ji Chan will come here.
I just need to get rid of him.
No...!
What's going on? That
rude boy is not in here.
What about Se Ri?
She's with the evil spirit.
- I-Is the evil spirit in there, too?
- Yes.
- Let's go in there.
- How can we go there just like this?
He says the evil spirit is there.
Let's watch the situation
a bit more and then go in.
Watch what? What if
something happens to her?
Where did the prince go?
It's driving me crazy.
I can't wait any longer. Let's go!
Grandma. Grandma!
Seriously... Grandma!
You're here.
What the heck are these?
Grandma!
Se Ri, are you okay?
No, Song Ji Chan!
No!
Why did you come here? Leave here, now!
I told you I'd protect you.
Don't worry about me and please go!
♫ It feels like I dreamt
a very long dream ♫
♫ When I open my eyes, you aren't there ♫
♫ It comes to me as a distant memory,
but also clear as if it was yesterday ♫
♫ As if I dreamt a very nice dream ♫
♫ Everything is the same ♫
Thank you.
♫ But only me, without anyone knowing ♫
♫ As if I came back after living in a different
world, even the morning sunshine looks unfamiliar ♫
♫ Only because you are not here ♫
♫ I'll say goodbye a little by little ♫
♫ I loved you to death ♫
No, no!
♫ I fear that you might
disappear in my faded dreams ♫
♫ I still live in the dream called you ♫
♫ In the hope of never waking up ♫
[3 months later]
- Excuse me.
- Yes!
You can click here like this.
It's good to see her smiling, at least.
I'm glad.
What are you so glad about?
She can't even see us anymore.
Now our wish is gone out
of the window, right?
What? Were you still
clinging to that wish thing?
Were you still around here because of that?
It's not just because of
that, but a little bit.
Both of you, be quiet!
I think now it's time for us to go, too.
Take care, Jung Se Ri.
Let's go.
Farewell. Thank you so much for everything.
Jung Se Ri, what are you doing?
I'm coming!
Why are you making such a fuss?
Take it easy.
It's because it's so busy. I don't
know why it's so hectic these days.
It's good to be busy.
You'll be rich, ma'am.
I got to buy a building as soon as
possible and get out of this life.
- I think the coffee beans arrived. Can you take that?
- Okay.
♫ It feels like I dreamt
a very long dream ♫
♫ When I open my eyes, you aren't there ♫
♫ It comes to me as a distant memory,
but also clear as if it was yesterday ♫
♫ As if I dreamt a very nice dream ♫
♫ Everything is the same ♫
♫ But only me, without anyone knowing ♫
♫ As if I came back after
living in a different world ♫
♫ Even the morning
sunshine looks unfamiliar ♫
♫ Only because you are not here ♫
Excuse me.
Here.
Hello?
I'm sorry?
What is it?
Excuse me?
Is there something on my face?
If it's not, do you know me?
It's nothing. I'm just glad to see you.
Pardon?
Did we meet before somewhere?
Not from here, but somewhere else.
We know each other very well.
Very much.
I see.
It's good to see you.
♫ Now it's time to wake up. It's
time to say goodbye to you ♫
♫ It's scary to forget everything,
but it's painful to hold onto you ♫
♫ The dream called you, the dream
that I don't want to wake up from ♫
♫ I'll let you go just that much ♫
♫ I'll say goodbye a little by little ♫
♫ So tell me this is real ♫
♫ Tell me and show me the truth, please ♫
♫ I can feel nothing ♫
♫ I can't feel anything ♫
♫ In the wandering time, I hope
at least you were sincere to me ♫
♫ So tell me this is real ♫
♫ Tell me and show your feelings ♫
♫ When did it start? ♫
♫ Was I wandering for a long time? ♫
♫ What have you been looking for and
waiting alone in this empty space? ♫
♫ The mysterious light that
I see is getting clearer ♫
♫ The thing that I can do for you ♫
♫ Is that the reason I was looking for? ♫
♫ So tell me this is real ♫
♫ Tell me and show me the truth, please ♫
♫ I can feel nothing ♫
♫ I can't feel anything ♫
♫ In the wandering time, I hope
at least you were sincere to me ♫
♫ So tell me this is real ♫
♫ Tell me and show your feelings ♫