Everybody said...
that the tree was rotting.
But I told them...
which was far from it.
That night I had a dream.
In dream...
I saw the tree growing strong towards the blue sky.
I gathered everyone together and told them that the tree was not rotting.
It was not a rotten tree.
All units, jump!
Jump, jump!
jump!
"Capitán Kwon".
Take cover! Disconnect enemy communications!
Received!
"Apoyo".
Complete disconnection.
"Recognition".
Right in the chest, take it already!
"Demolition".
"Negative space".
Clear sector.
"Yong_guru".
Captain! Captain!
Hey Mr. Hairy...
If you follow the captain, he will be exposed.
Captain, I've got the building scanned.
Look at all those enemies.
How do we disarm the bomb inside?
I will go ahead, the rest go behind.
What did you say? Will you get ahead?
Captain! Captain!
Enemies! Enemies!
Mr. Hairy, stay here.
- Captain, we're in! - Here!
- Fall back! - Report!
Captain, it's a trap!
- Can you hold position? - It doesn't look good.
Captain, can you disarm the bomb?
Leave it to me.
I'm almost there, just a little more.
Mr. S.S. Hairy!
I dont believe it!
I'm coming in, cover me!
Hold position!
Don't move, stay there!
Captain, I sent the bomb plans, take them as soon as possible.
Captain!
If you don't hurry, we'll be in danger! Fast!
Captain! Hairy is a lost cause, give it up this time!
Get Mr. Hairy Out!
Yong_guru, Demolition, go defuse the bomb!
Received!
He's crazy, seriously.
That is why he is our leader.
Captain, we are here!
Ok, in a hurry.
Captain, captain!
- Captain! - Yong_guru, hurry up, hurry up!
A little more, come on, hold on a little more.
Captain!
"Captain Kwon, killed in action."
Complete deactivation.
"Round won."
We won without you.
It's all Mr. Hairy's fault.
Shouldn't he get into another game?
- I'm sorry. - As long as we win...
Captain, you are such an idiot.
He knows it's bullshit and he calls himself captain.
Who cares. They always kill me.
Because you always try to save others.
Who are you to talk, Hairy.
Okay, since we won, let's meet for dinner.
30,000 each!
Captain, come tonight!
Being mysterious is overrated.
Let's take a look at you.
How about grilled intestines?
Deal! BBQ with the captain!
I'm very busy these days...
- Come on! - Another time, perhaps.
- "Miss Lee." - I do not want to see you.
What do you do exactly?
I am receiving many calls.
- I disconnect. - That? No!
That?
Where are you? At the internet cafe again? Because...?
You're a child?
Always with video games.
Why do you call me?
I left the gas valve on.
Go close it.
Did you call me for that? The gas valve?
It could explode, go quickly.
Why is it going to explode?!
I'm busy.
So proud of you, parasite.
Oh really...
I have a night shift at the hospital.
See if I ask you nicely.
I'm very busy!
- See you tomorrow. - Mother! Mother!
Nice, right?
My son bought it on a school trip.
It's germanium.
It seems that it is good for health.
"Team eliminated."
Hello?
Is it the internet cafe?
I left my phone there.
Could you bring it to me?
- Now I'm in... - Wait a minute.
I am a very busy man.
I'll pay you 300,000.
I do not believe this...
Where are you?
Hey?
Is there someone?
What's happening?
Hey?
I brought your phone.
Hello, I'm in the shower.
You can leave it anywhere.
You said you would pay me...
It's upstairs, in my bed.
Good.
I left your phone on the bed.
Excuse me, you should close the door, it can be dangerous.
Catch it! Grab it!
Stay still, bastard!
Be good, don't resist!
You're under arrest for statutory rape and murder.
According to the fifth...
What's going on?
- Call forensics. - Yes sir.
Don't move!
Show your face!
The rapist and murderer of...
"Murderous Rapist Arrested".
A minor victim...
He was arrested this morning...
The signing of this check, is this yours?
That's how it is.
Yeah, but the thing is...
What about your fingerprints all over the knife?
That's what I do not understand...
The prime suspect was a national taekwondo athlete...
Kwon participated in a violent game before the murder.
He was fired after an assault case...
and led a life of unemployment resorting to video games.
A national athlete?
What happens?
Where is my son?
- You can't come here! - Let go! And my son?
¡ Kwon Yu!
The suspect denies all charges...
While fingerprints and DNA...
found at the crime scene...
They were sent to coroners for analysis.
On a handkerchief found at the scene...
your sperm was detected.
My son is not a murderer.
Please read this.
Please...
Please read it...
My son was framed.
Please read this, thank you.
He has no conscience, he is a monster.
DNA found at the scene is from suspect Kwon Yu...
and the court is pressured to deliver justice.
Lawyer Min...
my son would never kill a person.
Please watch this.
You can leave the documents here.
Please look at them.
He won a medal.
Lord, ever since I was a child...
Yes, this is lawyer Min Chum-sang.
Yes, I am a public defender, what can I do for you?
Don't worry too much.
Send us the documents and we will examine them.
Yes Yes.
Thank you.
I brought him up even more strictly, because he had no father.
The way I see it...
ought...
ask your child to confess and admit it.
At least he'll get a mitigation.
But Mr. Min, you haven't even heard...
The evidence against him is numerous...
so if he continues to deny it, it could be worse...
Lady? Lady?
We can talk?
Did the police tell you to come here?
Mr. Min tries to help everyone who needs it.
- If you go home and wait... - Mr. Min!
Please believe my son.
The defendant promptly left the crime scene after the murder...
He only collected the reward...
The prints on the knife and the doorknob match Kwon's.
After sexually assaulting the minor twice...
Kwon stabbed her 31 times in the neck and abdomen...
and took the body to the bathroom to clean it.
Silence please.
I really didn't.
When a game addict becomes obsessed, he does not distinguish between fact and fiction.
That is why you can commit antisocial acts without remorse.
Death penalty or castration!
Just neuter him.
"The councilman proposes the 'Kwon law'. The councilman presented a project...
for a tougher sentence for rape.
After being kicked out of the national team...
Please understand that he suffered from severe depression.
Despite the clear evidence against him...
the defendant Kwon Yu refuses to admit his wrongdoing.
Therefore...
The defendant is guilty of sexual assault on a minor...
first-degree murder of a minor, and desecration of a corpse...
and is sentenced as follows.
Life in prison without parole.
My son did not go!
It was not him!
No!
I did not go! I know nothing!
¡ Kwon Yu!
I did not go! Mother!
Mother! Mother!
The identity of the defendant...
will be released to the public for ten years.
As part of the rehabilitation...
will receive five years of treatment for sexual drive.
Furthermore, given the violent nature of his crime...
and as it requires isolation from society...
He will serve his sentence in a maximum security prison.
- Wait! Please! - Salt!
Get out, bastard!
Wait! I did not go!
Come here! Come here!
Come here, move away!
You came for this.
Rape.
Rape a little girl. Bastard.
Was not me.
Motherfucker!
How dare you answer!
Look around you, see them.
They are all proud of their crimes. "I committed murder!"
"I hit him until he stopped breathing!"
"It pisses me off that I didn't kill him!"
Look at this moron.
You are denying everything.
"It wasn't me, I didn't do it!"
"They are wrong! It was spoiled!".
"It was love! We loved each other!"
Fuck!
Come here, bastard!
Boss! Boss!
Let go!
Motherfucker!
Aside!
Back off!
You're crazy?!
When an adult speaks, you say, "Yes, I understand, sir!"
They are elementary manners. Don't throw it to the ground!
How dare you hit me, you bastard?!
My hand!
You are dead.
Damn!
Back off!
Ma Duk-su.
I was hit, I am the victim.
He hit me first.
They are all witnesses.
Look, blood in the nose.
take it away
Kwon Yu, 30 days of isolation.
Asshole, I heard you hit Ma.
It's alright, it's alright.
We are not with them, we are on your side.
To be in perpetual life, how could you attack him?
You have to like him.
Like me.
And he, look at him.
He's a serial killer.
It ate the person it killed.
Be careful with him and Ma Duk-su.
Anyway, give us details.
How old was she?
Middle School?
Institute?
School uniform or street clothes? Tell us!
We have to be together, you could just die!
Unfortunate!
¡Agárrenlo!
I really hate...
to those who do not regret.
If you commit a crime, you must repent and start over.
Starting a fight, acting out and all that shit.
After today, I want to see you repentant and remorseful.
"Please don't kill me."
Come on, get it ready.
Do it.
What you did to the little girl.
Are you crazy?
And you? They can do it?
That? Yeah! Yeah!
I will do it! I will strive!
Forward.
Get off me, you fucking charlatans!
"Please find out the truth."
"My son is not a murderer!"
Bastard!
¡Agárrenlo!
- Quiet, dammit! - Do not move!
It's tough, isn't it?
I did...
a protest in front of the court...
and gave an interview to a new magazine...
and thanks to that...
I got in touch with someone who knows your alibi.
I'll see you next week, and I'll start the appeal process.
Kwon Yu...
I...
I don't want to be the mother of a rapist.
If you don't want to be a rapist...
be strong and hold on.
I'm going to get you out of here.
Sight.
He found a way to live.
Then I better help.
Rub it on your wounds.
You must have been an athlete.
You protect your pressure points even during beatings.
I've been watching you.
You are not a murderer.
I'm sure Ma knows you're not a murderous rapist.
You just messed with his ego.
Ma has fallen!
Kwon Yu, you have visitors.
Did he come alone?
and mom?
"Death certificate: Lee yeon-ok."
What is this?
He had a difficult time...
But I didn't think it would go this far...
What is he saying?
Why should he?
He said he'd get me...
to stay strong...
Why would he do this all of a sudden?
You must sign to do the funeral.
The district office will arrange the funeral.
But you won't be able to attend.
I tried to get you to attend, but the application was rejected.
Mother!
Mother...
Do not resist!
Kwon Yu! Loosen the razor!
If an artery, a muscle, or an organ is damaged, you're screwed.
Don't stab too deep, go for the waist, okay?
Do you have a plan when you go out?
I'm going to clear my name.
I promised my mother...
that he would not be a rapist.
Give me the key.
Rapist-murderer Kwon Yu escaped from prison yesterday.
When the police arrived on the scene...
Kwon Yu was untraceable...
and they sent a communiqué to all points of the nation.
Kwon's current whereabouts are unknown...
and his uniform was recovered in a fishing area.
The police found blood on his uniform and it is presumed that he is injured...
so it can't have gotten far.
They are reinforcing...
checkpoints at bus terminals...
searching the nearby mountains, and blocking the main roads.
You are a handyman!
Incredible!
If it wasn't for you, we would have had to cancel the whole vacation.
Our heroe.
We are going to Cheongju airport. How do you say?
- Cheongju Airport. - Yes, Cheongju airport.
We are going to Hangzhou, China.
Yes, in China. Yes Yes Yes.
Tour!
So happy!
What is this?
A road block.
It's a checkpoint...
What's going on? We don't have all day.
Wait wait wait. I know, I know.
Listen, we really have to go.
We have to take a plane.
- And if you let me talk to the officer? - Come in.
- Come in! - Thanks thanks.
Thanks thanks.
No trace on the roads towards the city.
We bought it for 200,000 won when we arrived in Korea...
now you can scrap it for...
How do you say 40?
400.000 won.
Shit car, shit car.
Thank you.
Two days have passed since the pursuit of the fugitive Kwon...
and is expected to continue for some time.
People have expressed concern...
for more rapes and murders with Kwon on the run.
I totally forgot to bring the painting.
My memory is not what it was.
President Chu Sang-duk?
President Ch...
Oh, from the Hyosin Group?
I'll call him back when I go over the scene tomorrow.
My picture...
I'm a wanted man, so I had nowhere to go.
I sneaked in without permission, sorry.
When he came to visit with my mother...
she mentioned...
to a person who knows my alibi...
- Alibi? - Yeah.
Did you meet with that person?
You didn't run away to see it, did you?
I don't know who it is, but I need to see it.
It's weird that mom killed herself while preparing my appeal.
I have to see it and...
It was false information, a prank call from some children.
He took it very badly.
I certainly couldn't look at you again.
cried for days...
and chose his destiny.
This belonged to him. You recognize it?
Call the police.
I'll investigate your case later, turn yourself in.
Kwon Yu, high!
Not here.
"Kwon Yu".
"The fugitive Kwon Yu on the loose."
"Police Recover Kwon Yu's Prison Uniform in a Fishing Area".
"Is Kwon Yu the real killer?"
Rapist and murderer of a minor, the video game addict Kwon Yu...
Does Mr. Hairy?
There are many discrepancies in the investigation of your case.
The CCTV evidence presented by the prosecution...
They only have pictures of Kwon, and nothing before or after.
The prosecution said it was a recording malfunction.
They also didn't know about a car camera...
where Kwon appears.
For that reason the owner of the car wanted to use that recording...
and sent it to a media outlet.
But for unknown reasons, the recording was lost...
and almost buried in the station's server.
A new hacker was hacking the station's servers...
and found it by chance.
Contrary to the prosecution's arguments...
Kwon was seen going in and out of the motel...
in 3 minutes and 16 seconds exactly.
Is it logically possible to have sex twice, stab her...
then take the corpse to the bathroom...
and clean it of all traces?
To investigate Ha Ji-su's whereabouts before her death...
We reviewed their Facebook and Instagram pages...
and we found her in a club two days before her death.
It was not difficult to find her on the club's CCTV.
At 3 am, he left the club with a man...
and his body was found a day and a half later.
The man in question was never a suspect.
But the unemployed Kwon Yu was immediately arrested...
Captain! Get out of there!
The manager found you out! Fast!
Hello? The wanted...
Captain, come to the Namyang cafe in the Bukchang district.
Let's meet there.
Welcome.
A handsome young man.
Bye sweetheart!
This is Namyang cafe.
Does Mr. Hairy?
Is there someone called "Captain"?
Is there a "Captain"?
It's a joke?
Are you the "Captain"?
Mr. Furry? Is this the correct site?
I just arrived.
Where are you?
Who are you? Who are you?
Did Mr. Hairy send you?
"Mr. Hairy."
Does Mr. Hairy?
What's going on here?
Who is this person?
It is legit?
- You can't... - It's me.
That?
The one in front of you.
Hello?
I'm Mr. Hairy.
But your voice...
There is a voice app.
It's a voice modulator.
"Mr. Hairy."
Sit anywhere.
This is safe.
Rice delivery!
Leave it right there.
Who could live here?
Heavens!
Rice?
Don't you live alone?
Where do you want it, Mr. Hairy?
Yeah?
They will arrive soon.
Don't let them see you like that, you're still the captain.
It was a walk.
Mr. Furry! We also want
Extra portion for me.
It looks delicious!
This neighborhood makes me hungry.
I thought I was going to starve on that climb.
There is no CCTV around and it is very safe as well.
right, captain?
So we finally meet?
- Thank you. - I bought eggs on the way.
We saw Mr. Hairy for the first time yesterday.
She never came to our meetings...
but after hearing that you ran away...
called us.
- Sit down, sit down. - That wasn't all.
He took control of my computer and made me see things.
He only talks on the phone.
Do you have sociophobia?
I was moved by your movie.
One moment, one moment.
So they're all...
This is Yong_guru.
When Yongsan Mall went bankrupt...
he is the legendary technician who became half unemployed.
And this is Demolition.
I'm Demolition, I work in a special effects team.
Those cool things you see in the movies...
I work on them.
He is a beginner.
And I am...
Negative space, university professor of Architecture.
Or so he says.
Why is everyone...
We can't stand to sit idly by and let you get framed.
We must all help!
Thanks for the thought, but I can do it alone...
That is not good, we must help.
I appreciate the intention...
There are a couple who couldn't come...
Support and Recognition.
They broadcast online helping the young and lonely!
Stars in the adult industry!
Did he mention where he was going?
No, he didn't say anything.
You must be a busy man.
Yes a bit.
If you call, let us know right away.
Yeah.
You can go.
Good.
Listen...
Do you still have your case files?
Can I review them?
Stop snooping and get on with your work.
Mr. Public Defender.
Clear...
Yes, Ms. Lee.
I visited Chairman Chu's workplace.
I sent Kwon Yu's prison files to his email.
Kwon Yu...
Ma Duk-su?
Drug smuggling, attempted murder, human smuggling...
arms trade with gangsters.
Kwon has balls to hit him.
Fucking bastard! Look at the traffic behind!
I'll pour gasoline up your ass and light it up!
Powerless son of a bitch!
Take the bus, asshole!
62n6089, "malhablado".
Common pattern?
I have dissected recent violent crimes...
that have similar traits.
Do we have to talk on the phone?
Am I the only one who thinks it's weird?
What about the pattern?
Most criminals tend to...
hide evidence as much as possible.
Yes, that's what anyone would do.
But the most important aspect of these cases is...
that all the proofs are exposed as in an exhibition.
How strong!
Hey!
The suspect is caught within 24 hours of the crime...
and their identities revealed even before the trial.
But that alone cannot be seen as a common pattern.
I think that's enough to establish a pattern.
Do you feel this?
Look at this screen.
I checked all the CCTV...
in a radius of 1 km when the captain went there.
What about the truck?
They see him?
It's a montage!
It's fake, look!
If you look at the time code...
The truck looks like it's been there an hour.
They wanted to hide where he went.
Exact.
Was the truck also present in other cases?
Who are those guys?
I checked their registered addresses.
They all belong to a junkyard near lncheon.
Negative and Yong were very jealous of me.
Because I'm going with you.
You are a god among gamers.
There! Look!
It's really here!
This is fat!
Mr. Hairy was right.
Suits in a junkyard look weird.
I'll follow the van.
Can you keep the fort here?
I?
You can do it? Of course you can.
Captain, the audi from before is back.
What's happening? They're turning it into a refrigerator truck.
Who are they?
They go, they go
What I do?
Go after them?
I don't have a vehicle.
Are you poly?
Grandpa, quick!
I was a marine!
Captain! Captain!
There, there, that building.
They delivered a fridge.
I tried everything to sneak in...
but I could not. What do we do?
I have it.
Okay, Negative, Yong, come on in.
Most technicians insist on coming in the morning.
They don't come running like us, we are responsible.
Today people have no spirit.
This is our specialist.
A legend in his field.
I'll go take a look.
Ah, right, I don't know if you've heard...
the manager of a nearby apartment has just been fired.
- Fired? - Yeah.
He said he worked responsibly and trying hard...
Yong_guru, find the main server and connect me to it.
He wasn't picky...
It was cheeky, wasn't it?
What do you think? Do you agree?
I don't understand...
Main server... Main server...
What I'm saying is...
What was he saying?
I lost the thread.
Where do you want to go?
To nowhere.
- None? - When I was 28 or so...
- 28? - That is.
- My hair... - Hair?
We are similar, you are brighter than me.
Why it takes so long?
You can't diagnose and fix a problem in a hurry.
Everything has to be checked and rechecked...
so it doesn't happen again...
Ready.
But it is also a piece of cake for an expert.
Mr. Hairy, connected.
Yes, thanks.
Captain #1306.
13th floor clear.
- It's Noh Joon-young. - Do you know him?
He was the star of the TV show "The Witch's Boyfriend."
It was a smash hit, now he's a celebrity.
Is that Noh's house?
That one! The box they delivered!
Why is he dead in there?
Were they transporting a corpse?
Life is vain, I was a rising star.
Captain, we have guests.
What are they doing?
Party preparations are over.
Full of footprints, nails and saliva...
it will not be easy to remove all evidence.
I've put together a list of candidates.
173 in total, unemployed and temporary.
Are you always so fast?
No need to run.
Our team can only work when the girl has been chosen!
President Chu won't stop calling me!
Fine, fine, stop nagging.
You know how this works...
being out of work is not the only criteria.
Let's trace the steps of Noh.
"Noh Joan-young".
"Credit Card Transactions".
¿"Boss"?
He spent a lot of time there.
Was he addicted to hostess clubs?
Okay, let's take a look at the girls over there.
"Big Brother".
"Journalist Seo Ji-seung."
- Hello? - I sent you a profile.
Prepare a headline and draft.
Do it tonight.
It won't be easy, I have other headlines...
That?
You can not do it?
Of course. I'll have it done for...
I pay you enough, be grateful.
The concept of this is...
"Ghastly murder of a celebrity who harassed waitresses."
Who is it?
I'm here to change the water filter.
Good.
"Big Brother: Traces Sent".
"Medident dental laboratory".
Yes, Mr. Min?
Miss Lee.
I need to get someone out of prison.
Sooner.
I investigated the owner of the farm.
His name is Chu Sang-duk, Chairman of the Hyosin Group.
Why does an actor die in another's house?
I know.
No questions.
They are articles about Noh and Chu Ye-ri.
¿ Chu Ye-ri?
President Chu's daughter.
The pieces are fitting.
Are they framing the girl in the photo?
I know!
I said no questions.
Mr. Hairy, can you find her?
Do you see this footprint?
They will go after her.
I'll try.
"Park Barber Shop".
It's nice.
How would you like it?
As thick as possible.
Touch the shampoo.
Good.
Captain, installed the "bug".
- Very good. - How is it so easy?
That is why you should not click on any link.
One click, and it's not your phone anymore.
Fucking bitch!
Why do not you answer me?
It's pay day, did you forget?
- I'm sorry! - Come here, bitch!
Please give me a few more days!
Give you a few more days?
Fucking bitch!
You don't answer me, you don't pay me!
What are you looking at? They are having fun?
Sell ​​the kidney if necessary!
You do not deserve...
¡Sueltame!
Who the fuck are you?!
I sent it last week.
Impossible!
I have no more money to send you!
If he needs the money, let him rob a house!
How can you say that to your brother?
You're important for sending a little change.
Bitch!
Mother...
Do you know how I earn that money?
Don't call me again.
I have reached the limit!
"Mr. Hairy."
Up all night?
You want breakfast?
It's alright, when they wake up.
You're still a fugitive...
You can't meddle in other people's business.
Mr. Hairy, you're the one...
helped my mother, right?
Yeo-wool.
My name.
Hello?
Hey, I found a wallet.
I'll pay you 300,000.
It's upstairs, in my bed.
I found this number in the wallet.
It's her.
The woman who called me.
Do you know Pentaportra apartments in Cheongdam district?
Yes, yes, if he comes here I'll give it back to him.
Thank you very much, I'll go right away.
Good.
He used the same method to attract me.
We have to catch her.
"Complete cheat."
I need three minutes.
Yes how can I help you?
Hello?
Get off me, you fucking charlatans!
My son did not go!
Life in prison without parole.
Hello?
what the fuck...
Hello? You must be tired.
I understand what you're trying to do.
Hey pervert, do you like breathing on the phone?
Bastard, did you call me a pervert?
I'll rip your stomach open until your intestines fall out.
Crack...
Oh...
fucking crazy...
Are you really that bored?
You are lazy, aren't you? A parasite, stupid.
A parasite can not call? Bitch!
I'm sorry, Mom.
I just want to fuck, is that too much to ask?
Do my obscenities turn you on?
Obscenities turn you on, huh?
You are the pervert, you win me over.
Dear pervert customer...
jerk off if you're horny, this is not an erotic line.
You're a slut, fuck you bitch!
Hello?
It's done.
Hello? Is it Mr. Bae Young-deuk?
I'm calling from Goryeo Resources.
We have a night shift opening at a construction site.
Is available?
Yeah.
You've been discovered, get off the map.
It's him, right?!
It's the fugitive, call the police!
What the fuck is this?! Move the truck!
I'm sorry!
Leave it to you at once!
You rapist!
It's been a while, you son of a bitch!
He's coming to.
- Raise it up. - Yes Boss.
Do not resist.
Aren't you curious how I got out?
Damn, I'm curious too.
Remember this? You shot me with this.
There it goes.
Damn, look at that bastard.
Sujétenlo.
Kwon Yu, there he goes.
Give me the knife, I want to cut his mouth.
I'll make a big hole for you and bury you well...
so rest in peace, okay?
Fugitive Kwon Yu!
I'm calling now that the fugitive doesn't see me.
Please save me quickly.
We'll rescue you soon, stay calm.
Boss?
The cops want this motherfucker.
Do not listen to them.
The guy who took me out will take care of it.
"Miss Lee" Miss Lee, we have another task.
Don't do anything unnecessary.
- Boss, boss! - We'll be moving shortly.
The Central ordered us to withdraw.
What are you saying? We have a hostage in there.
I don't know, that was the order.
Official! Please!
He's trying to kill me, help me please!
Get in here you fucking idiots!
Come in! Come in! Come in!
- What's that? - What's going on?
We give up!
- We are allies. - Who are they?
We are on the same side.
Come up fast! hurry up
What happened?
You left this in the middle of the road.
Thank you!
how do you drive
I don't have a card.
That?
Get changed, I'll drive!
But by the way...
how did the cops know where he was?
Hey buddy!
Adjust the speed, asshole!
Stop the car, bastard!
Let's make your hole!
I have it in the ass like a hunting dog.
Bastard! Flip the car!
Turn around!
Boss, we're on a ramp...
Turn around, dammit!
What's that?
Radiodetector.
Yong_guru did it.
Why is that there?
Wait wait!
Wait.
We lost your signal there, search carefully.
When you catch Kwon, you will be a free man.
So he got me out of jail to bury Kwon.
Must have power...
Focus on catching Kwon.
Or you'll go back to jail.
Did you hang up on me?
He gave you your mother's necklace...
but did it contain a tracker?
And those gangsters should be in prison?
Without Mr. Hairy, the captain might be in a grave.
Who really is that lawyer?
Shouldn't we go after the lawyer first?
Yong_guru...
do you know how to make drones?
¿Drones?
How are you? And the sign?
Clean.
Wait.
Leather jacket, is it new?
Mr. Hairy bought it for me.
Oh really?
Yong is amazing with this.
Yong_guru, you are amazing.
I can't believe this guy is unemployed.
That skin smells...
My father used to beat me for being silly like that.
"Lawyer Min Chum-sang."
I reviewed the budget increase...
and transferred the money to the operatives.
Good job.
Can we hear what they say in the office?
It uses lasers to detect sound waves.
It's normal now.
We comply with your request.
All leaked documents are destroyed...
and related information is kept safe as secure.
You know that Kwon Yu ran away, right?
He already came here to visit.
Take care of it before it becomes a problem.
Min is more capable than we imagined.
Please reassure the board.
Long conversations can be compromising.
I'll see you at the meeting.
"Lawyer Min Chum-sang."
Is that wretch a puppet?
How can you organize it in that dilapidated office?
You need loads of servers, that place doesn't seem appropriate.
Maybe they have one outside.
Yong, did you bring the metal scanner?
Send another drone.
Let's scan the building.
Shit, is it embedded in there?
It's like a safe.
If they built a fortress...
it means they have secrets they want to protect, right?
Mr. Hairy can't you hack the site?
You could take control of his computer like you did to us.
I've tried, but I can't get through the firewall.
Damn.
Everything would be solved if we went inside.
Negative, any ideas?
No one can enter unless someone opens the door.
Let's call the cops.
And if they are with them?
So let's get into the media.
Did Mr. Hairy's video get aired?
She's hiding because that put her on a watch list.
I have an idea.
Hello?
We have a problem.
- What's happening? - Noh's apartment was vandalized.
"You are finished, Min Chun-sang."
They cleaned up all the traces...
and they mixed various hair samples together.
We cannot know whose they are.
It's good.
How can you laugh?
The news will be out tomorrow.
Now what?
Let's delay D-Day.
Have the workers clean this place up.
Send Noh's corpse to a discreet location.
A country motel, perhaps.
And come back to collect samples.
Dad, any news on that bastard Min?
How long do I have to stay here?
The food is crap and I can't stand the smell!
¡ Min Chum-sang!
- Is that how you work? - President Chu!
Do you know what my daughter is suffering right now?!
I raised her like a princess.
We all work day and night...
please be patient with us.
Give me the money! Answer!
Give me my money!
Fuck...
Hell, everything pisses me off.
Who's the bastard?!
Well try it.
One two three!
"Party and event planners".
"We know what they're doing."
What the hell?
Motherfucker! For! Please!
Kwon Yu is going after all of our operatives.
We can hire new people.
Do you want Chu's fights to continue?
Let's finish the job first.
No need to worry about Kwon...
I have it under control.
News time.
Let's see them together.
I'm in a vacant motel in Yesan.
The body of actor Noh Joon-young was found in a motel, after a week missing.
We received the information that Noh Joon-young was killed.
Forensics are on the scene...
They can't come in here!
Stand aside! move away!
¡ Es Chu Ye-ri! ¡Es Chu Ye-ri! Chu Ye-ri!
Take photos!
"The dead body of actor Noh Joon-young found in a motel".
Dad, how long do I have to stay here?
The food is crap and I can't stand the smell!
Chu Ye-ri, the daughter of President Chu of the Hyosin Group...
was found at the crime scene...
and arrested for murdering Noh.
What the hell is going on?! Why was my daughter there?!
It will be hard to deny the charges.
Facing a tidal wave of criticism, President Chu faces...
the biggest threat of his life.
"Unknown number".
- Kwonyu? -Did you like him?
I copied your method.
Well, it was very surprising.
It's weird to be flattered by someone you want to kill.
It's true, lately it was very boring.
I got a high that is turning me on!
Time had passed.
Can you understand it?
This was pretty funny at first.
People were going to jail based on the scenarios I created...
and with the article he wrote, people laughed...
cried, or got angry.
The feeling of success...
So what, it's still a job, and it gets boring over time.
Everything is the same.
But lately I'm elated.
You are a threat.
No one has ever challenged me before...
but when you came after me...
It bothered me, but it was also amazing!
Hello?
How dare you hang up while I'm talking.
hung up...
what a jerk
That's the problem.
I can't communicate with millennials.
It's very serious.
Stupid millennials!
It wasn't asking for much, was it?!
I was talking on the phone!
I can not comunicate! I do not understand them!
That hurts a lot.
It really hurts...
Are you still asleep?
Get up!
Were you up all night playing?
What about a dojo?
No taekwondo.
I'll fix it for you.
I will never do taekwondo again.
Please read this, my son is not a murderer!
Please read this.
Isn't it fun?
Please read this!
It gets better towards the end.
Ah, I'm sorry for killing your mom.
I know it's late, but I apologize.
Be good and listen to me...
Listen to me...
It is important...
Wait! Wait!
It's very important, you might regret...
Do you know why it happened to you?
You were born to horrible parents.
Motherfucker!
I know you feel bad...
but that doesn't excuse you...
for hitting someone older.
Psychopath...
Anyway, it's almost time.
"Mr. Hairy."
You should answer.
Yeo-wool? Hello?
Damn, let's meet again!
Team Name:: Resurrection.
Yong_guru, Demolition, Negative space...
and Mr. Hairy.
They will all die because of you.
If you touch them I'll kill you, you son of a bitch!
Sorry to return threat with threat...
but if you continue with this, they will all die.
I think I have broken ribs.
I knew you would come to steal my information...
That's why I sent Ma after your team.
The server is huge. It will take about 30 minutes.
Although with that you will be a free man.
But your friends will die like dogs.
That's a shame.
I will kill you and rescue my companions.
I'm sorry for your tenacity...
but I told Ma that if I don't call him in 15 minutes...
I had to execute them all.
Maybe I shouldn't have.
Take the information and that's it.
You ran away to clear your name...
shouldn't you take care of that?
Forget them.
Nobody cares if they die.
Sooner or later they will all die...
I forgot to mention something, sorry.
That friend of yours, Mr. Hairy.
Yoon-wool.
It will be our substitute.
My men should be collecting your samples now.
Mr. S.S. Hairy!
"Hermit Hacker Murders Noh Actor".
The news will hit the internet in the morning.
Fantastic, isn't it?
He may be a genius.
For! For bastard!
And your other friends...
I ordered Ma to kill them now.
By the time you get there they'll be dead...
so get out of town.
You will arrive in time to feel their cold bodies.
Do not do it! Motherfucker!
Fuck!
You shouldn't have touched me.
bastard!
Do you know why they will die?
Who should I kill first?
Please wait!
Old man, you first.
Negative!
He is not dead?
What is this?
Wait! Let's talk! We can fix this!
It's defective?
He never served in the Army.
- Mr. Furry! - Get rid of her.
Get her out of here!
Don't do it! You bastards!
Give me your gun.
Moron!
Wait! Wait!
Let's talk! Let's talk! Don't shoot me!
We can talk about this!
Look at me! Ugly piece of shit!
Look at me, fuck!
Do not shoot! Do not do it! Bastard!
I can not concentrate! Shut the fuck up!
Do you want to die first?
I have a mother...
Good.
You will die first anyway.
Wait, sir, wait, wait a minute!
What happened? What's going on?!
I think it's a blackout.
A fucking blackout?!
Boss! There!
High! Stop shooting! Fuck!
High! High!
Light the lighter!
Is dead?
You found it?
hurry up hurry up
Negative, quick!
Stop there!
catch him! The one in the fur jacket!
High!
Faster! Faster!
Behind them!
Greyhound!
They are coming!
Why are they running away? He fights fucking good!
Car ahead!
It is very narrow! Impossible! High!
Come on!
Damn!
Is it the best you can do?
Call Yong-pal!
That?
Bring Yong-pal, you jerk!
Bring the car!
Hey, Ma...
I will send you the location of Kwon Yu.
so catch it please!
Boss, I'm here!
Yong-pal to the rescue!
I'll get you anyway!
It seems fun.
Why don't I give you a hand?
It's the loudmouth.
- What the hell? - How about a ride on the roller coaster?
Yong-pal, come on! Come on!
Come on! Come on!
Ah... there!
There!
Careful, careful!
Where I am?
What are those?!
Catch the bastard.
Understood?
Catch the bastard! Fuck!
Is it the TV station?
I would like to give a notice.
It's about the fugitive Kwon Yu...
Is that son of a bitch really trying to kill us?
I feel terrible.
It's almost time for the news.
Motherfucker.
- Last News! - Informative advance!
- Just arrived! - Identified the murderer of Noh...
such as the fugitive Kwon Yu.
Kwon Yu, killed Noh and kidnapped Chu Ye-ri. It's the real killer.
Police CCTV shows Kwon Yu...
and his followers, known as "Resurrection"...
kidnapping and taking Chu Ye-ri to the crime scene.
The problem is the motley crew.
Kwon Yu's followers helped him kill. Delivered to video games...
homemade bombs...
A psychotic criminal gang on a crime spree.
They called us a psychotic criminal gang.
Damn! Now the cops are after us!
It is getting worse.
Get him before the cops!
Whoever catches it has a great prize!
Kwon Yu, are you a game addict?
"President Chu."
Mr. Min, she knew she would get out!
He's a genius!
We will be fine?
We almost arrive.
While the fugitive Kwon was imprisoned...
he was known for regularly assaulting his fellow inmates.
Perhaps our society has created a monster.
Considering the revenge killings...
We are safe?
Do you have that?
They come here, two cranes!
Yeo-wool went down, catch her.
Yeo-wool is the girl.
It's your last chance.
Dude, I'm busy, I...
Damn, did he hang up again?!
He has no manners!
Good, let's go!
Attention please.
There are armed intruders in the studio. Please vacate the building. Attention...
Faster Faster!
Can you all hear me?
- Yes captain. - Captain.
- Captain. - Received.
We have to buy Mr. Hairy time while he gets ready.
And thank you all...
for helping me.
How many times have you saved our asses?
Especially Mr. Hairy.
She leveled up by following the captain.
We will annihilate them.
This is not a game.
It could be really dangerous.
Well here we go.
Captain, I request orders.
Okay, Resurrection, are you ready?
Let's fight without regrets.
Received.
Yong_guru, waiting.
Calm, calm, calm...
Yeah!
Demolition, shoot them when I pass.
Don't worry.
It will be like the Dark Knight.
When you pass and the crane arrives...
I'll lift them up with my cable.
I told you I worked in the movie industry.
Shit, that's not good.
I knew you were just a facade.
Bump into him!
Get through it!
Captain, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Ready for the next phase!
Good job Yong_guru!
Yeah!
Demo! The captain draws them to you!
Not yet! It's not ready!
No, no, not yet!
demo now!
Good demo! Next phase!
Mr. Furry! Furry!
What's going on? Yeo-wool?
Be quiet!
I'm sorry!
It's my fault!
Stay still!
¡Yeo-wool! ¡Yeo-wool! ¡Yeo-wool!
Bye you scumbag!
Bastard!
Yeo-wool, cross over!
For!
Boss! I'm here!
Asshole, shoot well!
Sorry boss! What happened?
fucking useless...
Closer, closer, closer...
- Captain! - Yeo-wool, come up!
No way!
0187, found suspicious vehicle.
Going through the Sangam junction.
18, I request reinforcements.
All units go to Sangam Junction.
Command center, send reinforcements.
Go around the TV station.
18, cut his retreat route, lure him to the third block.
Elite marksmen, you can open fire.
The suspect may be armed.
The fugitive Kwon Yu is coming!
He may be here to turn himself in.
They are watching a live broadcast.
"Live broadcast of Kwon Yu's arrest."
What about this?
Wake up, we are here.
We are already here?
Captain, I brought in Support and Recon.
Captain, I missed you!
There she goes again.
Captain, was it hard?
It's good to hear them.
Mr. Hairy, did you get all the data?
Altogether.
Mr. Hairy will block the normal news and broadcast ours.
Do this right.
They'll melt if you keep up with it.
- What nerves... - Ready?
The truth about the killer of the century, Kwon Yu.
We will offer it to you exclusively by entering 69.
Did he really kill the sexy Noh Joon-young?
That's the truth?
My daughter screwed up.
He is an actor named Noh Joon-young.
I think he is a failure.
He is the president of Hyosin Group, right?
Dad, I'm hungry.
That bitch is the Noh killer.
So what is the truth behind Kwon Yu's rape and murder?
My son made a mistake, he must have been drunk.
At his age he is prone to mistakes, even to kill.
You must be nervous before the big day.
- That is not you? - That?
Who murdered Ha Ji-su...
I'm screwed up...
He was the son of Councilor Park, who wrote the Kwon Yu law.
But instead Kwon Yu was arrested.
Did you see the news?
Will Kwon make it to the trial?
- I'm Min Chum-sang. - Sons of bitches!
"Sons of bitches"...
I'm turning red...
This is news!
Ms. Lee... Ms. Read?
Aren't you curious about the master of this puppet?
Min, I'm in trouble. I killed my wife by accident.
"A drifter arrested for murder."
His corpse will be found inside...
from a container, tomorrow in Jamsil.
What are you guys doing?
- They have done? - Min!
You saved my neck!
Thank you!
"Identity of Busan Torso Killer Revealed".
It was a great idea.
How should I pay you?
My office manager will call you soon.
Mr. Min, you are a genius.
Yes, it may be.
His is innate.
Detectives please. I'm sorry!
They should tear it to pieces.
People were going to jail based on the scenarios I created...
and with the article he wrote, people laughed...
Min Chum-sang is the son of a bitch who controlled everything.
Enough. bastards...
This is the guy who deserves to die.
¡Paren!
We will issue our data before delivering it...
so anyone harmed by it will be able to use them.
And officers, catch Min before he takes off!
How dare you challenge me?
The steering wheel...
Min Chum-sang, I took your flyer, you son of a bitch!
What do we do? He is completely unmasked.
Don't worry, it's replaceable.
One wrongful conviction is worse than losing ten criminals.
Aren't they smarter now?
Anyone can be framed.
That ends today's news.
I'm the sexy girl, Support.
Good! Very good!
Next.
¡Sr. Ma!
Excellent!
Is he?
Guys, what are you doing? They shouldn't do that.
Kwon Yu, who was framed and jailed for murder...
he was cleared of all charges and became a free man.
The authorities are also collecting public opinions...
on compensation for wrongfully convicted...
and the prevention of future similar convictions.
- The real murderer of Ha Ji-su - Honey, there are the keys!
And Councilor Park's son...
Park Jae-hyun was arrested after hiding in a motel for 40 days.
Everybody said...
that the tree was rotting.
But I told them...
which was far from it.
That night I had a dream.
In dream...
I saw the tree growing strong towards the blue sky.
I got everyone together and told them...
that the tree was not rotting.
This tree...
it is not a rotten tree.