ANSAN CITY OF HAPPINESS
This is Ansan 2-1, 2464, go ahead.
- We're going through 4-15, over. - Understood.
Turn to 2-1, 2813.
1-8, in distance.
Good.
Damn unfortunate thief.
Motherfucker.
I told you to come right after finishing.
I'm sorry.
Bring the tools.
What is the total?
Twenty-eight thousand.
- Hey. - That?
don't fuck with me One two...
I'm sorry.
Motherfucker. I saw you save more before.
I cannot neglect myself for a moment.
You always steal from me, you son of a bitch.
SAL MARINA NATURAL
bring us luck...
Don't do that shit.
What thing? Turn around.
We never got caught thanks to this, asshole.
If you don't listen to me, I'll beat you to the ground.
Yes, sure.
Yes Gi-Chul. Come here.
That?
Suck it, idiot.
Get the hell out of the way.
Damn fucking cop.
Jo Pil-ho: The Awakening of Anger
SOOKIE'S - PIG BONE SOUP
Hello. Is Mr. Wong here?
- Who speaks? - I?
We did water skiing a while ago. I'm Stephanie.
And with that? Did you sleep with him?
Why do you ask?
Yes or no?
Aren't you a prostitute?
I am the wife of that bastard!
Listen, honey.
Even if you're the wife, you can't ask if we slept.
Listen to this, whore.
Have a little respect.
What a stupid thing.
It's ok I understand.
If Mr. Wong comes back,
tell him I have the Viagra ready, to call me.
Do you have fun? You like me?
Don't ask me to do it again!
You must be an actress. You are very good.
You were nice.
It's me. I'm sending you a number. Get the call log.
That?
I told you before, he's the guy who disappeared with my money.
The number is his wife's, and he's going to call him right away.
Yeah.
Send me a text with the location. Good.
The prosecution executed a search and capture process in the Taesung Group
and is looking for the missing $780 million
which in theory were used as illicit funds.
Director Yi-Hyang Jung is under investigation...
Our largest corporation steals like nothing.
Investigation is a political move
to smear Taesung Group.
We didn't do anything wrong...
Seven hundred and eighty million?
Just give me $78,000 and I'll make you loose.
ANSAN POLICE STATION, DANWON DISTRICT
TRY 1 MACHETE
TEAM 2 HOMICIDE
Go ahead, over there.
- These morons! - Hey you!
They were hired to make doors, but they made knives.
- What are you saying...? - What the hell is your name?
You Azim! Again here?
Are you running guns now?
Fool!
Spit out the gum! How dare you!
Shall.
If Internal Affairs finds out, I'm down too.
You had another child, right?
- Idiot. - Another mouth to feed.
Eat the noodles and don't get high.
See you later. Say no to drugs.
You said you had a job at a soup shop, but if you smoke pot,
- how do you make me look? - Lord's word.
HOLY BIBLE
- Be good. - Amen.
What a sweet asshole.
Hey, Pil-Ho Jo!
Shit.
Ho, Ho, Johnson, shrink dick!
Where are you going?
Don't mess with my last name.
- Whoops! - Oh really...
Oh.
Honestly, at least wait until the sun goes down.
Do you already do tricks in bright light?
Go touch it to someone else.
Why do you always bother me?
You have a very big mouth for someone with such a small penis.
Holy shit.
What a dirty mouth.
Is Internal Affairs just promoting profanity now?
- That? - Alright.
Pil-Ho, this won't be like last time, when you slipped away.
I'll even search your anus and send you to Chungsong Jail.
- Oh really? - Yeah.
Too bad my car doesn't have GPS.
I wouldn't know how to get there.
Remember "Bones of Glass" Gibs, the brittle gangster?
He's been busy ever since he took over Mr. Yeom's building.
But something was smelly, so I investigated
and found out that someone convinced him.
A public servant like you, a policeman.
That cop even put up $300,000 to buy the building.
What would we have to do?
Lock him up and fuck it. It is not obvious?
Hey.
This is not advice
But you can't keep putting on a poker face.
Leave.
Stop fucking around, idiot.
How's the food, damn it?
It will give you a fit. Come and sit down.
imbeciles. They are hungry?
How can they eat now?
Go ahead, eat.
They just delivered it. I didn't even dip the chopsticks.
As soon as I got your money, they started snooping around.
Why does that jerk from Internal Affairs want to eat you alive?
I shouldn't have taken your money.
What the hell?
Let's make a clean slate.
Still, you were going to quit.
Let's sell the building before the AI ​​get any closer
and dedicate ourselves to alcohol.
With your network and my manpower, there is nothing to fear.
Can you get a loan for $200,000?
We have to cover expenses.
Two hundred thousand?
Do you think money rains?
Where do I get $200,000, idiot?
Then what do we do?
If we can't pay, we will lose all the money.
Our money will be gone! You understand?
Are you an Adidas model or something?
How dare you look at me like that?
What's wrong with that crazy woman?
Hey, Gi-Chul Han. Gi-Chul Han!
you misunderstood That night I was with Sung-Jin.
- Give me the bag. - Not even in dreams.
If you continue like this, ours is over.
- Yeah? We're done then. - Hey!
Let go! Let me!
Do not call me Anymore. I am going to kill you!
Mine! Wait!
Mina Jang, don't go!
Hey!
It is a misunderstanding! Mine please!
Was she the schoolgirl you mentioned?
How does it feel to be beaten up by a girl?
She is not like that.
How not, idiot.
- What is the total? - Twenty-eight thousand.
- So $59,000 combined? - Yeah.
Fiftynine thousand...
Why suddenly? Something happens?
Hey. Let's do one more job.
A big one.
It's an untraceable phone.
The alarm will stop working at 3:00. Then we'll go in.
Brother, this is not right.
Do you want to rob a police warehouse?
I'm not up to it.
They will give us at least 10 years.
Are you afraid?
I became a cop because cops scare me.
Don't worry, they won't catch us.
walking.
I'll be right back, boss.
Are you going on a trip, asshole?
Green wire, green wire...
Huh?
Why it takes so long?
CALLING...
RECENT CALLS
Report your status.
2-1 turn, change.
You cut the green, didn't you?
- By the way, I'm color blind, boss. - Yes, and?
I can't tell green from red.
And?
- What did you say? - Well...
They were both brown, so I cut both of them.
Are you crazy?
That?
We're fucking ruined!
Shit!
What can I do with him?
Why is he so calm?
Shit.
Hey. Gi-Chul. Gi Chul Han!
Friend! Get out of there!
What the fuck?
What the hell...?
- Are you awake? - What the fuck?
He's in a hospital.
I will look for its guardian.
You ran into a fire, and there was an explosion?
But was it a police depot?
Yeah.
Even a dog would laugh in your face.
Do not believe me.
We have a dead body, idiot!
Internal Affairs is reviewing all your calls!
You...
I'm not interested in knowing what happened.
But, Pil-Ho,
when you eat pasta and get dirty with sauce,
don't pretend it's something else.
Wipe off the sauce and act like nothing happened.
Back to work.
Damn.
- The boss already reviewed it. - That?
But I had hidden it!
- Did you kill him? - That?
- That guy. - Hear what you say.
- You are having fun? - Do not yell at me!
Damn.
Curse.
Everything burned, sir. What do we do?
DISTRICT ATTORNEY
Stand up straight.
Send a written apology you useless assholes.
Yes, it's me.
Did you verify that everything is gone?
Yes, confirmed.
Good job.
I'm sorry.
I bother you?
It burned. Can you get it back?
How nice.
New facilities and everything.
We treat everyone very well
but it seems they keep reporting poisonings here.
They bite the hand that feeds them.
How much longer?
I'm kind of busy.
Two hours?
Two days?
Do you know the Chilean dictator, Pinochet?
He killed 3,000 people in a week on a soccer field.
Divide that by seven days and you get 428.
It killed 428 people per day. It's amazing, isn't it?
414 researchers work here,
he could have killed everyone here in one day.
One day.
But does it take two days to get a phone back?
Keep going.
This is what happens when a man burns out.
It's not a man, it's a corpse.
A corpse. Yeah.
I had not seen a charred body.
Damn bastard, he had to die in there.
Have more respect for the deceased. No?
I'm sorry Mr.
His airways are clear. He died before the fire.
- That? - Look here.
A strong trauma. She broke her head.
- Before burning. - Aside.
What is this?
So how did he split his head?
I do not know? That is his job.
Did you find Han's cell phone?
I did not see it.
With a clear airway, does that mean you didn't suffocate?
Is this a homicide?
What is this? That?
This is from today.
Wait! High!
Those sandals...
Shit. Damn.
A shot to the head.
SORRY FOR MY FAMILY. SORRY FOR THE VICTIMS.
Jae-Man Hwang, the owner of the warehouse.
He set it on fire to collect the insurance.
But I didn't know there was someone inside.
Did you burn the deposit to collect the insurance?
Yes, it seems so.
I'll take care.
Yes sir?
- I know whose motorcycle it is. - Oh really?
Send it to me by text.
Hwang is dead.
Things got complicated!
I ran to a public place. Please come find me.
The Taesung Group caught Hwang!
Think about it.
Hwang was found dead a day after the fire.
They don't want to leave traces!
I will present myself with evidence as a witness.
I have the detonator too.
I'll stay here, so call me, okay?
I'm done.
Shit!
- What the fuck? - What a shame.
Give it back to me?
What a work of art.
This is very extrange.
HOPE PUB
Welcome.
Can I have a beer?
Doesn't a girl work part time here?
He makes deliveries on a motorcycle. She has short hair.
Out to make a delivery?
Aren't you Detective Pil-Ho Jo from the Danwon District?
Who are you?
It does not remember me?
Sorry?
I am Ji-Won Song's father.
¿Ji-Won Song?
Forehead...
That scar.
Stop crying like a bitch.
I'm sorry.
- Hurry up. - Yeah.
- Get me water. - Right away!
Moron.
...a symbolic uniform for Song's father.
Ji-Won Song, victim of the Sewol ferry shipwreck,
I dreamed of being a policeman
which caused grief to his own.
The police put together this event to comfort his family.
The commissioner is coming!
- Hey. - Yeah?
Dude, finish now.
Send two to the scene and let's go to the funeral.
SEWOL FERRY WRECK RESCUE LIST
There are more bodies of children. No time for that.
Hey!
- What madness! - The boss is looking for you!
What the fuck are you doing?
Let me in! Oh my God!
What's the matter? Damn!
Don't come near!
- Why did you arrive so late? - Journalists...
Look here please.
Mr Song!
Mr Song! This way, sir!
Can you look over here?
Here, sir!
Mister!
Mr Song!
ALTAR IN MEMORY OF THE SEWOL FERRY WRECK
The whole town is in mourning.
I saw some officers going to the scene.
Shouldn't you go too?
I'm too sensitive to go there.
- It's the police. Inspections. - What's that?
Open the door.
What do we do?
What do you mean by that? I am also a policeman.
What's happening?
Mister. What is he doing here?
What do you think I do? God.
I'm sorry.
Boss...
I was... Sir, it's not that...
I was going to clean...
She brought me underwear.
- Find them! - Right away!
You should have called me. What's going on?
The father who received the uniform this morning...
- That? He-he left a will and disappeared.
They report that they saw him here.
If he kills himself, we're screwed.
You're right.
Mr Song! Don't do this!
- Let me go! - Don't do this!
You have to stay calm.
Easy with him! Don't hurt him!
- Why can't I kill myself? - Please calm down.
We'll take him to the hospital first.
- Let's talk. - Grab him!
- Oh really? - You must go to the hospital!
He did not live even 20 years.
I was 17 years old. She was a girl.
- Let's just talk. - Sir, we hear you.
We understand how you feel, but you can't do this to us.
Come on, grab it.
¡Agárrenlo!
Sir, are you okay?
Shit!
Walk him outside!
- Mr. Song, come on. - Enough.
Pilho, are you okay?
- Get up please. - Get up, see.
Let's see.
- Motherfucker! - Hey!
Am at home.
- Sorry for the mess. - Alright.
Please pass.
No, I have very dirty feet.
Alright. Forward.
Well.
Ji Won, do you remember? He brought you the police uniform.
MY DREAM IS TO BE A POLICEMAN.
I found it.
It's her. Mina Jang.
They were best friends in elementary school, but she got in trouble.
What kind of problems?
He lived with his grandmother
but he became rebellious when the old woman died.
They kicked her out of school, too.
And the motorcycle was stolen?
Yes, he stole Ji-Won's clothes, shoes, and a backpack.
But didn't you report it?
She's not a terrible girl.
I thought it would be a bad influence on Ji-Won.
But he secretly organized birthday parties for my daughter in the basement.
Is mine in trouble?
No, I need it for a case I'm investigating.
Haven't seen this in a while. She keeps it well.
- What is this jump rope doing here? - I'm sorry.
- It's for dieting. - That?
It will be because I work in a chicken shop,
Ji-Won loved Korean food.
He would eat two servings and jump rope to lose weight.
I should have eaten less...
She doesn't look fat in the photo.
- She was pretty. She put it here. - Yeah.
Do you have Mina's phone number?
No.
You shouldn't protect her.
I don't know, actually.
It's not much, but share it with the other agents.
There's no need. I feel uncomfortable.
Too bad the boys like pizza.
Thank you so much.
Wait...
Yeah?
If he finds Mina,
Can you tell me to return Ji-Won's sportswear?
She was wearing it when she drowned on the ferry.
He wanted to burn it in his honor...
...but Mina took her away.
He wanted to send her to heaven.
Okay bye.
People are very simple.
They use the same password for the cell phone and the cards.
You deactivate the phone and use it to go crazy shopping.
Game over.
Good job, son of a bitch.
Alright?
Is very good.
Justifies the scar on my forehead.
- You better enjoy it. - Clear.
Good. I have it.
Let's see... What is this?
Oh. An unread text.
JIN-GYU SONG Do you know Mina's address?
¿ Jin-Gyu Song?
It's not my girl. How will I know?
Look for Mina Jang's Facebook, texts, her social networks
and transfer the data to your laptop. Do it.
Well.
Who is she?
Is beautiful.
Heavens.
Enough. It's obscene.
Some African tribes believe that by taking a photo
you take the soul of the person.
Take pictures of hands or something, not the face.
You have no respect for the dead.
I'm sorry Mr.
I miss the good old days.
Now everyone lost their common sense.
Mr. Kwon.
Yes sir?
One misstep and you're finished.
That feels good.
Shit. What do you want?
I live upstairs. There is a water leak.
- What waste of water? - Enters.
Let's see.
That?
Jin-Gyu Song, where is Mina Jang?
The fire chief is dead
and the detonator also disappeared.
With the witness missing, we were ordered to release Director Jung.
What I do?
You leave nothing to chance.
You killed everyone.
Soon you will be attorney general. Let's go out to dinner shortly.
The prosecution revoked the arrest of director Jung,
and changed the case to an investigation of witnesses.
The investigation into the missing $780 million is still pending.
Look at these ants trying to survive.
Ladies and gentlemen...
A desperate fight...
Mr. Principal!
What do you think of the result?
How does it feel?
Did they dismiss the charges?
Whose ethical responsibility is for missing funds?
A comment please.
Ladies and gentlemen, Taesung Group is the number one corporation in Korea.
But the prosecutor decided to roll our integrity through the mud.
Taesung
offers scholarships to needy students every year.
How am I going to stop saying that Korea is a constitutional and democratic nation?
As a parent from Korea, I feel very ashamed.
Mr. Principal!
Oh! Mr. Kwon, you do well on TV.
Oh! Exploded?
Yeah.
You took care of it, but is there another problem?
I'm sorry Mr.
This phone belonged to the one who died in the mortuary.
Did they send the video from that phone?
- Whom? - Two people, sir.
The first, Jin-Gyu Song, a three-time convicted felon.
- Her name is So-Hee. - Keep going.
She is Mina's minion.
- AND? - He's going to be with her.
The other?
Well...
It's police.
What an idiot...
Mr. Kwon?
Yes sir?
He's screwed, and he's going to jail by himself.
Friendship? What a stupid thing.
Stop your friendship nonsense. I'm going.
He is in room 6008.
Do you have guys there?
I don't know, I heard TV noise.
That?
Nothing, come on.
HOPE PUB
Mine Jang! Hey!
It's open.
What's happening?
- "Friendship" is your code? - That?
"Stop that friendship crap" is code for "there's a cop."
Of course not.
Yeah, sure, asshole.
Hey!
Enough! Bitch!
Let go! Fool!
Let me! What the fuck?
You!
High. Come with me.
- Do you remember me? - Who are you?
It hurts me!
- I said it hurt! - Hey! Enough!
What the hell!
- Enough! - Motherfucker!
Suéltala!
- Runs! - No! I won't leave without you!
Hey! Get off me!
- Curse! - Let go, idiot!
Shit! Hey!
What the fuck are you doing?
What's happening here?
Do something with them. Take them off me!
- I'll call the police! - Ma'am, I'm a policeman!
I am Police!
- May I go now? - Sure thanks.
- Damn traitor. - Fuck that.
See you.
Let's cut it short and get rid of it.
Wait.
She is sick. Can you let her sit down?
As?
She is very sick!
Sit down.
- Where is the money? - What money?
Again,
where is the money?
It wasn't from Gi-Chul.
Where is my $59,000?
Don't know. How will I know?
- Mina... - Are you okay?
You are suspicious. Do you want to go to correctional?
For the last time,
where is the money?
- You're not going to talk? - At home! I hid it there.
- Safe? - Is there.
Gather your things.
Are you the crooked cop Gi-Chul mentioned?
That?
He said a policeman made him do the whole scam.
Did he say that?
I won't let it go.
I'm going to expose you!
Yeah? What a pity. There are no witnesses.
He is dead.
Gi Chul Han is dead.
How he died?
- That? - Gi-Chul.
Who cares?
There's nothing to do.
I have a video.
- Give me my wallet. - What are you doing?
- Gi-Chul sent me a video. - What video? Sit down.
- I'll show you! - Damn!
- Sit down, Mine. - Stay still.
- I'll show you. - Heavens, damn it!
Stay seated, bitch.
You think I don't know your tricks?
You'll call someone to get the bag before I do.
I really have it!
Stay seated!
Stay in your fucking chair! How annoying are you, shit!
Do you feel like dying or something?
Mine! Are you OK?
What's happening?
- What the fuck? What happens? - Open your eyes.
She's epileptic!
You have to lie down!
What a fucking mess!
- Come on... - Let her go with this.
Mina, open your eyes.
Reaction to. Look at me.
- I do not believe this. - Mine...
How are you doing?
- Mine, let's go. - My phone.
Come on.
Mine, come on. Mine!
- We must go! - Shit!
Shit.
Shit!
Damn!
THE BOSS
We are almost there. Hurry up.
Come on!
What's happening?
What's going on?
My tummy hurts.
It will be because of the impact of before. It hurts me a lot.
- Hold on, please. - Mine!
Hello?
Anyone here? Someone?
Aid! Please!
Hey, look at this photo.
You declared that you were alone.
But who is next to you?
This?
I was driving and saw a foreign worker.
I felt bad and picked it up.
Yeah? Where did you pick it up and drop it off?
How will I know?
Go to the employment center, you will find many.
Don't get smart.
You killed Gi-Chul Han and set the place on fire.
Stop creating stories and bring me proof. Tests please.
The person responsible is dead and left a will. Because you follow me?
- I have a witness. - That?
We found him hiding in a motel room.
- Glad? - Take this off me.
Little dick Pil-Ho, you fucking son of a bitch.
- Finish it off. - Let go! What did the bitch say?
- What the fuck did you tell them? - Hey! Stay away!
Come here! What did you say? Fuck off!
- What the fuck did you tell them? - Hey! Don't worry!
- You don't know shit! - Come on!
Hey!
Let me interrupt.
Is that Johnson Pil-Ho Detective Jo Pil-Ho?
Detective Jo, we're here on the warehouse fire case.
The fire ruined the complex next door.
However, there was no wind. Weird, no?
You have a will.
That the owner wanted to collect the insurance?
Are you a detective and do you believe that story?
Listen, what was in the compound next door?
What do I know?
Twelve boxes of evidence against the Taesung Group,
about 400,000 illegal bond accounts for illicit funds.
You understand?
They were key pieces of evidence against Taesung.
But some sons of bitches burned them.
Then they passed us anonymous information from the fire chief who came.
He said that he and Taesung started the fire.
According to him, there was another person in the warehouse.
Who was this mysterious man?
Gi Chul Han.
Motherfucker!
What the fuck?
It gets more interesting.
Han's phone signal could only output video.
He sent this video just before he died.
Two people, no less, and I tracked them down.
One was an untraceable phone bought by a certain Johnson, who is...
You Pil-Ho Johnson!
We'll get back to that.
But why were you there? Did you steal?
Or are you also on Taesung's staff?
What's the problem?
you are pale
He doesn't know how to put on a poker face.
What are you doing?
Gi-Chul sent me a video.
May I smoke?
You're right. I bought the untraceable phone.
Did you hear that, Min-Jae Kim from Internal Affairs?
This prosecutor says I didn't burn the place down or kill Han.
Are you recording this?
I'm sorry.
You know how hard it is to be a homicide cop.
I was in the warehouse.
Han entered, and the building blew up.
I got scared and I went driving,
my phone started ringing. Maybe it was the video.
I got rid of him and got the hell out of there. That's all.
Shit, did I drop it while driving or after?
Who knew that it was so important?
Shit. Very sorry.
Drive? Humbug.
You woke up in a hospital. Are you trying to screw us?
Yeah?
I suffered a concussion.
NO SIGNAL
Wait your turn!
You're not that stupid.
Mr. Johnson, listen.
They have enough evidence to detain you for ten years.
If you leave the force, I can clean this shit up,
and you can live as a civilian.
Get me that video.
Damn.
Mine's address...
Curse! Is blocked!
Wait...
Please...
Sir, I just gave you my ID.
It's Mina's phone.
Shit.
Shit, I still feel the stun gun.
Very good!
That's all? Curse.
What is this?
Isn't that Mina Jang's house?
And?
I am your teacher at home.
- We had a date. - I see.
- It should happen. - Alright.
Happens.
The house is messy.
I'm a policeman.
The young woman is in trouble.
That sure doesn't surprise you.
I'm done here, but you can stay.
What is this?
Can I see your phone? Is it from Mina?
That?
So your teacher, right?
Who are you?
Shit.
Motherfucker!
Where is?
Hang on a minute.
I think there is a misunderstanding.
I'm a cop, you son of a bitch!
Shit!
I will remember your face!
Are you Mina Jang?
An adult asked you a question.
Who are you? What the hell you want?
Millennials...
...have no manners.
Please do not kill me.
I'm sorry, your life is a nuisance.
What the fuck?
Heavens, what the fuck? Wait, come on.
My God, what are they doing in my garden?
Why do they wallow like wild pigs?
Lady! Call the police!
OMG, look at my lettuce!
I'll pay you for the damage! Call the police!
Where is he going?
You have to pay me for the damages!
Damn. Goes up!
It is dangerous. Goes up!
- Who was? - I don't know.
Do not lie to me. I almost died to save you.
I Do not Really Know! Why were they at my house?
Despite everything, you escaped with the money?
Hey. Did you want to hit me with the pot?
I wasn't aiming at you!
Of course! You wanted to keep the bag!
Yesterday you hit me with the stun gun.
They want you for robbery, fraud and homicide.
Shit. you are finished
- You're bleeding. - That?
- You bleed! - Do not do it!
Do not touch me.
Damn.
What did you do with the rest of my money?
- I spent it. - Did you spend it?
Did you spend $30,000? A student?
We have things to buy.
Damn. There is no end in sight.
Damn!
Who the fuck was it?
Oh yeah, the phone... It was on the floor. Did you bring it?
I have it. Because?
Thank God. I almost got hit from behind.
Han fucked me up big time.
He killed Gi-Chul?
Wait. If what the prosecutor said is true...
- ...this is incredible. -Did she die for me?
Don't yell at me, you fucking thief.
- Give me the phone. - Not even in dreams.
bird.
Come on. Demons...
Let go! Take your hands off me.
Lady.
- Is blocked. unlock it. - Because?
You said he sent you a video.
Is that why he died?
Before... Forget it.
Listen, you didn't see the video.
Unlock the phone, and I'll forget about the money you stole.
Unlock it now.
- You do not feel like? - First, take off my handcuffs.
Why are you always negotiating?
You're a nuisance, for a girl.
Come with me somewhere, and I'll unlock the phone.
We have to do it now. She died.
Who is the dad?
GUARDIAN CONSENT FORM
He's a jerk.
But you have to tell your parents, at least.
Why are you pretending to be an adult? Sign and go.
Damn kids.
Take. hand it over
2-5-8-6? I thought she had tried.
Mr. Prosecutor, this video will be a tidal wave if it leaks.
Keep your promise to clear my file.
Detective Jo, did you cause any trouble in Ansan today?
- That? - We got a report.
We are looking for a young woman named Mina Jang.
Do you know anything about her?
Because she?
She's a key witness. If you find it,
I'll give him a promotion on top of everything.
I'm with her now.
Then bring it to me. Be discreet.
control.
Your uncle?
- More like his pimp. - That?
- It must be great. You will make a fortune. - Go to hell.
Take.
I'll give you 100 back. Let me try it.
I told Mina that I would do the abortion in return,
but he did not accept it.
I'm dying to try it.
He even brought you. What a disappointment.
Good. Heavens! I'll give you 100 more!
But I keep it all night.
As you promised, tonight is the night.
- Hey. I'm a policeman, come out. - He's a cop. Police!
Why did you chase them away?
What's happening?
What are you doing?
Come.
One tablespoon.
No.
Come on.
Isn't that too salty?
- Thank you. - Alright. Eat.
It's good?
Why didn't you make something healthier?
They like. It is not good?
- Yes, give him clothes to change into. - Well.
Take off those sports clothes.
- Because? - It is not obvious?
It was from your friend Ji-Won.
How do you know Ji-Won?
Does it surprise you?
We knew each other a long time.
His dad wants the clothes.
Even if she was your best friend, you can't wear the clothes of a dead man.
Give it away.
- This is cute. - Change out.
Take.
Not even in dreams.
What are you doing?
- Heavens. - No.
- Raise it up. - I don't want to.
I won't do it. It's mine, she gave it to me!
You can't make me change!
- Shit! What are you staring at? - Enough!
Damn...
Spooky.
Whatever, but you shouldn't swear during the meal, right?
Did you see the movie The Throne?
"Clean your ears."
- Pretend you didn't hear that. - Yeah.
let's leave it. What do we do with these girls?
Eat. Alright.
Aside.
- Take. - That?
- What are you doing here? - What is this, love?
Don't be so happy. It's not for you.
That?
- Give him something healthy. - Clear.
Nothing pork. Buy authentic Korean beef.
- Don't let her out of your sight. - That?
To her.
He is asking for help.
That? What's happening? Why are you looking at me?
Do you have something to say?
Did you always have that scar?
And if so?
Haven't we met before?
Us?
Are you flirting with me?
It's got to be a joke, baby.
Listen.
Give the set back to his dad.
Imagine what he must be suffering. He wanted to burn it in honor of her.
I know how you feel.
You lost your friend, you're a teenager. We all go through the same thing.
And your doll...
I went through all that: drinking, motorcycles, that shit.
- What do you know? - That?
What the fuck do you know?
We were going so well!
You're an asshole for pretending you know everything!
You are the idiot! Heavens!
You have a problem with your attitude.
I wonder what you will be when you grow up.
- Attack the titans. - That?
I will be the titan of that series.
I will destroy the president's house and kill everyone.
Do you take drugs?
Asshole, make it shine.
What do they do? Idiots, do you want to steal the bike?
What do they do? Stop doing that.
You need to cut the boot, you newbie morons.
What the hell is going on here?
- Damn... - What the hell did you say?
- That? - Come on.
Damn.
You really are a policeman.
I'm a fucking loyal public servant.
Can you give me that?
Well. Take. Heavens.
What's happening? Do not you want to go?
There is nothing wrong.
You just go and tell them what you know from the video.
Yeah?
Let's go to Ji-Won's chicken shop.
That?
I'll give you the jacket back, so let's go.
Don't you want to go alone?
And you buy me chicken.
The last time I ate it was with Ji-Won.
It's good?
Very good.
Fine, deal done.
Why must we meet here?
Hello? I'm here.
What the fuck?
Prosecutor?
Welcome.
Oh, no.
Take your hands off me.
Hello. So you are Mina Jang. Come on.
Here we go. We are not bad.
Hey, Pil-Ho Jo.
- You see? She knew that she had a premonition. - Motherfucker!
You really are a fucking Korean prosecutor.
Definitely a bona fide one.
I have a Taesung scholarship.
Why did you tell him that?
I had a hard time setting up the number for Taesung.
You look well.
Shit.
Detective Jo, it's a duplicate phone. Where is the one from that night?
How the fuck am I supposed to know?
Let's see...
Let me ask you again. Han sent this to two people.
- Where is the original video? - I don't know, idiot.
- Put your hand here. - Let go!
You must answer when I ask you well.
Detective Jo, for the last time...
This is the girl's, and this is yours.
Where is the telephone?
Fuck off, you idiot.
You're the best.
Above.
I'll close the deposit case like an accident,
so fix everything with the means.
Hey, Pil-Ho Jo...
Good job.
Study hard or you will be like him.
You have to live, study, travel and have boyfriends.
Tell me where you hid the video or you will die like Jin-Gyu Song.
You did not know? Her silence killed him.
Do not look at me like that. I didn't kill him.
- Mister? - Yeah?
Fuck off.
Stop, you son of a bitch.
Why are you threatening a girl?
- Let her go, and we can talk. - This scares me.
Hold on tight.
- If I fall, I'll take you with me. - Yes Boss.
Jo, if you keep lying, my arm gets tired.
I have it! Stop, wretch!
I have it. I have the original video.
- Where? - In a safe place.
I'll send it to you by FedEx. Let her go.
Damn! In the office closet.
I hid it at the police station. You will never find it.
I'll bring it to you. Let the girl go, and we'll talk.
Motherfucker! There is no other copy!
- Fuck me? - Enough.
- Oh really? - Stop it, idiot!
Damn!
Go home. You can go home.
Alright.
Good. Your telephone. Where is my wallet?
How much is it?
Here's a little more.
Buy yourself a nice phone with this.
We'll take you to the police station to deliver the video.
- Keep your promise. - Got it, asshole.
Prepare the car.
That? Do you have something to say?
OK tell me.
Idiots.
What an example of adults they are...
They are idiots and they are called adults.
Tell So-Hee I'm sorry.
Shit. She is crazy?
Throw it at him too.
throw it away
Let go! Hey! I have the video, you hear me?
You won't be safe if you kill me!
Internal Affairs saw me racketeering with the prosecutor.
- They know everything about the video! - Hey! Aside!
Hey! If Internal Affairs finds it, you're finished.
Why do you complicate everything?
Pay me and I'll give it to you.
They are all rich, right?
- Put him in the car. - Yes sir.
Damn.
You should eat fewer late-night snacks.
I went up a couple sizes, right? I have too many dinner dates.
Listen! Pil-Ho Jo!
An ex-marine, right? I was too.
Aren't you going to come?
- I salute you. - How gullible.
My family is exempt.
I thought it was tough. I like you, Detective Jo.
You know the saying: "The law is only for 10,000"?
All men fight to be included in that figure.
I know you like money.
Here is $78,000. Why?
Your video costs $780 million, divide that by 10,000.
The video.
How much does it cost?
I know the girl was engaged.
It is a scum of society, a vagina for customers.
Your life is worth 78 cents.
These cockroaches are running our society.
Compared to her, this is generosity.
Detective Jo, see you soon. It could be our obedient mole.
Detective.
You are here thanks to her. Do not forget.
Hello?
Who?
There is a civilian diver named Hong-Jin
who pulled Ji-Won out of the Sewol.
He had torn muscles and a broken spine.
The country stopped paying the bills.
But a few days ago...
HONG-JIN MO BREAKDOWN
...someone sent you $30,000 on my behalf.
To help pay for the hospital.
I didn't send anything.
Mine sure sent it.
He even saved my life once.
- Pil-Ho Jo! - Yes?
Don't make a scandal. Get treated.
Clear.
What a beautiful day, darling.
- Thank you. - That?
Use this.
I called for Ji-Won's dad to be here.
Thank you.
What the fuck?
What's happening? Do not you want to go?
There is nothing wrong.
You just go and tell them what you know from the video.
Buy me chicken.
The last time I ate it was with Ji-Won.
Fine, I deal.
Hi Ji Won. How have you been?
It's me, Mina.
Did you have your birthday party today?
I called you as soon as I woke up.
I'm crazy, right?
I even went to Bupyeong to buy you a dress.
It's not a joke, it's great.
But I don't know how to send it to you.
Your dad is fine.
Have a nice day with the others.
Give my regards to Hee-Jin and Mi-Ji.
Sung-woo and Jin-sung too.
And the teacher at home.
I missed you, that's why I went for a walk with your shoes and backpack.
I thought I smelled your scent, like you were following me.
I looked back, but you weren't there.
I cried like a wretch.
Ji-Won...
I really miss you.
If you don't recognize me, you're fried.
Mina loves Ji-Won, who loves Mina.
Shit.
PIL-HO JO I LIKE
I thought you didn't like pork bone soup. You are not like that.
Hee-Sook.
¡Hee-Sook Yang!
Yeah?
I love you.
Humbug.
Are you going far?
That...?
TAESUNG GROUP SCHOLARSHIP EVENT
Please come in.
Please come in. One by one.
He has orthodontics.
Can I go now?
Damn. Why is so complicated? Let's solve this at once.
Dude, stop touching my hairy ass!
I have a metal nail in my ass.
I got hurt catching gangsters. You do not believe me?
Upload it without making a mess.
I'm sorry. I didn't know about today's event.
Give me the phone and go.
I have to talk to the director.
On the illegal background.
I have key information from the headquarters.
I'll give it to him in person and talk to him.
We are on the same team.
Was this place always so majestic?
It will take two hours. Wait here.
Clear. Have fun.
What the fuck is that? It is expensive?
May I try it on?
They gave me such a beating that my whole body hurts.
Damn, how it hurts.
How is it turned on?
Why are you looking at me like that? It's not serious. I just want to try it.
"Astronaut experience"? What is this?
Do I become an astronaut?
Shit.
Where is the restroom?
They made me want to shit.
This massages your gut.
Nice to see you.
Welcome.
A pleasure.
What the fuck do you want?
Asshole, why didn't you call me earlier?
Did you run out of love?
Don't you want to catch me?
Hearing your voice makes me want to throw up.
Listen to what I tell you. It is important.
You know about the video Han sent me.
If it leaks, Korea goes to hell.
I'm about to make a deal with Taesung.
You understand?
Where are you?
At Taesung Headquarters, 15th floor. Hurry up, baby.
If you're late, I'm off to the Philippines with my money.
Huh?
Turn around! Right now!
We will start with a promotional video.
Please welcome director Yi-Hyang Jung to the stage.
Good afternoon.
I am the CEO of the Esperanza Foundation, Yi-Hyang Jung.
There is a camera on the wall.
Sorry, our job is to see everything.
To come see them,
I combed my hair, put on perfume,
and I drove a 5000cc car. Aren't they jealous?
You never had the video, right?
Fool.
Drown him and dump him after the event.
- People are watching. Careful. - Yes sir.
Leave me.
¡Suéltenme!
Shoot?
You want to try?
...lost everything he had. What did I do?
I took care of my siblings and studied hard...
I am here thanks to the generosity of my teachers.
AROMATIC MASSAGE OIL
Take this, asshole!
Motherfucker!
Damn bastard! Motherfucker!
Unfortunate! Come!
Come to me.
Shit!
Come.
And? Come to me, idiot!
Come to me!
Show me the best you got, motherfucker!
You can't catch me, can you?
Come on!
Motherfucker!
Let go! Son of...
What is the purpose of my anecdote?
What can I do for you?
I'm looking for someone.
Shoot.
...will start here.
You are the future and the hope of Korea.
Smile when you wake up and push forward.
Taesung will always be on her side.
Taesung will support you
with everything we have.
Therefore...
- Huh? -He went crazy?
Is it a parody?
Wrong room?
Get him off the stage.
- Mister. - It can't be there.
Exit the stage.
Pil-Ho Jo! What the fuck?
Pil-Ho Jo, stop!
Pil-Ho Jo, put the gun down.
Listen carefully.
No life is worth 78 cents in this world.
did you understand?
I won't hurt you. Alright.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have scared them.
I promised to buy you chicken.
But these sons of bitches...
Pil-Ho!
With the assassination of director Jung,
Taesung's case has taken an unexpected turn.
According to a witness statement, Director Jung ordered
the theft and destruction of evidence against him,
and Chief Prosecutor Sung-Sik Nam was involved in the organization.
Meanwhile, detective Pil-Ho Jo, who killed Director Jung,
acted out of simple revenge
and is expected to receive a severe punishment
for abusing his authority as a law enforcement officer.
I knew it would ruin her big. Look at her eyes.
I shouldn't have gotten involved with him.
Korean cops are all crooked. Damn cretin.
What's happening?
- Go away. - That?
I won't charge you, so walk away.
You are crazy? We not finished.
They talk too much without knowing the facts.
I'll cut out their tongues and make them mincemeat.
What are you staring at? You look like the head of an anchovy.
And you, a boiled pig.
You would look good in pork bone soup.
Shit.
Get the hell out of here.
Where are you? Class is over?
Come when you hear this.
I made your favorite dish, crab in soy sauce.
Bye bye.
Class is over?
Come when you hear this.
I made your favorite dish, crab in soy sauce.
Bye bye.
ANSAN CULTURE SQUARE
Hey, wait a minute.
Sit down!
Are you OK?
Let me! I have to talk to her!
Miss! Be fine! Have a nice life!
Subtitles: Rosana Galán