Ay, no. Ryo. Ryo. Ryo! Ryo! Ryo!
-Help me! -Keep looking. There is a lot of debris.
I'll leave the rest to you.
Yeah.
-Maybe there are still people under the rubble -Excuse me! I can't find my
-son! Where are the rescued people? -Is anyone trapped here?
Ryo… ¡ Ryo!
Brother! It's good that you're okay.
Hey, Yuko, are you okay?
-I'll bring blankets. -Yeah.
Brother. Hey, haven't you seen my son? Sorry!
What's going on?
Aid. Please…
This place is dangerous.
Someone is coming.
-Wait. -Hey. Are you okay?
Lucky.
I woke up, stranded alone on the beach...
No one responded to my voice and I couldn't feel any physical contact either. I felt
totally lost until you talked to me and...
Well, I know. I understand you. First, you have to calm down first. Breathe
war.
What happened… was shocking, right?
For now... Why don't you stay at our house? Hey, can you walk?
Yeah.
Ven.
And just like I told you, see? I came up with the idea of ​​this sand
star. Okay? You've probably seen these in souvenir shops.
I bought them for my family on my business trips.
I knew it. Yes. Well, that was my idea.
Here we go again.
I'm telling the truth, okay? She participated in student marches.
Then I ran out of money and had to flee to Iriomote Island.
And it occurred to you to sell sand in bottles. I've heard it a hundred times.
Hey. Do we have a new guest?
An earthquake. Do you feel it?
I think so.
Hello greetings! Hello Hello hello HELLO! Yes, it must have been difficult for you. I mean... It was
-a strong situation. -Michael, already…
What is this place?
Well... It's kind of hard to explain...
No problem. Calm down, friend. There's plenty of time to explain, yes? Kaori, give him the
-tour. -Yeah.
Hello! Kaori here. Good. Here.
It's just... Wait a minute. What…what is all this?
I won't tell him anything.
You see... It's a place... where people with issues in life meet. Well, no
only here. There are more places like this throughout the country and…
As? Which earrings?
Hey, Akira, you're not going to understand with so much detour.
Then you explain it to him, Shori.
Bluntly. You're already dead, you just… you still have unfinished business, so
you still can't go to the "other side."
I'm dead?
-I died? I died? -Well, well, well, well. Go to
rest a little, okay? We have good alcohol.
I dont need.
Maybe... come with me, okay? Peaceful.
It must... be because of a man.
I think so.
-Oh really? But she looks very old. -Sure, that must be it.
Hang on a minute.
Here.
The previous guest... has already left. You can use her room.
I know it's hard to process everything you just heard. You must try to
rest.
Are you also... in the same situation?
That's how it is. We are your tutors. We have experience. Have a good night.
Look, here's your baby. Congratulations.
Why don't you understand me, what the hell is wrong with you?
Well, I just…
That is what you want! I told you I don't need it!
Understand…
Pretty boy.
Ryo, come here.
-It was close. -Happy birthday to you…
-Congratulations! -Look.
Move on.
-Look what you did! -Mommy, look at this.
Ya basta.
-Hey, you have to go. -But I do not want!
Because? I have to go to work now. Hey.
I do not want to go to school!
Mommy, wake up!
-Mother! -Ryo!
-Hello. -Good morning!
-Good morning. -Likewise.
-Hello. Hello, hello everyone. -Good morning.
-Good morning. -Good morning.
Good morning. Kaori, can you get me some coffee?
-Clear. Here. -Thank you.
What are you doing?
Yoga.
Do the dead do yoga? Why are we concerned about health?
Do not be bothering me.
Yoga. Yoga. I was the one who brought him to Japan. Did you know that?
Do not start.
-Of course... -It's serious. That's how
-I hurt my back. You see? -Hello. Good morning.
Miss. Good morning. You look pretty in the morning. What is your name?
Soy Minako Kawakami.
Minako. Wow, wow. You're very beautiful.
Hey, Michael, in these times, saying that is inappropriate.
That? Oh really? Because?
The old man sitting here is Michael.
And the man who brought you to this place is Akira. And the young man who is on that side is
Shori.
He was a member of the Yakuza. That… is Mr. Tanaka, who was a banker. and I worked
in a bar Kaori here!
accompany us
Understand…
STOCK MARKET BURRS ECONOMIC BUBBLE
This is…
An old habit. Just that.
Hey, can I borrow your car key?
Clear.
That woman is kind of rude.
Hey! Is anyone trapped here!? Hello!?
¡Chinatsu!
¡ Kazuki!
Send!
HOSHISUNA STUDENTS
TEMPORARY CLOSURE
CONTACT US IF YOU HAVE INFORMATION ABOUT THE MISSING PEOPLE
¡Chinatsu!
Send!
¡ Kazuki!
You too.
I was separated from my family. I've been calling out your names daily to
find them. However, if they could hear my voice, it would mean that they are
dead.
I hope you can find yours.
Fortunately, the urban areas were less damaged, the highway acted
like breakwaters. We still have no news from Kawakami. Let's hope she's okay.
Rescue teams continue to search for the missing.
All we can do for now is work with the police and report the
news accurately. To work!
Yeah!
Mr. Kanda, I'm right in front of you.
-Come on. -I do not want to do it.
-Hello. You come back. -Welcome.
-Yeah. Hey thanks a lot. -You are welcome.
How nice you are here. We're about to eat nabe. Want
accompany us?
I'm sorry. I'm not in the mood for that.
That's precisely why you should join us. Yeah? Okay.
Is…
Now it's autumn...
on this empty beach.
Even if…
A singular dream appears...
He has sung it a thousand times.
Because I promised you the sand.
No matter how sad I feel...
I'm not going to die.
This is "Empty Beach." It is a good song. No, Shori?
Yes, not bad.
Good. Hey, Minako, do you want to sing?
No thank you very much.
You do not know? I teach you.
-Hey. Here you go. The nabe is ready! -Excellent!
-Come. Hey Hey. Come here. -Wow.
-Wow! -Wow! It looks delicious!
-To eat. Smells good. -Eat meat. To have power. Hey Hey.
Toma, Kaori. Ten.
-Eat, eat. -Thanks for the food.
Thank you so much!
-I feel it in my bones. -Excuse me…
Does everyone have… pending in the world of the living?
It's just that, well... everyone has pending things.
And that's why they spend all day lazing around?
-Well, you say "lazing around", but... What? -Well, I guess this
It seems to you to be lazy.
Well, I'm sorry to say this... But I can't waste my time like this.
Minako, wait.
Even one day... Why don't you hang out with us?
And why would I do it?
Because we... maybe we could help you.
Yes. That's just what I was going to say, right? Yeah.
Yes, surely.
It's time! Quick, finish eating! Fast!
-I want a little more. Please. -Hurry up.
Clear.
-Thank you. -Yeah.
It's delicious.
-Hello Hello hello. -Hello.
-We can't start without doing this, right? -Start it?
There is always a purification ritual before I make a
movie.
He is a self-proclaimed film producer.
Look at my movies. You will be impressed by some of those works
teachers.
They are all in the cinema over there. Yeah? Okay.
Okay, okay, let's go.
Good. Okay. Go Go.
Hey, what are you doing?
Once a month, on the full moon, we all get together and search...
That?
To the person that everyone wants to see.
It's very strange, right? I never imagined being with someone after death.
Shori, try to make sense of a contradiction, in itself it is a
-contradiction. -If there is little.
That?
-It's true. -Come on.
Hey! Hey! I found them! Look. Here.
Chinatsu.
Sky!
-Alive. -Dad.
Dad…
Kazuki.
I'm sorry.
It's strange, don't you think? We die, but we are still here.
It definitely means that we exist in this world.
Yes, we exist…
I'm sorry. I couldn't protect them.
My back hurts. Hey, Kaori, can I have a beer?
Okay.
-Here you have. -Thank you.
Do you think Minako wants one?
I'll give it to you.
Thank you.
Ten.
What did you think, Minako?
I... Well... I'm surprised. And very confused.
Who wouldn't be?
Minako, who are you looking for? To your boyfriend? Surely. I hope you find it.
Hey, that's enough.
Because?
To my son.
You see? I knew.
Turns out... I have a son, Ryo, who I raised alone. He is seven years old.
Knowing if he is alive or not... is my only concern.
Please allow me to be here a little longer.
Yes, it's cool. Of course. You will find it.
Good? Who talks like that?
Yes, like that. Güeno.
Good. Come here. Let's toast. Come come. Yeah? Come. Let's toast. Yeah?
Kaori, please.
-Good. Health. -Health.
-Health. -Health.
Health.
THE PARADES
Yes, it is open.
Happens.
-What, what is all this? -These are the notes that I have
taken for a long time.
But… you know, I'm going to combine them all like a professional writer.
Ahh…
What's going on?
It's just that I wanted to thank you for asking me to stay. Now I feel a little
-better. -You are welcome. I know what you're going through.
Are you also looking for someone?
No. I'm not looking for anyone. I just… I want to take note of everything I see here.
I want there to be a record that such a world exists when our lives end.
lives.
So, is that your unfinished business?
I'm not sure.
Do you need the car? You can use it whenever you want.
I appreciate it a lot.
I know you will find it. Peaceful. You could... take advantage of us and
ask us for more help.
Minako, listen... I would like... to interview you one day. Please tell me a little about
your life.
Sure, of course.
-Hello dear friend. -What's happening?
How cool. How cool. You look good in those clothes, don't you?
don't disturb
Know? A while ago I made a Yakuza movie.
It was surely one of those typical poorly done ones.
No not at all. It was a pretty good one! I'll show it to you someday.
Yes of course. See you later. See you.
JOBAN NUCLEAR REACTOR DAMAGED BY TSUNAMI
IF IT IS SLOWLY STABILIZING…
DECEASED
I have it.
They haven't found her yet. To Minako.
MINAKO KAWAKAMI MISSING
-Boss. Happy Birthday. -Thank you.
I will serve.
Thank you so much.
Yes sir.
Drink up, guys. Health.
-Thank you. -Thank you.
-Thank my Lord. -Thank you.
Happy birthday, dad.
Coman.
-Thank you. -Thank you.
I don't know how to act nobly,
But you don't need to do it to understand
That three people's problems are nothing in this crazy world.
One day you will understand.
C'mon C'mon.
Everything will be okay, baby.
Everything is in order.
Everything except one thing.
WHAT IS THE BEYOND?
-I'm back. -Ah hello!
Kaori, a beer.
Of course.
-Here I leave it for you. -Thank you.
What do you have, Shori? You look a little sad.
Oh really?
Today is your dad's birthday, right? How is he?
Well… It looks very good. But he is already getting old.
I imagine. It's been seven years since you came here, hasn't it, Shori?
Sometimes I wonder... how different it would be if I had stayed by his side.
Know? I made a Yakuza movie. But things have been very difficult for
they. They are a symbol of society. Since society was divided, people
He no longer has human rights. Listen, next time you go to the movies, I'll give it to you.
-I'll show you, okay? -Yes, whatever you say, whatever you say. Okay.
Yeah.
What is the matter you have pending, Shori?
I didn't expect you to ask that.
But I already told you which one is mine.
Well…
I ended up like this because of a Yakuza conflict seven years ago. I left my wife alone, and
Come here.
That? Were you married?
Well, not exactly. At least not something official.
-It's actually quite sensitive. -Hey, shut up!
And you've been looking for her for seven years?
Well… I'm not sure. Maybe I don't want to see it. Even if she sees her, I won't be able to hug her.
WHAT WILL HAPPEN IF THE PENDING ISSUES ARE NOT RESOLVED?
WHO HOSHISUNAZA
Good afternoon…
So tell me…
Is everyone safe?
Yes. You have to wait. Yes bye.
Now it's summer...
On this beach…
Sasaki, Tamashiro was arrested.
I see. The authorities act firmly. You are going to be next. So
Keep a low profile.
Understood.
Tamashiro was also detained. Let that be in tomorrow's flyer.
Yes. I'll have it ready later.
Well, Maiko, see you tomorrow.
Mr. Koga, are you okay?
Yeah, relax.
The other day, one of our members, Tamashiro, was unjustly arrested!
We must never give in to such oppression by the authorities!
-That's how it is! -That's how it is!
It is time for the students, workers, and people of Okeyinawa to stand up!
Stand up to abolish the security treaty and take back Okeyinawa!
The university can no longer allow their illegal occupation. Remove the barricade and
-Leave immediately. -That's how it is!
Raise your voice!
-Raise your voice! -Raise your voice!
¡Devuélvannos Okeyinawa!
-¡Devuélvannos Okeyinawa! -¡Devuélvannos Okeyinawa!
End the Vietnam War!
-End the Vietnam War! -End the Vietnam War!
Remove the American bases!
-Remove the American bases! -Remove the American bases!
Charge!
Joined!
Whom!
What time is it?
It's still midnight. You must lie down.
Does it still hurt a lot?
You scared me.
-Very sorry. It's me. -Minako, you scared me.
What is the name of the movie we were watching?
It's called "In Search of Lost Time." Great movie, isn't it?
Yes. Although it ended halfway.
Yes. It turns out that the movie was left halfway because I died.
-Ah, really? -It was going to be a big hit among
young people and it was going to have a big impact on all of them, seriously.
It would have been amazing.
And the poster was going to be Maiko, the protagonist, alone on the beach. And up
bam! Title. Without a doubt it was going to be a great success.
You even had the poster ready.
Yes of course. From start to finish, well, I already had everything planned. The theme, the
history and everything at all.
But why did you want to make a film about the student movement?
Oh, this one? Yes… This is a story about me.
¿Autobiographical?
Not exactly, but… I participated in a student protest. Which was, well, without
Regardless of whether it was correct or incorrect, the important thing was unity. The movie theater is
equal. Yes. All with the same objective, united. It's art.
You really loved movies, didn't you?
If it's an autobiography, does that mean Maiko was your girlfriend?
-What are you saying? Well, I guess so. -And what happened to your relationship afterwards?
Well. Many things happened. But I wish she could have seen the movie.
Maybe she's still waiting for her.
No. I'm not sure.
I'm here.
Welcome! Hey, dinner's ready.
Yeah!
Come on, Kenta. Your sister said dinner is ready.
Tare!
Hey, Kenta, put down your video game. Riko, give this to mom.
Oh yeah. Okay.
Kent! Dinner is ready.
Ten.
How much do they want?
The normal.
-And you, Kenta? -A lot.
A lot? So?
Thank you.
-Don't choke, Kenta. -That's lovely.
Hey. And how is the team doing?
-Second. -Good.
Is it going to be your match?
And? Will win?
It will be a piece of cake.
-The other day they lost by beating. -Hey, don't say that! In
-Serious! What's wrong with you, Riko? -I saw that game too.
Don't say that.
The baby kicked.
-Oh really? -Yeah.
That? Wait wait. Do it again.
-Wow! -He kicked! Hey, Kenta, come on.
Isn't it true?
-No, thanks. -Come closer and listen.
I know it's old, but it can still be used.
-Oh really? -Yes, look at it. Do not say no to me
shines. Hello, Minako! Good morning.
What are they doing?
Well... I was very moved by your words yesterday.
That? Which words?
Be careful with what you say. I have plans for today.
Seriously, I don't know what you're talking about.
Minako. You worked in television, right?
I was just a journalist. Yeah.
Just take this. Here. Listen. I decided… I'm going to finish the movie.
-That? -Good. Friends. Listen. On television,
shows come and go. Movies are eternal. I can not allow
let them do this without desire. Yeah?
-And what are we supposed to do? -OK. Akira, you see yourself
very slow, so hold this.
That? This is…?
-Kaori. Kaori, you the audio. Good? -Try it. That? It's a great job.
-Tanaka. Tanaka, you will be my assistant. -Yeah? Yeah.
And, well, Shori.
You, you, you, you, you are attractive. So you will be my son. Here is the script.
-Yeah? -Yeah?
-Good. -Are you going to be the director?
Director and protagonist. In the style of Yang Ik-joon.
So, so what, what style is that?
OK. Let's get started! Camera! Ready? Action!
Since then... About fifty years have passed since then.
Whats Next?
He says "I want, I want to see her again. I want to go back, I want to see her again."
That? That? I can't hear you.
I want to see her again.
Cut!
Wanna…
Ready? Action!
-What was that? -Well…
Clear…
Something got into the shot.
That? I want to see her again.
It's not about the lines! It's about the emotion.
-I understand. Let's do it again. -Yeah.
-I'm already in character! -Understood.
The door doesn't open properly.
I want to see her again.
I already know it.
Lots of shine!
How long should I wait?
Just try to get into character! Watch me and get ready!
-Let's do another take. -Yes that's fine.
When I first heard it, I wasn't sure...
What's happening? Why are you turning it?
No... it's nothing.
It seems that…
No, no, remember to start with "Since then." "Since then".
No no no no. Good good good. It's the first day. We have not yet learned to
teamwork.
Is that why it went wrong?
Of course that's why. Cinema is a team effort. Or not?
Why are you asking me?
Very good. Every department needs a meeting.
Minako. I'm going to teach you how to use the camera. Hey, come on. Because?
-No, thanks. -Is that another guest?
Yeah.
I will go to receive it.
It's very young.
How are you?
You see me?
What's going on here?
I am new too. Listen, why don't we go with them?
What is your name?
Nana.
-Hello! How, how are you? Nice to meet you. -That?
Nice to meet you.
I know. This is shocking. But I'm very sorry.
I don't regret anything. I'm happy my life ended.
Wow, we have an insidious girl in the house.
Oh, what do you care?
Okay. Miss, there is a place for you to rest. Come.
That girl is… you know what, Tanaka.
-Yes I know. -Yeah. Well I go.
Shori…
That?
Happy anniversary of your death.
Shut up.
Sorry, Shori. I decided to disband the group.
TOMB OF THE KATO
HAPPY SECOND ANNIVERSARY
THANK YOU FOR THE RIDES ON YOUR BEAUTIFUL MOTORCYCLE
TOGETHER FOREVER LET'S TRAVEL A LOT
I'm here!
Welcome!
You arrived early.
Yes. I sent you a message.
I didn't realize, sorry.
Curry lasts.
Thank you.
Mizuki. Next week I will have a day off. Would you accompany me to visit my
parents? I have not been able to present them officially.
Clear.
We also have to make decisions about our future.
I know.
So much has happened... But you haven't changed one bit.
He seems like a good guy.
Although I am much prettier than him.
I'm sorry.
Be happy.
Memories of you…
I don't…
-You came back late. -Hello. Kaori, serve me something strong.
Safe.
No matter how alone I feel...
I'm not going to die.
Shori, did something happen to you?
Ya la vi.
That?
She has already moved on with her life. She looked happy. It looks like she's getting married.
What good news.
Yes. Damn. You know what? Her new boyfriend is a wonderful man. It is completely
opposite to me.
It gives me pleasure. She will be alright. I'm sure.
Hey Shori! You haven't seen my movie yet.
You're right. I'll see her before I leave. The boring Yakuza movie.
Yeah! Well said. So, let's go! Come on, okay? Akira, come on, bring the car.
-Come on. They will be impressed. -Yeah come on. That is.
Safe?
Hey Girl.
Live well and enjoy your life.
That?
Do you have somewhere to go? Do you want to join?
-Boss, what are you talking about? -What am I talking about? It's good to have
a bigger family. What is your name?
Masashi… Yamada.
-How about? She's good, isn't she? -Okay. Alright.
Well, it's not bad.
Come back when you're settled.
Let's go.
Should we go now?
Yeah.
Hey, do you know yoga? I was the one who made it popular.
Oh really?
-It already started. -Thirty years ago, I worked
in an advertising agency.
At that time, there was a boom in everything sports. And I made yoga popular...
Nana. Good morning.
Good morning.
And... the one from the Yakuza?
He is already gone... to the afterlife.
To the beyond? I don't understand.
Tell me, Nana, do you have any unfinished business or anything you regret from when
were you alive?
That?
It's probably the reason you're here.
What are you saying? Is this some kind of cult?
A cult? How rude you are. By the way, do you want to record a movie?
-Minako, shall we go? -Because?
Yeah.
Nana, sit here.
DECEASED
Every day I get scared reading this.
If I find Ryo's name, what will happen to me?
I understand.
So, you wanted me to tell you about me, right?
Yes. Before you go to the great beyond, I would like to know a little more about you.
I am Minako Kawakami, thirty-five years old. She worked for the television station
Hokeyuto as a journalist, and was the mother of a seven-year-old boy.
And your husband?
We broke up after Ryo was born. I wanted to continue working, but he didn't.
He wanted me to work. Since then, we are alone.
Tell me more about… what this world was like for you.
Do you mean the world I lived in?
Yeah.
Well I do not know. She was obsessed with work and my son...
Now that I think about it, I don't know why I tried so hard.
If you could come back to life, what would you like to do?
Con Ryo…
I would like to go on a trip. I was never able to take it on a trip anywhere.
And I also want to apologize to him.
In this world, there are many unknown things that we cannot see as
atoms, electrons and elementary particles.
This is very boring. -For example, what we experience in daily life is
three-dimensional, or four-dimensional if we count time.
-Have you seen this video yet? -But scientist Lisa Randall has
I know.
Demonstrated that a fifth dimension exists.
This will go viral.
-Wow, she's a genius. This is incredible. -And some researchers claim that there are
up to eleven dimensions in theory, although this has not been demonstrated.
Are we going to publish it? If it is a good idea.
Hey. Yasuko. Don't go cutting your wrists like Nana, please.
What is clear to us is that the visible world is not the only thing that exists, are they
OK?
Are they paying attention?
-Yeah. -Yeah.
OK. So, let's analyze the word "dimension." It is defined as a
indicator for measuring a given space.
-How stupid she is. -Good. So what is a
dimension? A dimension is a line that…
Ten.
-Here is our dessert. -Thank you.
Hour.
Look, it's time.
It's already clear to me that I died, but can I kill someone? I want to get rid of
someone.
Hey, Nana, saying that is bad luck.
The people on this side cannot harm the people of the living world.
What the fuck. They're all dead!
Understand…
This doesn't taste like anything!
This is real hell! How long should I be here!?
Hey, Nana... why don't you join us for a moment? I want to show you something.
That?
You're going to have to trust. Just do it.
Well, that's it. Walking.
What is this?
All of us who die and leave our loved ones behind… we come to look for…
those people.
Our beloved ones…
I have no idea what your pending issue may be, but... we will help you in everything
that is possible.
Hey! Come here!
I'm sorry. Forgive me.
Wow! It just can't be! I got a message from you know who!
Oh really!?
Yes, look. Look, here it is. Look what she says.
There is someone... I must tell you that I am sorry.
This is your baby's face. Here are the eyes and the nose...
-Look, it's big. -How could I not accept my death?
Until my daughter gave birth, I desperately wished
-stay here to see it. -Wow.
This world is very forgiving, isn't it?
I think exactly the same.
Does it move.
-I have managed to be here with them so much... -How nice this is.
I no longer have earrings.
I have been watching my children for a long time, and they are very strong.
I think they would have been fine without me from the beginning. Sometimes I think that.
You know that's not true.
YOUR NAME DOES NOT APPEAR IN THE SHELTERS
THERE IS NO PROGRESS ON HOKUTO TV
Oh, it can't be! Look at Michael! Hey hey. What are you doing here asleep? Let's go to you
room. Come. Mr. Tanaka, help me. Here.
Yeah.
Hey, wake up. Very good. Okay, one, and two, and…
Michael, hey. Hey, hey, let's go. Above! Okay, okay, okay, walk, walk. Yes, it
Calm down, hey, hey, hey. You are very drunk. Let's go so you can rest.
-I have, I have. -Who is it?
Yes. I have it, I have it. Let's go. I have it. Carefully.
Still writing?
Yes. I'm enjoying it. But I don't think I'm anywhere near the end.
I already spoke, now it's your turn, Akira. Tell me.
That? No no. I don't have anything interesting to tell.
You always avoid talking when they ask you about yourself.
Do I really do that?
I just want to know what your life was like, Akira.
Minako, listen; I feel your journalist spirit.
That's how it is.
Well… I guess I don't mind telling you.
The reason why I haven't rested.
Is that… is your…?
Yeah.
My dad seems stubborn, right? For me, who has been physically weak since
little one… my dad was the scariest person ever.
Your food stinks.
-Look. He is lifting her up. -Wow! That!?
-But what are you going to do with that? -Are you going to eat it?
-Gross. -Oh no! Sorry. Sorry.
-She scares me. Strange. -Damn, she walked past me.
-Are you OK? -Are you OK?
Nana…
¡ Yasuko! Yasuko! Yasuko! Perdon!
Nana… Why? Nana…
-Nana, why? -Sorry. Sorry. I'm sorry.
No... Sorry, Yasuko, sorry.
-Nana. -Sorry.
Nana. Nana, no, Nana. Because you did? Until 18:46) Nana.
Oh, no.
I practically only lived in my bed. He was the son of the ranch owner, but he couldn't
work it.
I always thought that my dad didn't accept me as just another member of the family.
family.
When they told me I would die, I thought "why me?" Many times I took it out on myself
family. I'm sure I hurt them.
Probably… that's the reason why I can't go to the afterlife.
Although my father almost never reads novels, he has been writing his own for many years.
A story about your son.
If I were still alive, maybe he wouldn't be writing a novel.
Or maybe it would, I'll never know.
But that makes me very happy. I feel like for the first time I can meet him.
AKIRA WAS EXCITED ABOUT THE NEWBORN CALF
But… I know it's too late, because I'm no longer alive.
Look, it's time.
How much mess.
Sorry.
What are you writing?
I keep track of everything that's happened since I got here.
BEFORE GOING TO THE "BEYOND"
Something happens?
Know? I apologize. But… that didn't change anything. Because?
I am sure that one day your voice will be heard. Peaceful.
That's not an answer.
I lend you that.
-Bye bye! -Have a good night. See you tomorrow.
Bye bye! Have a good night!
Minako! Minako! Minako! Minako, listen! He is alive! Your son! I heard that
is alive!
Is alive!
We will wait here.
Ma'am, Ryo has a fever again.
It's been like this for a week. Tomorrow we will take him to the doctor again.
Yeah.
Mother. Mother…
Ryo, tomorrow we will go to the doctor.
I love my mom.
I know. I'm sure they will find it.
Mother…
Ryo… Forgive me. I left you alone.
Mother. Mom… Are you there?
Yes. Here I am.
I wanted to apologize to you. I was on my way to school to pick you up, but then
I was swept away by the tsunami. Forgive me.
Mom, when are we going home?
I wish I could.
Will I have to stay and live here, ma?
Forgive me. I will be taking care of you so that you are never alone,
okay?
Okay.
Mother…
Tell me a bedtime story.
Clear. What story do you want me to tell you?
Something fun you've done these days.
In the world that mom is in now, we all help each other to find the
people we love. Like a parade.
How nice.
Yes. They were the ones who helped me find you.
I understand.
So, now it's your turn to help others.
Yes you're right.
Hello, Mr. Tanaka.
Yeah?
I still have pending issues to resolve. It would help me?
If it's in my possibilities.
Akira, don't see me with that face of heartbreak.
What nonsense are you talking? I did not do it.
Well, Minako is very attractive. If I were younger, I would
-I would have invited… -How disgusting.
What thing? What's disgusting?
Gross.
Minako…
I'm back.
-Come here. -Minako, do you want coffee?
Thank you, Kaori.
Hey, Michael, I haven't thanked you yet. So thanks.
-Hey, stop it. You make me blush. -Your movie… You have to finish it.
That?
I'll stay until I finish it. You want to show it to someone, right?
Please stop now! You'll seriously make me cry.
He is ashamed.
Good! I'm going to do it. Yes. It's going to be the best movie in the world. Would you like to come inside,
-Nana? -What are you talking about?
Hey, Nana, this is mandatory, huh?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Tanaka.
Yeah?
Bring the camera!
-Your wish is my command. -Let's do it!
GOOD!
Filming.
-It's recording! -Yeah!
Take one. Ready? Action!
Fifty years have passed...
The movie is almost finished. Koga, the protagonist, believed in revolution and
He gave himself fully to the student protest. But for fear of being
arrested, decided to return to Tokeyio the same day of the protest... leaving behind
his girlfriend.
He just ran away… Pathetic fool.
Wait, Mr. Koga!
I'm sorry. I failed to make the revolution possible.
I don't need you to do that. Just stay next to me.
I'm sure we'll see each other again.
And then, Koga, gave up the student protest and fled to Tokeyio.
Our new product, star sand. It's going to be a success!
-Cheers! -Cheers!
-Maiko married Sasaki. -Congratulations!
I call it because of the star sand we talked about.
Kouga dedicated himself to working non-stop. Weird but cute?
We both buried our memories and moved on with our lives.
Mom, we're leaving. Bye, Mom. See you.
Bye, Mom!
Fifty years have passed since then...
Koga decided to return to the city of Okeyinawa.
Memories of that time come to mind as if it were yesterday.
Countries…
He's getting into character.
Are you Mr. Mitsuru Koga?
Koga had a meeting with Maiko's granddaughter.
That? I?
Mr. Koga, you know my grandmother, don't you?
Are you Maiko's granddaughter?
Please come see her. My grandmother has been waiting for him for a long time.
Cut!
-Incredible. -Incredible, are you a child prodigy?
Incredible. Perfect. Güeno. Güeno. Güeno. Güeno. Güeno.
-They flatter me. Enough! Enough. -Nana!
"Please come see her." Güeno, Güeno. Güeno.
-Hey! Making fun. -Michael! Don't make fun of her!
I see... You left this world before me.
It's very good. It's a great movie.
Mr. Koga!
See you later!
Enjoy your life! Enjoy it, sir!
Mr. Koga!
¡ Maiko! ¿ ¡ Maiko!?
¿¡Countries!?
Mr. Koga!
-¡ Maiko, hola! Maiko! -¡ No, Michael, no!
That?
-Wait! Michael! Michael! Michael! -Maiko, here!
¡Michael!
-Michael, wait! Come! -Don't run, Michael!
Countries!
-¡Wow!
-Let's go see it on the big screen! -Oh.
What's going on?
The thing is… I want to give this movie to someone.
But I'm embarrassed to do things like that. Friends, could you help me?
That? No, go and do it yourself.
Yes, I know, but...
Michael, listen. Let's go together. Ill go with you.
This is nice, like we're family.
Then I will go.
Oh really? Many people?
It's crazy.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
There's something I want to show you guys. Come, follow me.
-That? -It's this way. Look, look, look, look!
-That? -Wow!
Come, come, come, come, come, come? It's me. It's me.
-That? That's you? -You are an important producer.
I'm flattered…
-You weren't lying. -Wow!
Never, I only tell the truth.
-No, nobody believed you, right? -I'm wondering the same.
-Incredible! -Right? It's just that I'm handsome.
What nerves. I'm very bad at this.
You're going to be okay, Michael. We will wait for you here.
-Better another day with more calm. -Because? We already came here.
-But... -Now, you?
¿Sasaki?
Why do you come after so long?
By Maiko. I want to apologize. Please let me see her.
Happens.
Sasaki, did you… when did you die?
Two years ago, from cancer.
I see.
What's that?
Oh, this? I finished a movie. It's about Maiko, and also about me and you.
Even dead, do you make movies?
-You are obsessed. -You're right. It's the only thing I know how to do.
Here.
Maiko hasn't changed at all.
Maiko has always supported your work.
But, Maiko, she... chose you.
Know? I still think about the time we shared.
We could not achieve the revolution. But... what we did achieve was unite. I'm sure.
Countries…
Maiko, yo…
Sorry.
Very sorry.
-Hello! Hey, hey, hey, hey! -All went well?
Yes, everything went well. Perfect. Good. Good, good.
Wait, you didn't give him the movie?
Well, if you think about it, movies can't be watched at home. I know it
-I'll give it when it comes out on DVD. -But this movie will not come out on DVD.
Please, it's okay. Good. Let's go back home. Yeah?
Hey, friends. What if we project it? We can invite others not
alive.
Great idea! That's exactly what I was about to say.
Oh really? Yes Yes. Let's do it!
Let's do it.
-Go Go. -Yeah.
Perfect!
Michael, we're ready.
Good night all. I'm Michael. I forced my friends to help me finish
this movie.
This movie, actually. This film has the power to revolutionize the era,
and I also think it connects the past with the present.
Well... "Even dead, do you make movies?"
Someone told me that, but... as they say, the first person to do it wins.
I hope you enjoy the feature.
I have… a new idea.
-Other movie? -This is... my autobiography
from here. That's my new idea.
Michael, that... that's my idea.
So let's do it together. A collaborative masterpiece.
-I do not allow it. -I understand.
Minako, are you okay?
Yes. It's just that I process everything that happened.
Me too. I think I also feel a bit scattered.
-Mr. Tanaka… -Yes?
Tell me what the world is like in the afterlife.
That's classified.
That?
Mr. Tanaka is like our warden.
What is the reason for knowing it until now? That scares me!
-Please! Why don't you tell us? -You will find out very soon.
Tanaka is too serious.
But you know? It was fun to film it.
TRUE? The movies are good.
A lot of people with the same goal.
It's great.
Yeah.
¿No?
Nana. You have to make more movies. Use the notes from my room.
Nana, you can do it!
That? Why only me?
Akira, it's going to be your responsibility now.
Make sure you keep track of this world.
You can count on me.
But you have to stay on the offensive. Don't lose!
Am I going to compete against someone?
-Now, let's toast! Let's toast. Yes. Cheers. -Chin.
Let's toast.
-Let's toast. -Let's toast.
-We still have food, you have to eat. -To eat.
Alright.
A comer.
Can you pass me some kinpira?
-This? -Yeah.
Mr. Tanaka, do you want karaage?
-Just one, please. Yes, thanks. -You are welcome.
-Thank you. Do you want some fries? -Yes please.
-That's OK? -Yeah. thank you so much. You want to? Thank you.
-Minako, do you want fries? -Please.
THE SOUND OF THE WAVES,
AND AN EMPTY BEACH.
knock knock
Is everyone asleep?
Yes. In the end, Michael fell asleep while talking.
He is always full of energy. Yeah.
-Take. -Thank you so much.
Akira, are you going to continue writing?
Yes. I think I'll do it until my dad finishes his novel.
I see. Be sure to write about me.
Of course. I even plan to make you the main character.
Oh no. Please no. A small role.
I wish I could…stay with you longer.
Where did that come from?
It's just... I have feelings for you.
Where did that confession come from?
-Is rare? -Yes it's weird.
If we had met in life, would things have been different?
That cannot be known.
It's true.
Akira… Thank you. I had a good time.
Me too. Thank you.
Okay, let's go.
Okay, I'm ready.
-Okay, let's do it. -Forward. Very good. wait,
-Wait, this is the door. -Hey, let us pass.
In the middle, okay.
Okay, understood.
Wow, so many people.
-Oh really? Yes please. -Soon.
-I count on you. -I'll do it soon.
Oh, so this should be… Excuse me. Ryo.
It's been a while.
Yes, quite a bit. We still have time. Do you want to go for tea?
-Yes of course. -How big you are.
Thank you very much for coming. Is this your first time at Tokeyio?
Oh yeah. There are too many people.
-Yes, compared to our home, yes. -Yeah. You're right.
Hey, are you graduating next year already?
Yes, exactly.
And have you… decided what to do?
Well… still… I'm not so sure about that.
Maybe I'll try my mother's work, I think.
-Please, someday tell me about her. -Yeah. Of course.
Either way, I'm excited.
I hope you like it.
Nana! How long.
-Yes, a lot! -Hello!
What a pleasure to see you. Hello.
-Greets. -Good afternoon.
Güeno.
-Your tickets, please. Thank you. -It's room two.
-Your tickets, please. Thank you. -See you later.
Enjoy it. How are you?
-I'm anxious. -Yeah.
Okay, it's five hundred yen. Thank you.
Hello, can you please show me your tickets? OK thank you.
Wow awesome.
-Do you want me to carry you? -No. So I'm fine.
-Hey. It's already going to start. Get comfortable. -Settle down.
A NANA DATE FILM
En memory of "Michael".