cj entertainment presents
a JK film production.
"No trespassing".
"Order of the Supreme Commander".
Captain, nothing to report.
Get some rest, sir.
I'll sleep when the situation is resolved.
What the...?
How did you find me?
Aren't we doing this for food, anyway?
Does anyone know you're here?
Don't worry, I reported to the captain.
I hope it is well seasoned
Know...?
That?
There are shots! There are shots! All units report!
Wait here
AYUR Di
Yoo hai-Jin
Directed by Kim sung-hoon.
Captain, we have a lead.
Do you want me to wait until they rob us?
We will enter, come with me.
Hwa-ryung, bring up the rear, the rest with me.
Comrade Lim...
Let's wait for reinforcement.
And watch the sunrise?
Do not move.
Clean it up.
stay!
Stay still, he said.
I'll count to three.
If they don't drop their weapons,
They will take one bullet per head.
One.
Two.
I told you to wait.
Do you ever listen?
It's not worth spilling blood between comrades.
Put down your gun and come here,
We need a face to face.
Think about it.
I am right?
Shut up!
Yeah?
If you force me, his head will fly off.
Wait!
Put the gun down.
The rest of you too.
will you come down
Cover up!
AWEeRrnUnE).. -...
Cheol-ryung, are you alright?
This may sound weird, but I never liked them.
The censors are lap dogs, loyal to the Republic.
Rabid lapdogs.
Lucky son of a bitch.
Cneohrune)
My mercy...
It's the only reason you live
and not by the leader you serve.
I have a job for you, go tell the Republic.
I will take the plates as payment for the blood of the people.
See you.
"North Korean National Security".
Created at the 215 factory, 'the super ticket',
can perfectly replicate all security measures,
and evade any counterfeit detection
with the newest technology available around the world.
The engraved plates used to print them
and within 1 micrometer...
Go to the point.
The plates were stolen.
After the 2010 counterfeiting scandal,
Sanctioned production is like a declaration of war!
Who is the suspect?
Cha gi-sung, 44 years old, born in Hoeryong,
He was demoted for stealing drugs from the Republic.
His wife was punished for covering up, and died in prison.
It is presumed that he reunited his old squad again...
The Minister of Security has detected your route outside the Republic,
and reached Chungdo on the 12th.
He passed through Beijing and arrived in Dalian...
We're in communication, but China was just a stop,
and took a plane from Dalian today.
fate is...
seoul.
Confidential Assignment
High!
Bastard!
Where will you go now?
Look what I had to do to catch you.
Okay, okay, don't come.
Let's talk about this!
Don't come close, I'll cut you down.
Never!
Daddy, answer the phone! Don't pretend to be busy!
Can I take care of my daughter?
Daddy, answer!
¡Papi!
Yes darling.
¿Íphone?
Let's be honest...
did you accept a bribe?
What bribe? I never would!
So why let it go?
I couldn't do anything in the first place.
I know, I watched too.
Stop compromising.
What are you saying?
You can't leave our conversation like this!
Oh really?
He came at me with a knife, I'm not Robocop!
Boss Pyo!
In it. Kang!
Idiot, I told you to call the boss first!
I thought the arrest came before.
Stupid fool...
About what?
It was my mistake.
Forget it, idiot.
A newbie can't start with a mistake like that.
Go away, everything is done.
It's part of being a cop.
All right, go inside.
So the 12th District brigade leader, Cap. Cha Gi Sung.
He fled the country
but Major Lim Cheol-Ryung was in their ranks.
Why did he leave you alive?
What's your plan with Cha?
We are confused
If you dont do it,
I'll go after Cha to the gates of hell.
Dejennos.
A north-south ministerial talk will take place next week.
It is an unprecedented event that we put in place.
I'm going to include you in the delegation.
Go and capture Cha.
I didn't take the bribe!
Yeon-ah, my Princess, come here!
All right, close the curtains.
Üphonel
When will you buy it? You promised me!
I will buy it today!
Brother in law! It's an emergency!
Jesus, 31,000 is...
Shhh! Be quiet.
Brother, we are better than this.
Talk to your sister!
Send it to my account, okay?
What's going on here?
Did you see his face? You must be overworked.
Hey, idiot, aren't you going to work?
I'll answer then, hello?
- He doesn't res... - Give it to me!
I knew you would attend
Come have breakfast!
Hello?
Good morning.
¡ Jin-tae!
Lots of trash!
- Why are you here? - Let me help.
Are you rested?
15 years of collaboration don't mean shit.
Did you come to tell me that?
Joint investigation?
Have you heard about the ministry talk next week?
Your delegation will include a detective.
An agent of the censorship bureau.
Anyway, there was a criminal who defected to the south,
What crime did he commit?
I don't know.
It's an order from the commissioner.
Do you want me babysitting a communist?
- Don't call them that. - Forget it!
I worked for a just society, but I'm just a dirty cop.
And now you want me to do what?
How much more must I sacrifice for my country?
You're hopeless. You really don't have it.
You don't get it, do you?
I'm trying to do you a favor.
Forget it, I won't beg.
And you can't trust these details to a novice.
Lots of trash...
Today at 12:50 p.m.
Brother, pass me the controller.
There there.
Inter-Korean ministerial talks to proceed...
After a long period of inactivity,
the talk started by the North is getting a lot of attention.
With this case, you will be reinstated,
Dear
Thanks for everything, things will get better.
Take it yourself, it's in the fridge.
take what? I am thanking you.
Out of the way!
I said it's in the fridge.
Not good... we're not good at all.
Have you been investigated?
The case closed very well.
He's an undercover specialist.
That is why it is perfect for this job.
In any case, very good.
Your task is to stay with the Korean detective 24/7,
and report anything unusual.
Of course.
This is a covert and joint operation.
They must know that Intelligence is involved.
Not only in the South, but in the North as well.
Do you understand?
Find Cha and secure the plates.
Did you learn to use this hand phone?
The south controls the people with this.
You only have 3 days.
First look for Park Myung-Ho.
It was one of Cha's men, he's a smuggler in the south.
Leave your personal Vendetta out of this.
Do not forget.
What a stallion...
Aren't you the one with the Linm?
I'm Kang Jin-tae from Homicide.
The North's weapon is confiscated
This is rule 1 of our joint work.
They are the rules, and you must obey them.
Come on.
Eat something.
Our taxes feed you to catch the criminal.
The south will assign you a snake.
He can't know anything about the plates.
I've been at this 20 years.
I feel the weight on my shoulders.
No...
Sit down, sit down.
Your job is to expect full cooperation.
and drive away your detective.
What brought you here?
I have read the dossier on the case.
An ordinary assassin wouldn't start a north-south meeting.
Shouldn't they celebrate the arrest of a murderer?
But do not have sense.
Oh yeah?
That flag.
If you let it...
Rule #2, this is an undercover case.
very uncomfortable...
Look around.
The south is full of CCTVs.
So since...
True, the north is always watched the same.
I guess we are all the same.
It's too early for these pamphlets.
Hey.
Have you ever seen one of these?
Call them.
Use this cell phone.
My number is in favorites.
Oh really?
You can use this.
Well, what's your number?
Needless.
Bastard...
Take it when you come home.
Anywhere you want to go? Seoul Tower or Itaewon?
This may be your last time in Seoul.
Are you really a special investigator?
Have you heard that? Yes why do you ask?
You sound more like a tour guide.
Do you think I don't know how to investigate?
My bosses are tracking Cha,
Would you like to go shopping? Well why not.
Weren't you better off as a soldier?
Why police?
Find another route, one without traffic.
I wish I could, but there isn't.
For a country without oil, why are there so many cars?
Are the cops in the South all like that?
Yielding to all the traffic, they play with the cell phone
In Seoul there is no way to get out of the traffic.
That stare of yours...
I better give in.
Only ambulances can do that.
What were you saying?
We are partners, inform me.
Daemyung Condominium, #1108.
Sha's associate lives there.
Park Myung-ho.
It's all I wanted to know.
Hostage situation in Mapo district.
A man in his 40s holds a woman hostage with a knife.
What world do we live in?
D-1 is close, we'll go see.
What are you doing?
You heard the radio, there is a hostage.
Have you forgotten your orders?
The safety of a citizen is the first priority of a police officer.
If we don't go, she could be hurt.
Enough of that garbage.
Damn...
You better let me go.
We're not that close for this level of intimacy.
Well, let's talk about it again.
Come on!
Curse!
What do you take me for?
You are making a big mistake.
Return that!
It's okay, okay, okay.
Truce, ceasefire.
Take them away from me and we talk like democratic people.
CD as communists?
Cheol-ryung, hey, listen to me.
¡Cheol-ryungg
Hey! Hey!
¡Lim enedEnNuUnc)!
That's one crazy son of a bitch!
Even if he's Special Forces, this isn't the place.
Det. Lee, I need to track down a taxi!
19 m6918.
Sixty-nine, damn eighteen.
Daemyung Condominium.
Hey!
you arrived in one piece
Detective, let's have a chat.
Why are you so like that?
We need to talk about...
stop Lee, Seoul 31SA 2914!
call when you have it
Made in the north?
Como Bingdu.
Asshole, either from China or North Korea
It's not that fake shit you get here.
This is authentic, genuine from North Korea.
Look here.
You've lived long with fake shit.
The dirty, ragged deserter is getting bigger.
You're just a junkie hunter.
Give it to him.
Fool.
Oh yeah.
Let me know if you are in the market for these.
I don't just deal drugs.
Park myung-ho.
Where is Cha Gi-Sung?
My arm!
Who are you?
Don't you think I use it?
I'll blow your head off.
¡Lim enedEnNuUnc)!
- Where? - Ltaewon!
It's dangerous, go inside!
' ¡HaWOUngl
' ¡Papi! '
Come here!
¡Ha-young!
' Are you OK? - Daddy!
Look at this...
¡Lim enedEnNuUnc)!
Wait!
Curse!
I have a clue
Dalian a257 on 18th street under the alias 'Hwang Wui-Wan.'
Look for the nearest door.
Investigate the owner of the car.
Yes sir-.
Park is here, sir.
Park Myung-ho reporting.
You do not get tired? Leave that greeting.
Is a free country.
The ship and weapons will be ready tomorrow.
Good.
But we have a problem.
He must come from the homeland, he is looking for you.
It's probably from unit #5014.
There are two of them.
Have you gone mad?! You've gone mad?!
Why don't you yell at everyone that you're undercover?
I could have died!
When I found Lim, he looked like he was in an action movie.
He fled, he was long gone.
Did you let it get away? Didn't you question him?
Did you want me to?
I can not believe it...
We have Cha Gi-sung's file.
Stay with Lim 24/7, don't let him cause trouble.
That's a little too much...
This could be the exile of a VIP.
And kill him while they work together?
We would be screwed.
Did you give him the phone?
You want to use yours.
That?
You know we'll track it down! Do you want me to force it?
Curse...
Where is Lim?
The. Glue?
I'm the detective Lee Dong-hoon.
I'm the detective's partner. Kang.
In other words, we are on the same team.
Nice to meet you.
Our countries may be divided, but we share the same blood.
As a joint team, we can figure this out very well...
- Nothing to report. - Don't tell me, how strange.
God.
Let's go out.
Come.
Park is missing, and there's no lead on Cha.
Will you go knocking door to door?
Here
You lost the suspect and terrorized the streets.
Your legs, please.
I'll jump, move your legs.
open them up a bit...
Legs together...
Wait...
my goodness...
When will this day end?
Detective, this is hard for me too.
Can't we trust each other?
We can triangulate it fast.
Don't underestimate the power of our reach.
if you do that,
I will follow the investigation rules of South Korea.
I will do that.
Take them off.
And what do you go on your own?
I want to trust our joint mission.
I got a lot of shit from above because of you.
Let's drop the formalities.
I usually share a drink and we become friends.
Good.
Very good,
To celebrate our new friendship, here.
Show me your leg.
Very good
This device is...
It's a discreet sign that you're a detective here.
Not a gps tracker?
It has that little function.
As I explain?
Let's say you arrive at a crime scene.
You cannot know who is who.
"Are you a detective?"
"Yes I am. And you?".
Are you a detective too? Great job here."
That's what it stands for, okay?
Is loading. I take it every day.
I accept happily, thank you.
- Take a drink. - I'm fine.
Just one drink.
Since we're on this mission, it's the end of the bad guys.
If I catch Cha, what will you do for me?
Let me think, anything?
I can send the girl to a private school, marry off my sister-in-law,
and give the rest to my wife
That's cheap for enslaving a redneck cop for 3 days.
Do you know what my salary is?
You will be surprised to hear it.
Taxes paid, about 838,000.
Divide that by 12,
and gives about 83,000.
Curse! Almost minimum wage!
Honey, we have a guest
He doesn't have a room yet.
So he brought fried chicken.
This is my wife!
And my princess.
How was your day?
Say hello to Mr. Lim.
- Hello. - What is this?
Silly. And resume!
Come in, come in!
This is how we live.
Who says?!
He has a sharp tongue, but he is kind.
I wouldn't have invited you, if it weren't so.
He is so handsome...
Is it in there?
Yes, why?
That? what?!
It won't stay in the main room!
You can sleep here, it's Yeon-Ah's room.
I hope it's not too uncomfortable.
This is my room.
Have a good night.
Once we locate Cha,
I hope you like it, I made it for you.
Please try it.
Do you have any preference?
I have never seen you cook in these three years.
It's a guest, sister.
I hope it is to your liking.
North Korea?
He deserted because it is difficult to live there.
He's a North Korean policeman, be nice to him.
Good girl.
Hey? .5 c S for him?
It would be nice if you gave me a little too.
Please start.
There's no need to spin around
Who starves these days.
Go read some newspapers.
There are plenty.
That?
She's not one to starve, look at her flawless skin.
Stop looking at him, eat your breakfast.
- Please eat. - We have to go.
His grave.
My wife is a great cook.
Boss, we have the owner of the car.
Put our men on '(with and Aang.
Report when they contact Cha.
How about the free life?
I sleep and eat well like a free man.
If you have money, freedom can be easily bought.
Left and right do not really exist.
Come on, that doesn't prove shit.
I have to see them plates printing the money.
We are not negotiating a negligible sum.
Let's see what those boards can do.
We have to make sure it's authentic.
What do you take me for?
Detection of counterfeit money is quite advanced.
We need specialists and equipment too.
I only need 2 days.
Whether we verify it or not is up to you.
But if the deal closes, that's on me.
You have balls.
Motherfucker.
Mr Yoon.
I have betrayed my country
to my family, and to my youth for those plaques.
Do you want my organs too?
You worked so hard, you deserve to get paid.
Anyway, I'm the only one who has the resources.
Correct.
Then I will wait.
We'll meet here tomorrow with the plates.
Very wise.
If you want to fuck me, I'll kill you.
Rewind please.
High!
To the basement.
What is there?
- Tax free? - Yeah.
We can't break in without evidence.
Park carries a different bag.
That?
In the South, suspects are innocent until proven guilty.
So it's up to me to do things right.
Good day.
We are here for Park Myung-ho, he was here yesterday around 3 pm
The one with the big head and dirty hair.
We saw it on the security cameras, so don't pretend...
Why are you here?
Buddy!
Swordsman, you know me, come here.
Come back, idiot!
Boss, this is bad!
What is happening here?
And who are you?
Are you the boss here?
I would like to ask for your cooperation.
Do you know Park Myung-ho?
Did you bring an order?
It is being sent by mail, but we can talk.
Did you skip the process and come without one?
You have shit for common sense.
Are we seriously going to start off on the wrong foot?
Do I deserve this kind of treatment?
This is real?
Give it to me, idiot!
Where is Park?
Those are bad manners.
Obstruction of justice is an applicable law.
We will take the appropriate measures.
Boss!
A detective
You must treat it accordingly.
Bastards...
IS it toilet paper?
At home, toilet paper is not a weapon.
No one will see it as such here either.
How did you do it...
They came to me, it was in self defense.
Park's number is here, trace his location.
Boss.
Can you get me off this mission?
Lim knocked out a group of thugs
That?
The triad?
The DS Fund is a corporate gang,
and Cha was in contact with them after arriving here.
- Oh really? - Yeah.
Did you plant the chip in Lim's cell phone?
I did it.
How could I know?
Jin-tae.
let's figure this out first
Okay, listen, I've got Park's location.
Yeongdeungpo District, 66 dosin St.
Due to the low unemployment rate, the youngest depend on...
Sister, what is Jin-tae's salary?
After taxes and insurance, just over 830,000.
Career men with 3,100,000 salary line up behind me,
It's a step backwards to marry a policeman with 330,000
A significant discount, right?
He proposed to you?
If I want it will.
And?
You are just a profiteer.
Where did you get that dress from before?
I lost count because of you!
So why does he have to be so handsome? I can not decide.
Why do you get carried away by the look?
I was also surprised, fatal, right?
Totally fatal.
Their reckless fight was...
Sister, sister!
Isn't that CheoHyung?
Even engaging in a fist fight...
My God! It just can't be!
The cartridge does not fit correctly.
Please wait here.
No way, how could I trust...
Curse...
It's not that I don't trust you
Welcome.
Hello.
It is this?
What is this place?
Damn enlarged...
- Let's move. - Lieutenant.
Can't I live here in the south forever?
I made all the preparations, got the weapons and the ship.
I don't need my payment
so please tell the captain for me.
Hey!
Who are you?
That?
Are you the boss here? Who are you?
Look at these guys...
Hey cheol-ryung!
¡Cheol-ryungg
Damn...
Wait wait!
Do you have a death wish?!
How did that?
Shit!
Come here!
I can't risk a betrayal
Please...
I took care of Park.
2Y Lin?
Talking about the devil.
Comrade, answer
¿¿Cneowsyung ?
You should have let it go, when I forgave you.
I left you alive because we went through a lot together.
But you come to catch me?
Shut up and wait.
You're with one foot on the grave
It's not my fault, rest in peace.
¡Cheol-ryungg
Who was that bastard?
Secure first and second floor!
How he died?
Evidence and warrants are useless now.
Did they shoot you?
Like hell, they almost killed me.
Shit, they cut me off.
Move over, please.
What is all this?
Where is Kang Jin-tae?
In it. Kang!
What's that? That...
- Boss! " 'Come here!
Come here, fool!
This is a sting operation.
Listen.
I will report this situation to the boss myself.
This is Park's cell phone.
Extracts all locations from the last 4 days.
It's okay, undercover...
Come on.
In it. Kang!
- Blood! - It's okay, I'll be fine.
How will I tell my wife about this?
Are you OK?
Of course not, it hurts like a bitch.
How could you do that to me?
They were coming for me, and you left without telling me.
I'm disappointed, you fucking disloyal.
Anyway, that big guy who killed Park,
Curse...
If I ask you something, answer me for once!
Forget it! Whatever you want!
Damn this joint mission.
You probably know that Cha was a soldier.
How many men do you have?
Don't know.
His squad consisted of a dozen men,
And if his mercenaries got involved...
Lim Cheol Ryung.
What the hell is going on here in the south?
Why would an officer from the north come here with his men?
I tell you everything, but you don't.
Who is Cha and why is he here?
Long ago, he killed a squad of censors.
AND?
They were like my family.
The men in the photo...
We were supposed to wait
but because of me...
Because of your fault?
As if terrorizing the streets wasn't enough, murder?
We didn't do it. it wasn't us
Well, if it wasn't you, then who?
Cha is not alone, he has soldiers.
Yeah.
What is Cha's ultimate goal?
How could I not know? Do more intelligence.
I'm not a fucking vampire!
What is your area of ​​specialization?
Violence...
I see, masochism.
The girls are mine.
Do you want to know how to free yourself from the anklet?
Aid! Please!
He must be a cop too.
Damn...
You said you weren't hiding anything from me.
You did not want to accept my cell phone,
What if you get into trouble in a foreign country?
Listen.
I can't seem to cut it.
Alright, I'll try again.
Anything can be cut.
Here we go! Let's see!
I have it!
I could barely cut this thing.
I have to return it, idiot!
Oh my gosh, that was close.
Where are you going?!
Who kicked your ass?
Stop! That is enough. It's just a bruise.
Idiot!
Oh really...
You pinched me very hard.
give me face
Come here!
If you get stabbed again, we're done.
So I'm not going around getting stabbed.
Hey.
Why did they hit you?
Mister.
You are a policeman like dad, right?
must fight very well
Does he shoot bad people with guns like him?
That's how it is
take it off
That?
I mean, roll up your sleeve.
There's no need.
It looks bad...
How can you say that with those hands?
Your salary is low, but I hate to see you hurt.
If you were to get married, would you live in the South?
I'm sure you don't have much, but I'll skip that.
I have a girl.
Why do not you tell me before?
My God...
How embarrassing!
I'm sorry.
You love her?
Of course I love her.
Come on...
They were like my family.
We were supposed to wait, but because of me...
Think it's so cool...
«Park Myung-ho».
Good job
I will reward you all for your contribution.
Once we complete this mission, we will achieve freedom forever.
Fight to the death.
We have something
It's coming from Park's body.
After 3 days of ministerial talk, the northern delegation is returning...
You scared me.
Have you been able to sleep?
Do you only have one suit?
Come here!
Park's phone was recovered, let's do it.
So make it quick!
Damn...
What about food out of season?
This doesn't seem normal.
It's the North Korean style.
North Korea? For him?
- Come on, eat. - I hope you like it.
I looked up the recipe online and made it myself.
- Oh really? - You like me?
It's great.
Aunt, mom did that.
Hey!
Want something?
It's uncomfortable, sit in your seat.
' Bam? ' Yes ​​baby?
- I'll buy it. - When?
"Boss Pyo: Your cell phone is bugged."
Alright?
Have you not finished.
Finish your food.
It's okay, please.
Wait wait!
Wait!
Can I be informal with you?
You already are.
Oh yeah?
I don't know what you do to come back with so many bruises
And I know you won't tell me
Please take care of my husband.
He's stubborn, so my scolding doesn't work.
Take the hard work for yourself.
You're still single, so maybe you don't understand...
There must be someone, I'm sure.
Anyway, take care of it.
He may be a jerk, but he's all I've got.
I understand
It is called 'super ticket', the plates can print counterfeit money,
Did you track down Cha's location?
Not yet
- Park's phone... - Tell me, I know you know.
Are you going to hit me?
- Tell me. - Don't know!
Even if I did know, I wouldn't tell you, asshole.
No wonder, my grandfather always said,
You couldn't be trusted, even back then.
The third generation under the dictatorship really screwed things up more.
They are starving people to death.
The rich get richer, the poor get poorer.
Do you know what the debt of the South is?
That's a lot of bullshit.
Is it fair for your leader to burn the cash instead of helping?
Don't insult the Republic!
But I did, so what, are you going to hit me?
It's alright, alright.
Let's be honest.
But you told me you wanted to avenge your comrades
How can you lie with something like that?
I believed your lies
And I almost helped you carry it away, damn it.
I have never lied.
Forget it.
- Please help. - How can I trust you?
If you help me catch him, I'll give you the plates.
I promise you.
I know it's a lot
please help.
I beg you, comrade.
We should wait, support is on the way.
What are you looking for?
The two of us can't take on an entire squad.
That?
They are ex-special forces who fought in wars.
They are not like your untrained colleagues.
If you want to live, stay here.
It's not exactly 3100000.
What is this?
Yankee things are not good for boys,
but at least they can live with some class.
What do you mean by that?
Thanks for everything.
So the plates are verified, let's get to the deal. So the plates are authentic, let's talk about the deal.
I was thinking
the technology is mine, and so is the printing and distribution.
For that reason, the plates are overpriced.
Let's meet halfway, $5 million.
Do you have coke? It could take a bit.
Partners cannot be separated by more than 10 meters.
The joint mission did not end.
Down there?
You have a plan?
010-2335-6972, that's my number.
Winett Will you do?
It took you quite a while.
Reply.
It feels good.
I missed this every time I came home from abroad.
My people must taste the sweetness of capitalism.
$10 million isn't even close.
Let it be $20 million.
That?
No? So s30 million.
Time runs while you hesitate.
$40 million.
This is highway robbery!
I told you not to fuck with me.
I didn't come here to make a deal.
I'll transfer the $10 million we originally agreed to.
There's no need.
I'm going to print my own money.
Take the plates.
What are you going to do? Hey! Hey!
So you came.
It's good to see you alive.
Should we break things every time we meet?
Time's up, come on
Get covered!
What the hell was that?
Are you OK?
So that's Cha's asshole?
That is.
See you at the pier.
He missed the heart
So=no!
That. Kang.
It's okay, you will live.
Officer down, Sector C, parking lot!
Send an ambulance!
Part of being a cop.
I won't die, please go after him
Go and catch Cha.
Apply pressure there.
So=no!
Route 2330, Songdo spur, runaway car found.
This is D-1, we're on our way, out.
You, bastard.
Go back to the station at once.
Why exactly?
Why the joint mission can be exposed?
The mission is over!
You told me to do intelligence.
I'm with the agents.
Stop where you are and turn around.
Because I should? You saw it too!
He shot a cop in broad daylight!
Who cares if it's south or north?
Alright. Good.
We are in a state of emergency.
We have to arrest Cha and secure the plates at any cost.
You must prevent Lim from killing him.
If necessary, take out Lim.
Curse!
You promised, the plates are mine.
I mean, from my country.
Let me do my duty, become a respected policeman.
Tomals.
One more thing.
When we get Cha, will you kill him?
I understand your situation,
but revenge is not part of our job.
He must be arrested and punished.
Nothing else, understand?
Don't answer carelessly.
I said I understand.
That's what being a policeman means.
There, it's him!
Slow down.
Hold the wheel.
Come closer.
Hey Cheol-ryung!
Stop Please.
Because you did?
Chem-only.
I didn't want to be the lapdog
of rotten heads of state in the name of our people.
Do not tarnish the honor of our people.
You betrayed his trust to be here for your revenge.
Damn shit!
Do it.
Do not do it!
What are you doing?!
You can't, you will die!
Let me go!
Are you going to shoot me?
You promised, asshole.
He killed my wife.
This was among his belongings.
I thought you needed to know.
Shit
Before the cavalry arrives,
Take this.
He fell into the river along with Cha.
It's the only way for you to live.
Your wife in heaven will want that too.
Cha jumped to his death.
Go Go.
Go right now!
Good job.
It is a pride for the Republic.
We haven't recovered Cha's body.
If you give me some time...
That was the President's order.
Forget Cha.
This marks the end of the joint mission.
Lend me your phone.
Daddy, answer the phone!
Don't pretend to be busy!
Daddy is on his way home.
- Whose girl are you? - Daddy...
Check it out.
there is something i lost
I don't have it, it's already with...
You have 2 hours.
Bring the plates to the power station on the pier.
Then I promise your family will live.
If you get police support, I'll break that promise.
I will tear your family to pieces.
Please let my daughter go
¡Cheol-ryungg
Cha gi sung...
He has my wife and Yeon-ah.
He wants the plates at 9 o'clock at the power station on the pier.
Or they will kill both.
CheoHyung, please help me.
Please don't let them kill Yeon-ah, please.
Dejennos.
Comrade
Cha is still alive.
Let me take care of that.
I told you the mission is over!
Are you still bent on your revenge?
Separate the order from your personal revenge!
He took my South Korean partner's family hostage.
Leave them.
I don't want to lose anyone else.
I don't want to lose you either.
I'm sorry.
I'll be back later.
Mother"
Yes baby?
Yes, they are gone.
But keep your eyes closed.
Let's wait for daddy a little while longer.
It's good.
The goal is here.
¿Yeon-ah?
Yeon-ah!
Dear!
Honey, this way!
- Dad! - We are here!
- Dear! - Daddy!
Love...
Where are the plates?
Let the girls go first.
Then I'll give them to you.
Do you want to die together?
hand them over
You don't have them.
No! I don't have them, you bastard!
I do not have them!
Stop hiding and get out of there!
No, I am not sorry. Oh really.
Sorry comrade.
Captain Cha, it's all my fault.
My family doesn't deserve this.
I'm sorry, let them go. Kill me instead!
You are listening?
Yeon-ah, dad is here.
We will go home soon.
Shoot.
Comrade, are you okay?
¿¿CneoHryung ?
I'm sorry, I was late.
Thank you.
Move and you're dead.
Motherfucker...
Let the southerners go, I'll give you the plates.
Cneohrung).
You betrayed your country to save those people?
But...
How can I trust you?
Crane, upper deck.
Captain.
Some pieces are missing.
Cneohrune)
There are only two small parts.
Like I said, let them go first.
Not bad for a lap dog.
Alright, alright.
Let them go.
Take your family and go home, comrade.
Yes, it's alright, Cheol-ryung.
and what happens...
with...
configo?
Brother.
I'm sorry.
I got you into this mess.
I need you to move.
Okay, thank you, thank you very much.
Go for him!
Cheol-ryung, there's no need to shed blood
If you go back to the North, you will have a firing squad.
Join us.
There is a ship waiting for us.
Captain!
Alright, I'm going.
Why aren't we moving?
Dear.
You know I love them more than anything, right?
But...
I am a detective. A South Korean policeman.
AND?
Cheol-ryung is alone...
the mMueve mor vl
Kill them all and bring Cheol-ryung back.
Do you really want that?
You won't go alone, right? Will you contact the boss?
Yes of course.
Look over there.
¡Cheol-ryungg
Take this.
Are you OK?
Great.
I'm sorry, I was late.
Cause you're not at home?
And why are you here? It's the same deal.
You cried and begged for help.
Yeah, I cried like a bitch, didn't I?
There is no one like me, anyway.
Just be thankful.
char. she's running away out there!
I'm actually a good shot.
Where was he? It's very fast.
I should have killed you first!
Hey, jerk!
Do you know what those plaques are?
They are revenge against the Republic for abandoning its people,
and it's a reward
by my blood and sweat!
Can't you ruin such a noble plan?
Cneohrung).
Come on...
For!
CheoHrnunc), mirame.
Let me see
Curse!
Sons of bitches.
take it with you
Are you that desperate to go to prison?
My country should be ashamed of this.
Be a respected cop for yours.
It's not like we get paid that well for our services.
And it's not like they're going to reward us.
Why did you become a policeman?
I didn't know it would be like this.
I thought I would look good while shooting guns,
How about you?
They're all starving so no criminals I guess.
Wait, it's a detective's paradise.
Take me with you, I want to defect to the north.
Better beware.
That mouth could put you in prison.
Anyway, that's how I started.
Catch the bad guys, save the good guys. You?
Me too, at first.
Man Man. Everything hurts.
It took their time.
That boss bastard.
"1 Year Later, Pyongyang".
¿Pyongyang?
Yeah.
Pyongyang's first serial killer.
The suspect is a South Korean, who defected to the North.
Anyway, it's a covert operation.
They already chose your counterpart.
Oh yeah?
You're still as ugly as ever.
- Good to see you. - I am glad too.
Rule #1 of our joint mission,
the southern weapon is confiscated until the case is resolved.
OK, it's OK.
Here we go.
My sister-in-law went crazy when I told her I was coming...