[crumbling]
[munching]
[Hwang] All right.
You know, Tae-gu,
I had a feeling Yang would send you.
Just know, I'm only sparing their lives
so that you can save face.
If it wasn't for you,
I would have had them buried
in cement by now.
Understand?
[henchman 1 chuckles]
All right, that'd be hilarious.
Welcome, Sir.
-[henchman 2] Hello, sir.
-[henchman 3] Welcome.
-[henchman 4] Where are Yang's boys at?
-[henchman 2] Over here, sir.
[Tae-gu] So, what now?
[Hwang munching]
Is that a message you want me
to relay to the boss?
Whatever.
Tell him what you like.
[man grunting]
[man groaning]
[moaning]
[man grunts]
[coughs]
[Tae-gu] Should we discuss…
[Hwang munching]
…since it's obvious you stabbed
my boys in the back,
maybe you'd like to let us know why.
Why would you pull something like this
all of a sudden?
[sighs]
Why bother asking
when you already know the answer?
You've been in this business long enough.
Listen, Tae-gu,
have you ever heard the story,
The Chariot and the Mantis?
[Hwang] The Chariot and the Mantis.
Come on,
why are you bringing up old proverbs?
It's not really your style.
In this story, there's a great wheel…
[groans]
…rolling along.
A tiny mantis stood in the way…
[grunts]
…determined to stop it.
[scoffs]
Shoot, man.
The mantis had balls, sure enough.
[Hwang]
However, we know how the story ends.
You can learn from this tale, huh?
What do you think you're going to achieve?
Do you think standing against
the Bukseong gang
is gonna end well for you?
I get that Yang wants to expand
his operation, but I don't understand
what you have to gain
from getting involved in all this mess.
From what I heard,
Bukseong Chairman Doh
attempted to recruit you,
but for some reason you refused.
[Hwang scoffs]
What's wrong with you?
Are you tired of breathing?
You better watch yourself.
Chairman Doh only spared you
because he thinks
he can get you and your crew on his side.
If it were me, you'd be a dead man.
Think about it.
Without you, your boss, Yang…
[chuckles]
…he's no more than a cripple.
I'll relay that message to him as well.
Sure, say whatever you like, huh?
I'll go then.
[arcade game music playing]
[man over PA] We have a winner on 19.
They'll be moving onto the third stage.
-[woman over PA] Please be advised…
-[grunts]
[sighs]
It's raining.
[Jae-kyung] What took you so long?
Have a look at the time.
Yeah, what took so long? We were waiting.
Shouldn't you be able to read a clock?
Ah, Ji-eun, I'm sorry.
Uncle got tied up with some business.
-Look at you, mm…
-You too.
Are you hungry now, sister?
There's a place nearby that serves
my favorite raw fish soup.
[sighs] I'm not sick enough for you?
I can't even stand the smell.
Come on, they have abalone porridge
as well. It'll nurse you back to health.
Is that right?
You look like you could use some yourself.
Huh? Why do you look so tired?
[Tae-gu] I'm not tired at all.
-You don't even work hard.
-[grunts]
Don't gangsters just lounge around?
Why are you the only haggard criminal?
[Ji-eun exclaims]
-Ji-eun, your mom could read my resume…
-Okay, just ignore me.
-…over the loudspeaker.
-Don't act embarrassed. You have no shame.
And don't give me that business
about you quitting again.
Though you should.
Once I'm gone, you'll be
the only family Ji-eun has.
Who'll look after her if you get stabbed?
Hey, she can hear everything
you're saying.
Don't you think she knows these things?
Kids know everything.
Jeez.
You don't need to know
everything, Ji-eun. Right?
Jae-kyung.
Go ahead.
I'll get your medications
and drop them off later.
[grunts]
Ji-eun, I'm gonna come visit you later,
so now, you're gonna ride home
with your mom, all right?
Okay, Uncle, but promise
you're gonna be able to make it.
Try not to get stabbed
because I think that would be really bad.
[sighs]
All right, Ji-eun,
I'll be there. I promise.
-Yeah. All right.
-See you later.
And guess what day it is coming up soon.
My birthday!
[whispers] I have a secret. I bought you
a gift and you should open it early.
-For me?
-[Jae-kyung exclaims]
-Right there!
-[Jae-kyung] Oh Ji-eun, you're so lucky.
-What could it be? Something expensive?
-[Tae-gu] Open it. Go ahead.
-Thank your uncle first.
-[Tae-gu] Ji-eun, do you like it?
-Will you move so I can get in? A bit.
-Hold on, just a sec.
And what is it? Ta-da!
Move. Jeez. When did you get so strong?
I'm making some dishes for you.
Better come pick them up.
Uncle got me an iPad!
Do you like it? Now you can watch
all your favorites shows.
-That's enough, she likes it.
-Do you love it?
Just go. What's got into you?
You're being so sappy lately.
[Jin-sung] Hey, drive careful in the rain.
-[knocking]
-[Jae-kyung] Ji-eun…
-Ji-eun!
-…look at this clown.
[Tae-gu] I hope you like it.
Ji-eun! I'll see you later. [chuckles]
[surprised grunt]
Bye!
[Tae-gu] Oh, Ji-eun!
[laughing]
[clears throat]
I'll get a car, sir.
Actually, you can head back on your own.
I still have business here.
I should escort you, sir.
It's fine, you can go, my friend.
I just need to pick up
Jae-kyung's medications.
Okay, go on.
[Jin-sung]
Okay, I'll see you later then, sir.
[doctor] We ran every test
and I have the results. I'm sorry, but…
you are not a compatible donor
for your sister.
You two are not a close enough match.
Though this is rare
between a brother and a sister.
Uh, well, uh, my sister and I…
have different fathers.
Oh, I see.
So, doc…
how much time
does my sister have left?
[delicate music plays]
[sighs]
[exhales sharply]
[phone vibrates]
Oh, hey, sis.
[exhales, clicks tongue]
It's fine. Forget about the fish soup.
Just a suggestion.
I'm just fine.
There's nothing for you to worry about.
Hello? Sister?
Jae-kyung?
Still there?
Jae-kyung, are you there?
[dramatic music]
[sirens wailing]
Uh, the boss is here, sir.
Did you get any sleep?
Have you had anything to eat?
Yeah.
Today would've been…
Ji-eun's birthday, right?
[Do-soo sighs] How could that bastard,
Chairman Doh have done this?
He must be going senile in his old age.
No matter how things are
between us and them,
this is a line you don't cross.
And after he fawned all over you
to get you to join his side…
[sighs]
[clicks tongue]
What can we do about this situation?
[Do-soo] They'll all continue to overstep
because they know
they have us by the throat.
I'm ashamed to say…
but there's nothing I can do.
Then I'll meet with Chairman Doh.
[suspenseful music plays]
What would you do?
I would do whatever you ask of me, sir.
Isn't this what
you've been wanting anyway?
It's inevitable.
[Chairman Doh breathing deeply]
[exhales]
I'm grieved by the loss
of your sister and niece.
[clicks tongue]
Of course, I was shocked to hear the news.
It's not enough to say
that we're in a rough profession.
Only a real lowlife
would think of going after family.
[scoffs]
Some asshole has no idea
the mistake he made.
[sighs]
[clicks tongue]
I'll find out who did this.
You have my word.
And serve them up to you.
You hear me?
What's done has been done.
Doing that won't change anything.
Hearing you didn't give the order,
I'll see it as an accident.
[chuckles] Good.
That's it.
[sucks teeth]
You know, I admire your attitude.
It may sound cool but life goes on.
So what is it that you want?
What can I do?
I'm assuming you must have
something in mind,
or you wouldn't have asked
for this meeting.
Let me splash some cold water
on myself first.
Sure, yeah.
[Chairman Doh] Hey.
There's no reason for you
to be on edge, huh?
What's going to happen
when we're just sitting here naked?
Must you embarrass me?
I apologize.
Try to relax.
Flip the hourglass.
[tense music playing]
[grunts]
Come here.
[groans]
[henchman 5] What the hell? You…
-[slashing]
-[groans, grunts]
Tae-gu, wait. Just hold on.
[Chairman Doh] Hold on, Tae-gu.
[grunts]
-[slashing]
-[groaning]
[water splashing]
[breathes heavily]
[contemplative music playing]
[engine starts]
[revs]
[contemplative music rising]
Here.
[chair creaks]
[Do-soo] Very good work.
Any injuries?
I'm fine, sir.
[Do-soo] You discarded your phone, right?
You can use this one for now.
I got you new identification
and some cash.
[zipping]
First step…
Jeju Island.
[Do-soo] You hide out there a week.
From there, we'll put you on a boat
to Vladivostok, Russia.
Safer in Russia than China.
You know how close the Bukseong Gang is
with the Chinese.
I don't care where you send me.
Tae-gu.
Yes, sir?
Just know that you saved us all.
Let's go.
The boat comes in a week.
Enjoy the scenery and the fresh air.
You should just think of it
as a short holiday.
Yeah.
[woman speaking indistinctly over PA]
[clicks tongue] All right.
Is Kuto ready for him in Jeju?
Yes, sir. All taken care of.
And our guys?
Check on them.
[tires screeching]
[men shouting]
[clamoring]
[tense music playing]
[clamoring continues]
[screaming]
[grunting]
[groans]
[plane engine humming]
[rain pattering]
[cell phone vibrating]
[Jae-yeon] Is this Mr. Park Tae-gu?
Yeah, who is this?
Over here.
I think I'm the person picking you up.
Bingo.
My uncle got busy and couldn't come
so here I am.
Come this way.
[Jae-yeon] Seriously?
Not coming?
Yeah, coming.
[wind blowing]
[Jae-yeon sighs] God damn.
[whirring]
[sighs] It's windy out today.
[clears throat]
[clearing throat]
[clicking]
[Kuto] Real version Tokarev,
not the Chinese knockoffs.
Here you go. I'll throw in a box of ammo.
I have more for sale.
Wow! Great fucking deal.
I'm certainly not gonna argue the price,
but are you concerned
about selling so low?
Make the Bukseong gang
or the Russians get upset with you.
You buying or not?
Sure I am.
The Japanese will pay me double for 'em.
[boss] Kuto.
I hope you can appreciate how hard it was
to pay you on American cash.
During this recession,
it's nearly impossible.
Here you go. Take 'em apart and wrap 'em.
Hey, do you have a better way
to send them than, uh…
-in the fish?
-How?
You want me to put them in the mail,
sent to your house?
Yeah, all right,
and I'm just saying these things smell.
Cut the shit and pack 'em.
Fishing boats are the safest.
Give me a cigarette.
Kuto,
why are you selling
so aggressively lately, huh?
You usually work through the Russians,
now you put together your own deals.
So…
you planning your retirement or what?
If you're done with your shopping,
it's closing time.
[crickets chirping]
Do less examining and more eating.
Yes, sir.
I'm just curious.
I heard about you moving here.
They told me you started a farm.
How long will you stay?
About a week is what I was told.
But I'm not sure.
[Kuto] Where are you headed?
Vladivostok.
[Jae-yeon] You mean, Russia?
What an honor.
You must be a national hero.
[sighs] You done with this plate?
Actually…
[Jae-yeon] So, a week it is then,
unless you'd like to leave earlier.
We really don't wanna get mixed up
with you people, over just a few bucks.
[dishes clatter]
[water running]
[birds chirping]
[atmospheric music playing]
[phone line ringing]
[operator] The person you are calling
cannot be reached at this moment.
[tense music plays]
How did it go?
Director Ma…
[clicks tongue] He escaped, sir.
[sighs]
You pieces of shit!
Don't you know none of this works
if Director Ma's alive?
[yells] How?
Sorry, sir.
[sighs]
[foreboding music]
Sorry, that's not all.
Bukseong's Chairman Doh…
I'm told he's still alive.
He's in surgery right now.
[exhales]
[scoffs]
[sighs]
[exhales]
Director Ma, sir.
It's Do-soo.
[Sang-gil] Hey Yang, how are you?
I bet you're thinking,
"Man, I really fucked up this time," hm?
[sucks teeth]
Though I have to admit
I was pretty surprised, you know.
That a useless prick like you would…
[whispers indistinctly]
Listen to me, Yang.
You little weasel.
I don't know what you were thinking.
Maybe, your balls just dropped.
It doesn't really matter.
You know what happens now.
I'm gonna cut you open,
and watch your guts spill out
just to see what's inside.
Hm?
Just wait.
It won't be long.
Take me to those bastards right now.
[tires screech]
[tense music playing]
[gasping]
Give it to me.
[groans]
You know, it doesn't seem right
that you have to pay the price.
That Yang's men have to pay
for his mistakes.
Bite down hard.
This is gonna hurt.
[screaming]
[exhales]
-[clears throat]
-[gunshot]
[gunshots continue]
[sighs]
[clicks]
[tense music playing]
Huh?
Hey, hold on!
Hey!
Hey, hey!
Hey, stop it!
[Tae-gu] Hey, wait, what are you doing?
Just wait.
Hey! Hey!
Why are you doing that?
Please don't.
Put the gun down. Hey!
Stop it!
All right. All right. All right.
Calm down. Just stay calm, all right?
[Tae-gu] Hold it. Don't do it.
Just…
Hold on.
Hey!
That's right. All right. Hey!
Stop it, don't do it.
-Don't do it! Stop it!
-[clicks]
[Tae-gu] Psycho woman.
[train horn blowing in distance]
[railroad rumbling]
[exclaims]
[groans]
[retches, spits]
Oh, shit. I just ate lunch, dammit.
Get it out.
[Captain Park sighs] Shit.
[exhales]
-Mr. Yang…
-Yes?
Help me.
What are you playing at here, huh?
Are you children playing pretend?
Sorry, sir.
[sighs]
I'm sorry, Captain.
Sir, please, sorry, just…
Help me get out of this.
You must think I'm some kind
of miracle worker.
I mean, why did you have
to create this mess in the first place?
[sighs]
This isn't 1980s for fuck's sake.
A coup like that in these days
and in broad daylight.
[clicks tongue]
Hey, Director Ma, it's me.
It's been a while.
About time we met for some face to face.
Let's sit down for lunch.
Pick some place nice.
[chuckles] Always.
[Captain Park]
And you'll still argue who pays the tab.
[clanking]
[door opens, closes]
[crickets chirping]
[sighs]
[birds chirping]
[sighs sharply]
[car horn beeps]
What the hell?
Hey! Hey, lady!
What's wrong?
-[moans]
-Huh?
[gasps] Damn!
Move!
-What are you doing?
-I need you to drive.
-What?
-Get behind the wheel and drive!
[Tae-gu] All right.
[panting]
To the hospital!
-[engine starts]
-[Kuto] Jae-yeon! Jae-yeon!
[sighs deeply]
Do you expect me to share that with you?
I haven't drunk from it, sir.
[sighs]
Has Yang contacted you yet?
When is he coming for you?
He is sending a boat early next week.
[exhales] That's good.
I need the rest of the money he promised.
[clicks tongue, sucks teeth]
We gotta leave here soon ourselves.
Where are you going?
United States.
Jae-yeon will have an operation there.
She only has a ten percent chance
of living here.
Goes up to 20 percent over there.
[sighs]
In her current condition…
she will be lucky to last a month.
[sighs]
[rain pattering]
Did you have a shower this morning?
No, I didn't, sir.
Why?
Do I look that bad?
This filthy bastard.
[slurping]
[Sang-gil] Come on, Captain Park,
let's have it,
or did you come all the way for this, huh?
Cheap old noodles. We can do better, huh?
I told you I'd pay the tab.
Why not let me treat you
to something better?
Well, a government employee
can't be seen accepting
something that could be
construed as a bribe.
[Captain Park] Can you pass the vinegar?
[Sang-gil] Sure.
[gobbles loudly]
[burps]
Why aren't you eating?
[Sang-gil] Ah, leave him be, huh.
It's really better this way.
Less mess when I cut him open.
How considerate.
Less shit for my boys to clean up.
[Captain Park chuckles]
Must you speak so ghastly.
All right then,
since he has lost his appetite,
we'll talk sharp instead, okay.
So I heard, Chairman Doh survived.
What if he did?
He's been left a cripple. Shit.
Fortunately, he was religious, huh.
Donated a lot of money to church,
attended all their services.
[chuckles]
I guess the heavens spared him.
Fucking Hallelujah, right?
The heavens, my ass.
The doctor that saved him.
[chuckles]
So considering,
Chairman Doh survived the ambush,
and as I hear, a couple of Mr. Yang's men
already paid…
[clicks tongue]
…the ultimate price.
[Captain Park] Don't you think Bukseong's
had enough retribution?
We should consider… [exhales]
…calling it even.
Ahh, let's see.
No, absolutely not, huh.
Your math simply doesn't square.
It's not that easy. This isn't a score
that can be settled so cheaply.
[Do-soo] Let's be honest.
You people were the ones
who started all this.
Oh? You sure?
Sorry, for a second there,
I almost thought it mattered
what the fuck you had to say.
[clatters]
-You shit.
-[Captain Park] Ah, Director Ma.
What's with you?
Allow me to do my job.
Let's resolve this peacefully.
If you keep killing each other,
I'm gonna lose my job.
[chuckles]
I even got an earful about it
before coming here today.
They say I'm too lenient
on worthless thugs.
My fucking evaluations are coming up.
[scoffs] So I say…
enough is enough, all right?
[clears throat]
Look, Captain Park.
Respectfully, this isn't even something
you can really intervene in, huh.
[Sang-gil] They attempted
to assassinate my boss.
The chairman of the great Bukseong gang
was shanked by some lowlife punk
that he himself ordered.
And so, how could we possible just let
something like this slide, huh?
This is such a fucking
goddamn embarrassment.
I can't even hold my head up
when I walk down the street.
Fuck.
[sighs] Goddammit.
[Sang-gil grunts, clears throat]
You stupid fucking piece of shit.
Yeah, Ma Sang-gil.
Come on.
[Captain Park] What do you think
you're gonna do about it?
-Captain Park…
-Shut your mouth, you worthless cunt.
I'm speaking here!
Yeah.
You think…
because we're sitting here,
eating noodles together,
that we're buddies or something, huh?
You think I'm a joke, huh?
Yeah?
Let me remind you that there are lines
that cannot be crossed.
[Captain Park]
I told you my evaluations are coming up.
And if I miss this promotion,
will you take the blame, huh?
You think that just because
I'm being nice to you,
that I'm gonna let you walk
all over me, huh?
It's as if you're challenging me.
[chuckles]
Huh? That it?
Maybe, I should do my job, eh,
and put your asses in jail!
Of course not, sir, I apologize.
What about you, Sang-gil?
[exhales]
Are you finished, Captain Park, huh?
You fuckers.
You have anything more to add?
[sighs] I don't know.
I just hate seeing you
get all worked up like this, huh.
And aren't you always the one…
constantly preaching to us
about mutual respect?
Shit. You need to be smart about this.
You know that Yang has people
higher up than me on his payroll.
If you were to cause him physical harm,
it would be trouble for both of us.
[Captain Park] So that's off the table.
Director Ma, I'll beg you if you'd ask.
[Captain Park]
It's not like we're strangers here.
I know we can find a way
to get along, huh?
[tense music playing]
[clears throat]
All right, huh?
What's the deal then?
[exhales]
-[Jae-yeon coughs]
-You're awake.
What are you doing here?
[Tae-gu] Kuto had to meet
some customers at the farm.
Hey, what are you doing?
Hang on. Wait, I wouldn't…
Oh, jeez.
-[sighs]
-You can look, kid. I won't charge you.
[sighs] As if someone would pay for that.
You have something to ask me?
What?
No, not really. Nope.
[clears throat]
Why do you look at me like that?
Do I look different to you now?
[Jae-yeon]
Now that you know I'm a dead girl?
What?
Wanna grab lunch?
Aren't you hungry?
Well, are you?
No, not really hungry.
[clears throat]
[Jae-yeon]
I hope you're not afraid of raw fish.
This place makes the best mulhoe soup.
Folks from the mainland don't know
about this place yet. It's nice and quiet.
I've made peace with dying.
But I'll definitely miss the mulhoe
from this place.
-[Jae-yeon] Thank you, ma'am.
-[waitress] Mm-hm.
-Please enjoy.
-[Jae-yeon] Yeah.
This is the best.
[moans]
[munching]
I guess this isn't your kind of food?
Too spicy for you?
[Jae-yeon] Or is it the smell?
No worries, kid.
That's your prerogative.
[moaning]
I'll make this better.
Excuse me, one bottle of Hallasan.
Hm?
God, everything is a struggle with you.
Unbelievable.
[sighs]
[grunts]
You're good with a pistol.
That was nothing.
It was easy.
All I do is imagine
the one I want to kill.
[Jae-yeon] Also…
I feel safer carrying it.
Sure you don't want to drink it?
It's a crime to visit Jeju
and not try this.
Come on, just a sip.
It's good, right?
Isn't it?
Cheers then. Drink up.
No, thanks. I shouldn't,
I'm the one who has to drive us back.
Ah, nonsense.
You can handle one shot, kid.
Hm?
Besides, the cops don't check
for DUIs here.
I've lived here my whole life
and I've never once seen a DUI checkpoint.
[Jae-yeon] That's not a thing here.
So no worries. Drink up.
[groans]
[dialing]
Dispatch, Kim Hyeong-jin.
Kim Hyeong-jin. November 11th, 1987.
-Listed as local resident…
-Let's do this again.
You're going to blow
like you're inflating a balloon.
It's 5626.
Blow.
Blow, blow, blow…
You're good.
[officer 1] And him?
Yeah, he's fine, sir.
That's good. Just a sip like he says.
Thanks for your cooperation.
[officer 1] All right, drive safe.
Yeah.
Hang on, please stop, sir.
[officer 2] Oh… oh, off the road.
Please try to stand up.
Will you… your girlfriend.
She had way too much to drink.
[officer 3] Get her under control.
-Stop this.
-Please help!
[whining] I promise to be good.
[officer 3] Wow, look at her.
She must've drank her own body weight.
[moans, groans]
[officer 3] Help her back on to her feet.
-[indistinct chatter]
-[moans]
Hey, hey, hey.
Oh, oh, oh, no, no!
-No, no, no…
-[Jae-yeon screams]
[phone vibrating]
[Do-soo]
I'll be there to meet you tomorrow.
So be ready to leave.
I don't need to remind you,
no trace of you
should be left behind, all right?
I understand.
You know, sir. I haven't been able
to get a hold of Jin-sung or my guys.
[Do-soo sighs] Yeah, that.
Uh, shit.
You probably guessed by now,
but the operation failed.
The Bukseong gang demolished us.
Jin-sung and the boys
are already in hiding,
and I'm making plans
to go to Vladivostok with you.
I'll fill you in on everything tomorrow.
Get ready to meet me.
Yeah, all right, sir.
[sighs sharply]
[ominous music]
[Captain Park]
Imagine this as Park Tae-gu.
Park Tae-gu is the one
who butchered Chairman Doh.
As an apology, you hand over Park Tae-gu.
Just like this.
Over to Bukseong…
and Bukseong deals with Park Tae-gu
how they like.
And we will all agree with Park Tae-gu
who is acting entirely on his own,
who did this.
We end it there.
Are we good?
-[sighs]
-[Captain Park] Okay, now…
Once that filthy assassin
who had the unmitigated gall
to flash a knife
in front of your Chairman Doh
is dealt with by Director Ma…
[Captain Park] Tae-gu is handed back
and the cleanup will be done
by Yang and his men.
Good? And I expect him
to disappear without a trace.
If anything of him is ever found,
Mr. Yang will assume all of the blame.
Okay?
Understood.
All right, Director Ma,
are you happy with the terms?
Well, I don't find it fully satisfying…
but I'll agree to it.
[Captain Park] All right then…
There better not be any loose ends.
Understand what I mean?
We're in agreement?
-Yes.
-[Captain Park] Okay.
[Jae-yeon] I'm wondering about…
what you did that was so bad
that they sent you here.
Right? You must've done
something pretty bad in Seoul.
Didn't you?
Hey, cut it out.
Vladivostok, Russia.
To be sent there,
you must've fucked up pretty bad.
Do you wanna spill the beans?
Come on, stop.
Ah…
So I'm not the only one to receive
a death sentence.
You're dead too.
[brakes screech]
[sighs]
I said stop.
I asked you to cut it out.
Is that something you can respect?
I knew it.
Death sentence.
It all adds up.
You fucked things up,
and you ran off to save your ass.
Okay, say that again.
-[thud]
-[exhales]
Come on, hit me.
It's all right with me.
I can take it, kid.
[sighs]
Take your best shot.
I don't understand
why you're doing this to me.
What did I do to you?
Whatever. Go ahead and drive, kid.
Uncle will be waiting. [exhales]
[sighs]
[engine revs]
[tires screech]
I don't know why you keep calling me kid.
I'm older than you.
Show some respect.
You're the one who started it.
So, how old are you?
Oh, so now you're an old geezer.
What's with people demanding respect
because they're older?
All you've done is have
a few more meals to me.
Anyway, you may have been born before me,
but I'm likely to die before you.
That should even things out.
If you don't like it, die first.
[sighs]
[clicking]
[boss] You don't need to bother counting.
It's all there.
If you're done shopping, head out.
I have someplace to be.
[boss] I'm curious, though.
Is this all the merchandise you have?
I already told you that it was.
[boss] But, is that the truth?
Watch how you speak.
[boss chuckles]
Hey, don't be so serious,
you're frightening me.
Anyway, whether you have more or not,
I'll just find out in my search.
[groans]
[gangster] Where you goin', old man?
Get back over here.
[grunts]
[groans in pain]
I'm impressed.
Kuto still has some fight left.
They weren't kidding
when they warned me about you.
Said you were big time.
What are you doing? Who sent you?
Don't you remember what I told you?
Dumping weapons like this
doesn't sit well with some.
They made me a deal.
Bukseong said, if I get rid of you,
I could deal with the Russians.
Go on and finish him off.
We don't have all day.
[gunshots]
[intense music playing]
[grunting]
[panting]
Get out of here.
[boss] All right, Kuto. Don't shoot.
All right, yeah.
We… we can talk.
[yelps]
[gun fires]
[grunts]
-[bones crack]
-[yells in pain]
Look out!
[gun firing]
You fucker!
[panting]
Throw the money over.
[grunts]
[tense music]
[pounding]
[panting]
Hey.
So long, old man.
[gunshots]
[gun firing]
[groaning]
[whimpering, moaning]
Boss, are you all right?
[boss] Come on, get the money
and guns. Hurry! Hurry up!
-Uncle!
-[Tae-gu] Hey, wait!
[panting]
Hey! [grunts]
You look fine, boss. It's just a scratch.
[boss groans]
How would you like to have a matching one?
[groaning]
Uncle!
Huh?
[Jae-yeon] Uncle!
-[chokes, grunts]
-[Jae-yeon] Uncle, no!
Uncle, open your eyes. [sobbing]
-[sobbing] What the hell happened here?
-[grunts, exhales]
[Jae-yeon crying]
Go kill her.
No…
[boss gasps] Shit! What the fuck?
-[grunts]
-Hey.
I'll kill him.
-Boss?
-Hey, fucking back up.
He's got a knife. Put that shit away.
-Got it.
-[clattering]
[sobbing]
[wailing]
No!
Jae-yeon…
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry for everything.
Hey, don't speak, Uncle.
[Jae-yeon] Just stay still. Hang on.
Save your strength.
I'm grateful…
[groaning]
…that you didn't hate me for it.
Thank you…
[gagging]
[Jae-yeon] Oh, Uncle!
[grunts]
[chokes]
[gasping]
Come on, Uncle.
Uncle, don't you dare.
Uncle!
[Jae-yeon screams] Uncle!
[gasps]
Uncle, no!
[yells]
[sorrowful music playing]
[Jae-yeon wailing continues]
[grunts]
I see. You're Park Tae-gu.
Get the son of a bitch!
[gun firing]
[dramatic music rising]
[gun fires]
[clicks]
[clicking]
[Tae-gu] It's over.
Let's go. Now.
They'll be back with others soon.
[Tae-gu] Come on!
Hey, snap out of it. We need to go.
Come on, we need to get out of here, now!
What about Uncle?
[panting]
Your uncle…
I'm sorry. He's dead.
[slap]
[Jae-yeon] Don't you say that to me!
You take it back.
You say he's not dead!
You say that, you bastard!
-Snap out of it, damn it!
-How can you say that about him?
[yells]
You bastard!
Let go of me. Let go of me!
Stop! Stop!
[door slams]
Stop the car!
[horn beeping]
Stop it!
[crying] Stop the car, please!
-Will you just sit still?
-Please! No!
-Stop the car!
-Please!
[both panting]
Hey!
-Not now, damn it.
-[Jae-yeon moans]
[groans]
Hey, hey! Stay with me.
Hey, this it?
[whimpering]
-[groaning]
-[bones cracking]
[grunts]
[plaintive music playing]
[both groaning]
[plaintive music continues]
[water trickling]
DRINKING FOUNTAIN
[delicate music playing]
[delicate music continues]
Do I turn left of here?
Yeah.
[crickets chirping]
[woman chuckles]
She's here!
Jae-yeon, it's been so long!
How are you? You doing good?
Good. How about you guys?
-Good.
-Are you sick?
You don't look like you're feeling well.
Oh, will you be all right?
Um, yeah. I'm just tired is all.
-[man] Let's get you inside.
-[woman] Right.
[man] I prepared our best room for you
as soon as I got your call.
[chuckles] Hey, by the way,
where is your uncle looking to move?
What's the deal?
Is he looking to upgrade or something?
He contacted me and said he was looking
to sell the house at a bargain.
Did the pipes burst again?
-Hm?
-Ah, I don't know.
You know how fickle he is.
[both chuckle]
-That's true.
-Right. [laughing]
And who is this?
Is he your boyfriend?
What?
Oh, no, no.
He's one of uncle's guests.
Oh… good.
Yeah, you need to be careful around men
these days, you hear me?
[man] No reason to fill her with nonsense.
[woman]
It's important she knows these things.
[man] She's not a child anymore.
[crickets chirping]
[approaching footsteps]
I thought you didn't like to drink.
Are you okay?
Really?
Should I be okay?
No.
I hate people who ask if you're okay…
when they clearly know that you are not.
If you don't know what to say,
you might as well say nothing.
[sighs sharply]
Are you okay?
Do I look okay?
No.
You know,
I hate it when people ask me
if I'm okay, when they can see that I…
[clicks tongue]
So then, what now?
I'm finally alone.
I don't have any family left.
[gasps]
[Jae-yeon] Because of my uncle,
Russian mobsters killed my entire family,
and my uncle's way of fixing things
was to kill them all in revenge.
[Jae-yeon] I understand that made him
a legend in your world, so they say.
I always hated my uncle for it.
He's the one that should've died.
Why did mom and dad have to die?
Why did my sister have to die?
They'd still be alive.
If only he would've been the one
to have died back then.
I cursed him every day for it.
"You fucking lowlife criminal thug,
just die."
But now, he's actually dead.
Why aren't I happy?
[inhales deeply]
It hurts…
right here.
I don't know why it hurts.
I wished him dead a thousand times.
I should feel satisfied.
But I don't.
[Jae-yeon sobbing]
Why is this happening to me?
Why does everyone keep leaving?
[Jae-yeon] You wanna sleep with me?
It's all right.
Come on, don't you want to?
What?
Come here, let's go.
[exhales]
It's fine. It doesn't matter.
It's not like I'm saving myself.
I'm dead soon.
So it really doesn't matter.
I'm good with it.
Yeah, but the thing is…
I'm not good with it.
What?
Ah, don't be offended.
Uh, hey, look,
you're an attractive girl and everything.
I'm just discerning.
What I mean is, what kind of guy sleeps
with just any woman
who throws themselves at him?
I'm not that guy.
[scoffs]
[door opens]
[clicking]
-[scoffs]
-[lock clicks]
[sighs]
[scoffs]
Discerning gangster.
You're not my type anyway.
Such bullshit.
[clicks tongue]
[dramatic music]
[dramatic music continues]
Sure, I'll see you then, sir.
[Tae-gu] No problem.
Okay, then.
[clears throat]
Let's go grab some food.
It's all right. Not hungry.
Come on. I'll get you something good.
Gonna try it?
Mm.
I have to after your review.
You said it's so good
you'd miss it from beyond the grave.
Really good.
I thought you didn't like raw fish.
Well, it's not true. I'd eat it every day.
[sniffles]
Actually, mulhoe is my favorite food.
When I was young… [sniffles]
…my family lived by the sea.
Whenever we run out of food,
my mother would go down
to the fish markets,
pick over leftover fish
to make mulhoe for us, like this,
with chojang or whatever she had.
My sister got so sick of eating it,
by the time she grew up,
she couldn't even stand the smell.
But for some reason, I always loved it.
Even… today.
Just seeing mulhoe reminds me of my mom.
The smell makes me think about her.
It's nice.
Aren't you gonna eat?
I'll have yours too, then.
No way. Uh-uh.
Get your hands off.
Of course I'm eating.
[delicate music playing]
[munching]
[waves crashing]
[birds chirping]
[dramatic music]
[sighs]
Do we have our guys ready and waiting?
Yes, sir. They're with our men from Busan.
I need to drop by the airport.
Don't go.
Something's off.
You said yourself,
you couldn't reach any of your guys.
-It's just a situation…
-I don't care.
It's just… [sighs]
Please don't go.
It doesn't feel right.
Besides, I hate being alone.
[woman] Oh my,
what wonderful weather today.
Your blanket will be crisp and clean
in no time.
[man] Why are you screaming?
Everyone will hear you.
Of course, they'll hear me.
I'm talking to them.
-That's the point, you old fool.
-Don't you snap at me.
I won't be long.
[suspenseful music]
[engine revs]
[somber music playing]
[inaudible]
[phone vibrating]
Shit, Jin-sung, what happened?
Why haven't you been answering?
[Jin-sung] Tae-gu!
What's going on?
That fucking snake, Yang, betrayed us.
What?
I'm telling you.
Your boss, Yang, sold you out.
And it's not just you, that asshole
turned on the entire lot of us.
We're all fucked, boss.
Save your ass.
[grunts]
Hello? Jin-sung? Jin-sung!
[Jin-sung groaning over phone]
[line cuts]
[suspenseful music]
[phone vibrating]
Wait, hold on, hold on.
Tae-gu!
Where are you going? Hold on. Hey!
Move!
-[henchman 6] Stop right there!
-[henchman 7] After him!
[grunts]
[intense music playing]
[henchman 6] Second floor.
Get up the stairs!
[grunts, groans]
[Tae-gu] Shit!
You…
[tense music]
Move, damn it!
[panting]
[tires screeching]
[henchman 6] Hey! Get him!
[intense music continues]
-[tires screeching]
-[horn honks]
[breathing heavily]
[horns honking]
[intense music continues]
[brakes screeching]
[rasping]
[glass shatters]
[engine revving]
[grunts]
[tires screech]
[ominous music]
[pants]
[groans]
[henchman 6] Drag his ass out!
[panting]
[henchman 8] Hey!
-Open the door.
-Come on, shithead.
[grunting]
Tae-gu, son of a bitch!
You're a dead man!
[groaning]
[henchman 9] Drag him out of the car!
[elegiac music playing]
[grunts]
[screaming]
[henchman screams]
[groans]
[slashing]
[grunts]
[panting]
Come on. Come on! I dare you.
[sirens wailing]
-[grunts]
-Get him!
[panting]
[clamoring]
[grunts]
[sirens wailing]
[phone vibrating]
[clatters]
We lost him, sir.
[groans]
What now, asshole?
How are you gonna honor
our deal now, Do-soo?
-Give me a tool or something.
-Wait, I can catch him. I can get him.
Not a gun, moron.
[spluttering]
Mr. Ma, don't do this. Listen.
Just hear me out.
All right, then.
-Tell me how you're gonna get him.
-Hold on. There's a guy named Jin-sung.
He's one of his men, and I have him.
[Do-soo panting]
We can use him.
You fucking snake.
You're a real scumbag, aren't you, hm?
Oh, this piece of garbage.
I feel filthy just being in the car
with this asshole.
Scoot over there. Get away.
As far as you can.
-Open the windows, will ya?
-[henchman 10] Yes, sir.
[panting]
Hey!
Where did she go?
Jae-yeon. Do you know where Jae-yeon's at?
Jae-yeon went back to her farm.
[man] She said she had to see her uncle.
She was getting something.
She asked to borrow my pickup truck.
Wait… Don't worry.
She said she'd be back soon.
[panting]
Hey, where the fuck are you?
Hey, what's with all the swearing?
[Tae-gu] I told you not to go anywhere.
Get back now!
Yeah, and I told you
not to go anywhere too.
Yeah, yeah. Fine.
Just come back right now!
I'll be back soon. I couldn't just leave
my uncle like that.
Goddamn it! Listen to me.
Your uncle's gone.
They already would've cleaned
everything up.
Are you listening to me?
You have to get out there right now!
I can hear you just fine.
Stop freaking out.
-I'll be back soon.
-No, wait! Hey!
Hang on.
-Ah, son of a bitch!
-[engine starts]
[dramatic music]
[car approaching]
[banging]
[panting]
[phone vibrating]
[Do-soo] Ah, Tae-gu, you finally answered.
Where are you?
Tae-gu?
Why'd you sell me out?
Tae-gu, it's not like that…
Why'd you sell out my guys, too?
It's more complicated than you think.
Answer me, you asshole!
How dare you speak to me like that?
Shit, okay, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry about everything, really…
You gotta be kidding me with that.
Don't forget that you're the one
that started all this.
[exhales]
You need to take responsibility
for your actions.
If you don't turn yourself in,
more innocent people are gonna die. You--
Hey, Park Tae-gu. Director Ma, Bukseong.
We met a few times. Do you remember, hm?
I'll keep this short.
There's something we need to settle, huh?
I'll give you an hour to get here.
And if you don't show up,
there will be a steep price to pay.
First of, your boy Jin-sung
is gonna die, of course,
and so will she.
[tires screech]
[Sang-gil] Listen.
Just come in and we can wrap this up
nice and clean.
There's no reason
for innocent people to die, right?
You'd still die,
no matter what.
Whether you show or whether you don't.
So think about the price of running away.
You still there?
All right, then.
-I'm coming.
-Ah, that's the spirit.
That's the guy I heard about.
I knew you were a stand-up guy.
But you promise me…
Jin-sung lives and so does the girl.
Ah.
Don't worry yourself, huh?
You have my word.
You know me.
I don't stab people in the back
like some you know.
[Sang-gil] What?
[sighs]
Sure.
We can do that.
What? Wanna see her on video?
Shit, just come see her yourself.
[grunts]
Phone call for you.
Don't come, are you insane?
Why would you? Are you an idiot?
Remember, I'm dying anyway.
So am I. You heard what he said.
I'm dead either way.
Besides, you hate being alone.
[Tae-gu] Just hold on, I'll be there soon.
[Sang-gil] An hour isn't very long.
I don't have much patience
for those who show up late.
But if you do show up on time,
you get a reward.
Think of it as a going away present.
And when you get it…
[chuckles]
…you're gonna thank me.
You remember meeting me?
You were only this high
last time I saw you.
Now, you're all grown up.
[chuckles]
Do you remember now?
[scoffs]
Are you fucking kidding me?
Do you think I remember
every slimeball I meet?
[laughs]
Oh, you really are a mouthy little thing.
Oh my, haven't you been taught
to respect your elders?
You have to earn my respect.
And you haven't earned shit.
You must wanna die.
Kill me.
Whether it's today or tomorrow,
I'll be dead anyway.
Oh, this girl's got no respect for life.
How'd you end up with that outlook, huh?
Whoa! Kuto did one hell of a job
raising you, little one.
[dramatic music playing]
[dramatic music continues]
[groans]
[grunting]
You fucking bastard!
[groans]
[grunts]
-[henchman 11] Who are we kidding here?
-[henchman 12] Asshole!
[henchman 13] Fucker!
Son of a bitch!
[panting]
Welcome, asshole.
[henchman 11]
Park Tae-gu, you piece of shit.
[door opens]
[Sang-gil] You're here.
Look.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
You okay?
[groans] Do I look okay to you?
[chuckles]
No.
You know what,
I hate it when people ask if I'm okay
when they know that I'm clearly not.
[chuckles]
But…
it's nice of you to ask.
Okay, what is this situation
I'm watching here, huh?
Has there been something brewing
between you two?
Are you boyfriend and girlfriend?
What if we are?
[Jae-yeon] Is it your business, asshole?
There's her classy mouth again.
[sighs]
Make the call, you fucker.
Let Jin-sung go,
just like you promised me.
[scoffs]
And now, we have another mouthy one here.
Don't you have any manners?
I guess, these days,
no one respects their elders.
[sighs]
Ah, whatever. Whatever.
You're gonna be dead soon,
anyway. Shit.
Hey, call the hospital and let him go.
[henchman 11] Yes, sir.
[Sang-gil] Ah, kids these days
are so disrespectful.
-[groans]
-Hold still.
[choking]
[whispers]
Somebody already got him.
Huh?
What the fuck are you saying to me?
Hey, Yang.
Really? Huh?
You went in and had Tae-gu's men killed?
Well, we needed to get him anyway.
No reason to risk him,
causing problems for us or anything.
-Are you fucking kidding?
-[Do-soo] Mr. Ma! Hold on! Come on!
[Sang-gil] Goddamn!
-[Do-soo] Hold on a second.
-I'm gonna spill your guts all over.
-[Do-soo] Ma, I'm sorry. Don't kill me.
-I made a promise to him.
Please forgive me.
Forgive me just this once.
Hey, remember what Captain Park said?
Remember what Captain Park said?
Killing me is a bad idea.
It'll make trouble for everyone.
Okay, listen to me, huh?
Jin-sung, he was loyal
to take him to a fault.
There's no telling what he would do.
We couldn't risk keeping him alive.
I did the right thing by killing him.
I did it for us.
You fucking son of a bitch, Yang!
You motherfucker!
[grunts angrily]
How could you do that?
-How could you fucking do that?
-This shit.
[Tae-gu] I'm gonna kill you.
-Oh, this asshole…
-[metal clatters]
You need to watch how you talk to me.
[Tae-gu] You bastard!
You need to check yourself
before you start cursing other people.
[Do-soo] Keep in mind,
this is all your fault.
None of this would've happened,
if you hadn't attacked Chairman Doh
in the first place, huh?
Oh, hey, Yang Do-soo!
Yang Do-soo, I'll kill you!
[Tae-gu] Yang Do-soo, I'll kill you!
I'll kill you!
Looks like you haven't had enough yet.
-[Do-soo] You shit!
-[Jae-yeon] No! Stop!
Don't hit him! Stop! Stop!
[Do-soo] Did I tell you to do it?
Did I order it, huh?
-[Jae-yeon] Stop!
-I never told you to do a thing!
Son of a bitch! [grunts]
[Jae-yeon wailing]
-Stop!
-She's right. Come on, enough.
[Sang-gil] That's enough.
Oh, shit. He's gonna kill the damn kid.
[grunts]
[Jae-yeon] Please, stop!
-Please!
-Yes, you shit now, you fucking…
Oh, hey! [groans]
[groans] Ah, fuck, that hurts.
[Do-soo groaning]
[clears throat]
This guy is really something, huh?
Real fucking piece of work, huh?
He's barely even human, isn't he?
He's more like a cockroach,
this fucking guy.
[groaning]
Ah, shit.
I told you to stop, didn't I? You asshole.
[claps]
Hey, Tae-gu!
Tae-gu.
Remember the gift…
I promised you earlier?
I have information
that should interest you.
It's about your dead sister.
[Sang-gil]
Chairman Doh had me investigate.
I assumed we were involved,
so I roughed up my own guys,
really grilling them hard.
Turns out…
it wasn't us after all.
It's true.
[Sang-gil] Yeah, just think about it, huh?
Even if we saw you
as some kind of obstacle,
we wouldn't dishonor ourselves
with dirty tactics.
[clicks tongue]
We would've just killed you.
You know.
Who then?
Well, Yang, speak up.
[Sang-gil] You care to tell him
what happened to his sister and niece?
He has some questions.
[tense, dramatic music plays]
Why…
Why would he…
[Sang-gil] Isn't it obvious, huh?
Chairman Doh had poached everyone
from him and was recruiting you.
He was worried that you would leave
and that you would take
your boys with you.
And then, he'd be left all alone and weak.
Does that, uh, about sum it up?
[Sang-gil laughs]
[breathes shakily]
You bastard!
[Tae-gu] I'll fucking kill you!
[yells]
I'll kill you, fucker!
[grunts]
Son of a bitch!
Bastard! Die!
[choking]
[Tae-gu] Die, you bastard!
Just die, damn it!
[Tae-gu] Fucking die!
Fucking die!
Wait! What are you doing?
[Jae-yeon] What are you doing?
No! Stop! What are you doing?
[Jae-yeon yelling] Oh, my god!
No!
[Jae-yeon whimpering]
Oh, you goddamn son of a bitch!
Get up, you asshole! Come on! Come here!
[grunts]
[wailing]
Let go! Hey!
Let go, you asshole!
[Tae-gu] You motherfucker!
[groaning]
[grunts]
[groans]
Tae-gu…
Don't speak my name, you asshole…
I'm gonna take you to hell with me.
You're dying with me, you worthless prick.
[Jae-yeon shouting] No!
[dramatic music swelling]
[slamming continues]
Oh, no! [screaming]
No, no, no…
[Jae-yeon grunts]
[Jae-yeon wailing]
[dramatic music continues]
[Jae-yeon sobbing]
[Do-soo] You bastard.
-[groaning]
-[Jae-yeon crying]
[sighs]
[Jae-yeon] You goddamn bastard!
I'm sorry,
but I've let you have enough fun, eh?
[exhales] I really wish I could…
let you kill that bastard.
I would offer him up
as a parting gift to you, if I could.
But, there'll be nothing
but trouble for us if that scumbag dies.
[panting]
Tae-gu, hey.
It's time for us to settle the score.
Hm?
[Jae-yeon screams]
[dramatic music rising]
[Jae-yeon wailing]
-[squelching]
-[grunts]
[screaming continues]
[crying] Don't…
[sobbing]
[gasping, groaning]
Don't cry.
It is pointless.
Stop your crying.
I'm not.
Why would I?
[Jae-yeon] Over you?
Why would I cry over you?
Well…
Now, you respect me…
since…
I'm gonna die…
before you.
Your rules.
Did I say that, kid?
'Cause I'm not agreeing to it.
Anyway,
you're just a short time ahead of me.
Of course…
of course, you'd say something like that.
[both chuckle softly]
[gasping]
[breathing heavily]
No, stop, back off! He's already dead!
Please, let him be.
[Do-soo] Yeah, you're right.
He's definitely dead.
-Leave him alone!
-[Do-soo groans]
Stop fucking biting me!
Shit!
Crazy bitch.
Oh, that actually fucking hurts.
[Do-soo groans]
[somber music]
[exhales]
[delicate music playing]
[Do-soo] Tae-gu.
You're in a lot of pain.
Here, I'll make it stop.
-[squelching]
-[Tae-gu groans]
[Do-soo grunts]
[lighter clicks]
[exhales]
All right, let's go. Clean this shit up.
What about the girl, sir?
Why would you ask me that?
Director Ma, I'll do it. Here.
-Hand me the knife.
-[Sang-gil] What?
I'm already covered in blood.
I might as well be the one to do it.
You won't touch her, huh?
I keep my word.
Besides, as we heard,
she doesn't have long to live.
This heartless bastard.
Even more reason to offer it.
She should be dead soon, anyway.
I said, no, that's enough,
you sick bastard!
-What the fuck is wrong with you?
-All right.
Take a look at yourself.
You're the goddamn one
that should be lying there dead.
Get him out of my sight.
[Sang-gil] Go.
I can't stand the sight of him.
Oh, wait. Hold on. Hold on.
Give me my check.
-[door slams]
-[sighs, groans]
[grunts] Shit!
[groaning] Oh, my fucking head.
[sighs]
[Sang-gil] Ah, I hope the room's ready.
I need to lie down.
[somber music plays]
[fire crackling]
[somber music continues]
[Jae-yeon] Oh, they're out for breakfast.
Thanks so much.
Did you recommend a particular restaurant?
Thanks! I appreciate your help.
[plaintive music playing]
[ominous music]
[indistinct chattering]
[clicks]
Well, look who it is.
[henchman 11] You here for breakfast?
I have bad news.
Seats are all filled.
[henchmen laughing]
[henchman 12] Hey, let her in.
She can sit on my lap!
[laughter continues]
[henchman 11] So, how about it?
You wanna come sit with us?
We can get to know each other right now.
Why don't you come have a drink with us?
Come on. Come on, it's fine.
Look at all these pussycats.
We aren't all that scary, are we, huh?
[henchmen laughing]
Over here!
[indistinct chattering]
[henchman 11] Shit.
[laughing]
[gun cocks]
[groans softly]
[ominous music]
I'm not here to eat.
Now, get your hands off.
[gunshots]
[intense music soaring]
[deep drums echoing]
[clicking]
[clattering]
[Jae-yeon panting]
-[clicking]
-[henchman yells]
[men gasping]
Oh, you fucking assholes.
You shitheads think this door
is bulletproof or something, huh?
This isn't a pellet gun she's holding,
you idiots.
[scoffs]
[sighs]
[chuckles]
You got a score to settle.
I can respect that.
Gotta do what you gotta do.
[glass shatters]
[henchman 13] This bitch is crazy.
[whimpering]
[gunshots]
[men groaning]
[gasping]
[choking]
[groans] Damn it.
Shit.
[Do-soo gasping]
[gasping]
[Do-soo] Wait, hold on. Just hold on.
Stop, now.
Hang on, we'll talk.
We can talk, right?
No. [splutters]
[gun fires]
[thuds]
[lock clicks]
[somber music plays]
[somber music continues, rising]
[waves crashing]
[somber music soars]
[sirens wailing]
[waves crashing]
[gunshot echoing]
[delicate music plays]
[somber music playing]