This film was inspired by true events
Tokyo Harbor
A powerful hurricane has emerged
off the Philippine coast,
and is projected to move north.
Its name is Jane.
Jane...
That's a lovely name.
Sir, we are ready to begin
the Diversion Operation.
Planning to launch
in Yeongdeok, Jangsadong,
Gunsan and Samcheok
on September 12th and 14th.
Sir, if I may...
Yes?
This operation could entail
many casualties.
Should we proceed?
June 25, 1950
June 25, 1950 With the Soviet Union's
support, North Korea invades the South
June 27, 1950 USA President
Truman deploys the U.S. Army
June 27, 1950 and assigns General Douglas MacArthur
as the Commander-in-chief of the UN Command
However,
the rest of South Korea, north of
the Nakdong River, falls in a month
In order to turn the tide of war,
Gen. MacArthur orders
a covert operation involving 8 men
One week ago
Comrade, got a light?
"They Fought For Their Country."
THEY FOUGHT FOR THEIR COUNTRY
If you read those books too much,
you will lose touch with reality.
But our ideas of the world
all came from books.
At the end, the protagonist gets shot,
and while dying,
he looks up at the blue sky.
But...
Sholokhov describes the blue sky
with a beautiful metaphor,
and I'm saying that is a lie.
Cut the chitchat
and get to your point.
What I mean is...
when a man is dying in pain,
would he admire the beautiful sky?
Am I wrong?
Comrade Park Nam-Cheol.
We'll go to Incheon for you.
Head of Incheon Defense Zone Ops,
Lieutenant Ryu Jang-Choon, Sir.
I'm Park Nam-Cheol.
Defense Commander is expecting you.
Our convoy is standing by.
PROTECT OUR LAND WITH OUR BLOOD Incheon has been
liberated by Democratic People's Republic of Korea!
Incheon has been liberated
by Democratic People's Republic of Korea!
Hooray for the liberation of Incheon!
Citizens of Incheon!
Your land has been liberated!
Let us march forward together
toward the liberation of the country!
Your time of peace has started!
Unacceptable, intolerable, insulting!
War Room, UN Command HQ, Tokyo
Get back to work!
Tell the French to send more troops!
War Room, UN Command HQ, Tokyo
Pester them until they do!
If they refuse, I will call
President Auriol myself.
And what of the Australians?
Are they sending their
aircraft carriers or are they not?
Find out at once.
And I won't accept anything but "yes."
Yes, Sir!
Sir, we've just received intel on their
fortification efforts on Wolmido Island.
The commander in charge
is named Lim Gye-Jin.
And the construction is under his control,
not Pyeongyang's.
Park Nam-Cheol reporting.
I'm Lim Gye-Jin.
How's the Nakdong River front?
It's a bloodbath.
Of course.
Here is the report
of our troop placement.
226th Infantry Regiment is in Incheon.
918th Artillery Regiment,
second battalion is stationed there.
2,048 infantry, 231 in Artillery Regiment
and 487 in 42nd Armored Vehicle Regiment.
Considering Incheon's geography,
the enemy can only access land routes
from Gimpo, Siheung and Hwaseong.
Aviation units and artillery units
are stationed at each location.
Incheon's harbor is fortified
by six meter-high seawalls,
making it impossible to climb over.
What is the best defense
if the American bastards attack by sea?
There is only one narrow channel
into the bay they could access.
One disabled landing boat
could completely block the entrance.
Once it's blocked off, we'll use a 76 mm
artillery gun barrage to wipe them out.
That is all.
Comrade Lieutenant...
76 mm artillery guns would be useless.
If the landing boats get to shore,
it's all over.
They must be stopped at sea.
Also...
why no mention of naval mines?
Are they not set?
We...
lined the waterway with them.
You marked them clearly on a map then?
Bring it to me.
I...
will be personally reporting that
to the Supreme Commander himself.
When will you begin
the on-site inspections?
Tomorrow at 0700 hours sharp.
Comrade Park...
don't be so hasty.
Good work, men. Rest easy.
Just pass out on the bed.
Incheon became like this
in just two months.
Young Master,
allow me to do that for you.
I've got hands, too.
And I told you not to call me that.
The dog days have passed.
I had so many chickens back home.
Confirm their transmission
and send this, too.
Yes, Captain.
Report 1, enemy regiment
locations in Incheon.
Report 2, defensive positions
on the coast.
KLO Incheon (Korea Liaison Office)
Covert Intelligence Unit
This is SEO Jin-Chul from KLO Incheon.
Sir, we've made contact with the KLO.
Tell them to locate the mines.
Finding the exact location
is top priority.
Do whatever it takes.
Yes, Sir!
This is a direct order
from General MacArthur.
Is that Palmido Lighthouse?
That is correct.
VICTORY CELEBRATION TOAST
This is Inspector Park Nam-Cheol
from the headquarters.
They're Incheon Hospital staff.
Be careful of him.
This gentleman is here to monitor us.
Isn't that right?
Comrade Park...
When I studied
at the Communist University of Moscow,
Professor Malchikov was my idol.
Mine, as well.
When he...
shot his beautiful sister Sonja
and executed her with his pistol,
all of the Korean students cheered.
Do you know this story?
Sonja believed in Christianity...
so she got three bullets to the head.
Comrade Han, what do you think?
If your uncle believed in Christianity,
what would you do?
Dissuade him.
And if it's impossible
to dissuade him, then what?
But still, he's my uncle...
She means, he raised her
since she was a baby.
Just say you can kill him.
But how can a religious man
follow our party's ideology?
Religion has to be rooted out
just like with opium.
What would you do, Comrade Park?
It's up to the individual.
Comrade Park...
Do you believe in God?
Do you see God?
Where is He?
The party has already said
there is no God.
Isn't that right?
What is your unit password?
I could be shot
for being reckless with it.
Comrade Lim...
Crimson Dostoevsky
Crimson Dostoevsky.
This is Jung Sun-Sil.
Head Secretary's Office
DPRK HQ, Pyeongyang
Head Secretary's Office DPRK HQ, Pyeongyang
It has been a while, Defense Commander.
Head Secretary's Office
DPRK HQ, Pyeongyang
Head Secretary's Office DPRK HQ,
Pyeongyang How may I help you?
Do you know Park Nam-Cheol
from the Supreme Headquarters?
Yes, of course.
Do you know him well?
Comrade Park has a knife scar
on the left side of his neck.
All done.
You don't need a trim today.
Very good.
As you say.
Take it, it's a gift.
But Sir, why me?
I don't deserve this.
Please give it to Comrade Han.
I'm kidding! Put it on!
Of course!
Supreme Commander
Kim Il-Sung! Hooray!
We're at wits' end.
They won't cough it up,
and we don't know where it is.
Can't they use a minesweeper
at the start of the invasion?
That's nonsense!
The coverage area is too wide
for something like that.
Emergency inspection!
Everyone freeze!
Yankee Nemesis MacArthur
Puppet Syngman Rhee
Defense Commander...
This document was submitted to me.
The number of naval mines
doesn't match up.
I need to inspect them personally.
Give me the chart.
Comrade Park...
you're awfully interested
in those mines.
What's with the fixation?
My objective here is to make sure
everything is in order, is it not?
I told you before...
I'm reporting that
directly to Pyeongyang.
Do you still want to see it?
Defense Commander...
have you made a mistake?
Why can't I ever get
a clear answer on naval mines?
My apologies.
Spies are littered everywhere.
Begin sending out false intel
regarding landing operations in...
Wonsan, Jumunjin,
and Gunsan.
Make sure the transmissions
are wiretapped.
Send out massive amounts!
Yes, Sir.
Yes?
Efforts to gather intel
on the mines were unsuccessful.
They need more time.
Without detecting the mines,
our fleet cannot navigate through
the narrow waterways at Incheon.
Orders, Sir?
Orders?
Get God on the phone.
Tell Him it's me.
Tell Him we need more time.
September 2nd,
Wonsan bombing scheduled.
October 14th, landing in Jumunjin.
September 19th,
assemble 120 ships in Gunsan.
September 12th,
landing in Yeongdeok, Jangsa-dong.
Central Relay Center DPRK HQ,
Pyeongyang Lieutenant...
Central Relay Center
DPRK HQ, Pyeongyang
Central Relay Center DPRK HQ, Pyeongyang September
6, the UN forces are assembling in Kobe port.
Central Relay Center DPRK HQ, Pyeongyang They're calling
for all-out attack at the Nakdong River frontline.
They're calling for all-out attack
at the Nakdong River frontline.
Where are they targeting?
Win over Lim Gye-Jin.
Earn his trust and gather necessary intel.
Captain...
We're to recruit Lim.
LONG LIVE THE PEOPLE'S REPUBLIC OF KOREA
Where do you think MacArthur will attack?
I'm certain it's Incheon.
I have to convince
the idiots in Pyeongyang...
but the proof isn't there.
I know you worked
at the National Intelligence Bureau.
You didn't hear anything?
Any words you heard
from the Soviets or China?
Headquarters believes
that it won't be Incheon.
I believe MacArthur will...
come to Incheon.
Do you know what those Americans
estimate as their chances at Incheon?
Five thousand to one.
It's virtually impossible.
So why should he come
to Incheon with those chances?
To be remembered as a hero?
That old decrepit wants Incheon
to be his Normandy?
UN Command HQ, Tokyo
August 23, 1950, final strategy meeting
Well, well, well...
The Pentagon must be on milk break,
dispensing The Three Stooges
to silence the old mad dog.
The Three Stooges, huh?
To silence the old mad dog.
Who's Moe?
Well, I'm Larry.
Well, I'm sure as hell
not gonna be Curly.
- C'mon gentlemen!
- Then, I'm Moe!
Big smile!
DPRK HQ, Pyeongyang
Where do you think the UN will attack?
Wonsan, Jumunjin, Gunsan
and Incheon are all smoke screens.
I believe it's very likely
that they will invade Gimpo
with paratroopers
from hundreds of planes!
They could defy convention
and attack Pyeongyang directly.
Supreme Commander
Kim Il-Sung
Supreme Commander Kim Il-Sung Why
is no one talking about Incheon?
Why is no one talking about Incheon?
Incheon tides
are the worst in the world!
They rise and fall at an average
rate of 29 feet each day.
Sometimes as high as 36!
Our ships will be stranded
within ten minutes of entry!
And the harbor?
Harbor's too narrow
to be able to turn around.
That is why we developed
three separate routes.
Red, green and blue!
Even if we get through,
there's only one landing zone
in Incheon.
Incheon Harbor
There!
Landing is not the only problem.
Incheon Harbor
The mudflats will swallow our tanks.
How do you expect our marines
to climb treacherous cliffs that high
with waves that harsh?
There is a simple solution.
We use ladders.
Ladders...
More importantly,
how do you expect to move
75,000 troops at dusk
with only one hour
of daylight remaining?
There is a lighthouse
on the Palmido shore.
We will seize it, and there will be light.
Well, I don't know
about you, gentlemen,
but this gives me great confidence.
I'm gonna go back to Washington
and break the good news.
"President Truman,
General MacArthur says
we've got nothing to worry about.
Because we have ladders
and a lighthouse.
We're not going to Busan.
Instead, we're gonna send
75,000 troops to Incheon.
Why?
Because we have ladders
and a lighthouse."
I think I'm gonna drink to that.
To a successful campaign!
Vandenberg,
do you want to win this war?
I think I should be asking
the same question of you, General.
What do you think?
There are men dying in Busan,
and you're proposing a suicide mission!
Fortifying Busan is suicide!
Don't hit them where they are strong,
hit them where they are not!
Cut off their supply line!
Force 'em to starve!
Is MacArthur stupid?
All of our forces
are at the Nakdong frontlines.
Why'd he try to fight us there?
Are they all morons?
Out of the frying pan and into the fire?
Hey, hey, hey!
Even the U.S. Secretary
of Defense has said
the odds of a successful invasion
of Incheon are five thousand to one.
Five thousand to one.
Five thousand to one!
That's the odds that you get on this one!
This is the riskiest military operation
that I've ever encountered!
But that's it!
Know your enemy and yourself,
you can win all wars!
Supreme Commander...
do you know what MacArthur wants?
I fight wars to win!
Operation Chromite
is the only way to victory!
Operation Chromite?
It's a cute name.
You intentionally delay reporting to us...
your plans.
You wait until we get here
all the way from Washington,
and then you not only insult us...
but the President of the United States.
And then,
you have one plan with no recourse!
One plan!
Why?
Why the fixation on Incheon?
What MacArthur wants...
is to be the president.
That's why he needs a miracle
of five thousand to one.
This is exactly why he'll invade Incheon!
What are you after?
What do you want out of this?
Two days after the war
broke out in Korea,
I made a secret trip there
from Tokyo to assess the damage.
I made a secret trip there from Tokyo to assess the
damage. South Korean Defense Frontline June 28, 1950
South Korean Defense Frontline
June 28, 1950
I came across a young Korean boy alone in the trench.
South Korean Defense Frontline June 28, 1950
South Korean Defense Frontline
June 28, 1950
No older than sixteen South Korean
Defense Frontline June 28, 1950
No older than sixteen.
He had no gun, no shirt.
All others had retreated.
I was perplexed.
"Why are you here?" I asked him.
He replied,
"No one ordered me to leave."
No one ordered me to leave. He
replied, "No one ordered me to leave."
I was moved by his courage.
I said, "I will give you
anything you want."
He looked at me
with fire in his eyes and said,
Give me a gun and give me bullets.
"Give me a gun and give me bullets."
That boy and I shared something.
We were soldiers.
Two soldiers with the same goal...
victory!
I knew then I had to save
this boy's country.
We've got until September 10,
2100 hours to secure the chart.
It's not in the armory nor the archives,
not even the naval war room.
Their offices are the only places
left to check.
FOR THE VICTORY OF THE PEOPLE
Welcome.
When does the boat depart
from Songhaksa?
Have you brought an umbrella?
Sir...
Navy Intelligence Bureau
Captain Jang Hak-Soo.
KLO Incheon, Choi Suk-Joong.
Come sit down.
How can I help you?
We'll bring the naval mine chart.
Arrange a carrier for us.
When will it arrive?
Midnight tomorrow.
Understood.
After you hand over the chart, muster at
the abandoned school on Youngheung Island.
A unit led by Captain SEO Jin-Chul
will be waiting there.
Be careful.
Lim Gye-Jin is relentless.
Come in.
Not asleep yet?
May I...
go visit my children for a moment?
My wife sells vegetables
at a morning market nearby.
Once this mission is over,
the war will end.
Please hold on a little longer.
Of course.
Have a good night.
MARCH FORWARD TO ULTIMATE VICTORY
IN THE WAR OF UNIFICATION
We must infiltrate during the day.
Kang Bong-Po...
track guards during all shifts,
and their relief time.
Nam, distract the guards.
And Cho will sneak into Lim's office
through the window.
Song and Yang, get us more weapons.
Oh and CHUN,
secure the vehicles and exfil route.
I'll keep Lim and Ryu occupied
in the meantime.
Let's synchronize.
It's currently 1638 hours.
Upon securing the chart,
get out swiftly and safely.
Do it again.
Is this a joke?
Your salute is all wrong!
Get your eyeline right!
Where are you going?
Stand together. Salute again.
You clap and salute, clap and salute!
Stay focused! Clap and salute!
Again! Salute! Clap! Salute and clap!
Don't salute, clap!
Turn left when I say "Comrade,"
and your training is complete,
but if you turn right, you're a traitor.
Okay, Comrade.
Snap out of it! Do it right!
Again, Comrade.
We're leftists. Once more.
Comrade!
Snap out of it! You stupid shit!
Here.
I have many things to report,
so I'll head back, Sir.
Okay.
Comrade Ryu...
It's a good day,
why not stay a little longer?
Have a great time.
Do it right!
Comrade Ryu...
What brings you here?
Get back.
Back to your position!
Yes, Sir!
I managed to secure myself
a bottle of vodka.
Comrade Ryu...
Don't you hear me?
How about 50% alcohol vodka?
Your tongue will go insane.
That vodka...
looks like this.
Open it!
Incheon Sea Naval Mine Placement
Guards! Guards!
Two Southern spies!
Capture them!
Bastards!
Lift the sofa!
Get the chart!
Go!
In-Gook!
Get them! Go capture them!
Go!
When we achieve unification,
you should come to Incheon.
Okay.
What is it?
You must get out of there!
They're all imposters!
South Korean spies!
Park Nam-Cheol...
I've got a question for you.
You're part of the Soviet faction, right?
There's a famous story
that Soviet faction members know.
A guy was ordered
to shoot his bourgeois father,
but he couldn't.
So his friend fired the gun instead,
and he went nuts
and shot his comrades,
then defected to the South.
I know the faces
of all Soviet faction members,
but I don't know his face.
What was that crazy bastard's name?
Jang Hak-Soo.
Right, Jang Hak-Soo!
So, Jang Hak-Soo...
why are you here?
LONG LIVE THE SOVIET UNION
Answer me...
Jang Hak-Soo.
Young Master...
Hold.
Get out! Get outta here!
Out! Go!
Pan-Dong! Yang Pan-Dong!
Die!
The traitors are inside!
Get inside!
Hurry! Get inside!
The commander is in danger!
Go save him!
Captain!
Hop in! Go on!
Protect the commander!
Hurry up!
Sang-Deuk!
Captain!
Go!
Just go!
Sang-Deuk!
No!
You sons of bitches!
They walked in and robbed you blind!
Who was on guard?
I-I was, Sir!
Who else is a spy?
Did you help them infiltrate?
Commander!
These brothers had Yankee weapons!
Are you the older brother?
Brother! Brother!
Don't kill me!
I'll talk!
Look at him shake!
Untie him!
What's your name?
Lee Young-Cheol, Sir.
Tell me who handed you...
the guns.
Go on, tell me.
A man, he had big eyes...
and was wearing a watch.
A Kim Il-Sung watch!
I swear!
Isn't school the rendezvous point?
The mission went south.
Perhaps it was too much.
Why are you all so weak?
Skipped dinner?
How will you even hold up
a gun like that?
Pull yourselves together.
They're members of KLO Incheon.
They handle the DPRK food supply,
so they got unlimited access.
Let's go to Dongmundang first.
Ah, General Vandenberg.
General MacArthur.
Good to see you!
Please, sit. Tea? Coffee?
You've put us in an impossible
situation, General.
Truman is seriously
considering your plan.
But he wants to make
one thing perfectly clear.
We don't want the Chinese
to join the fight.
Once we reach this line...
the war has to end.
This war will not end by a politician
simply drawing some line on a map.
I won't agree to that.
It's a direct order from your
Commander-in-chief.
Why are you being
so stubborn, General?
And why is Truman so ignorant?
He wants a limited war?
That doesn't do any good.
Communism cannot be contained
with a limited war.
These politicians...
They don't know what war really is.
God, it's immoral to send our soldiers
to war unless total victory is sought!
I'm curious, General...
What's behind Operation Chromite?
What do you really want out of this?
Is Incheon supposed to be
your Normandy?
Huh?
Some grand theatrics...
before your second run
at the presidency?
You think I want to go to Incheon
to become president?
I have dedicated 50 years
of my life to the battlefield.
I'm Douglas MacArthur. I win wars.
Don't try and educate me
or analyze my motives.
Why did you volunteer
for this operation?
Well...
I wanted to protect my mother!
"I wanted to protect
my mother," Sir.
What are your plans for after the war?
I'd like to get a good night's sleep.
I would like that, too.
I will land on Incheon no matter what.
Open the way for me, Son.
I'll wait for you in Incheon, Sir.
This way. Hurry.
Uncle...
Chae-Sun...
What's going...
Wait, shush!
Uncle...
What's all this about?
- Uncle...
- Chae-Sun!
Jang Hak-Soo is a spy!
He's lying to you!
Please listen to me!
- No, you listen!
- What are you doing?
Rope! Rope!
What's going on?
What's happening?
Let go!
Uncle!
Let me go!
Freedom fighters hid here
during the Japanese imperialism.
Chae-Sun's parents built this place.
This is a secret tunnel.
It's connected
to the vacant house next door.
Use it in case of emergency.
Uncle, you're a traitor, too?
You can observe outside from here.
You're a traitor? Their snitch?
Please stay quiet
until sunrise.
Are you mad?
We'll all be killed!
Stand by until sunrise.
Please get me in touch
with the captain of KLO Incheon.
Will do.
Who's there?
Choi Suk-Joong.
Are you...
looking for this?
I was...
a communist once, too.
There's a phrase that I really loved.
"If the roots are rotting,
how could they bear fruit?"
It's a good phrase
to get students hooked.
But one day...
my comrades captured a bourgeois
and handed me a gun
and told me to shoot.
But it was my father.
I hesitated, too shocked to react.
Then my best friend shot my father.
My hesitation cost my father's life.
My friend looked at me,
filled with conviction...
and said,
"Ideology is thicker than blood."
You are being lied to.
What your uncle is doing-
Lights out!
Search every inch.
Let's go!
It's empty, Sir.
Where's Jang Hak-Soo?
I don't know who that is.
Fucking traitor.
Wake the whole neighborhood!
Walk faster!
Tie him up!
Please! Please help him!
He's trying to save you!
He's going to die!
I AM A YANKEE PUPPET
I DESERVE FULL PUNISHMENT
Please untie me!
If I talk to him,
the commander will listen to me!
Captain, she's gonna snitch!
We'll all be killed!
I won't tell them about you.
I'll never tell.
LONG LIVE THE INDEPENDENCE OF KOREA
You have to believe me!
We can't just watch him die!
Open the tunnel!
Captain!
Uncle! Please!
Lim Gye-Jin...
do you actually believe
in your rotten ideology?
Do you really want
everyone to be equal?
How can you kill those
who have different ideas?
It's your last chance.
Where is Jang Hak-Soo?
Go on, shoot me.
Shoot me!
No!
Uncle! No!
Let go!
U-Uncle!
Come on, bitch!
Uncle!
Where are they?
Where are those rats?
Tell me!
- You traitor!
- That's enough.
Enough.
It's Kim Hwa-Gyun, the driver!
Good, you're all safe.
Who's Captain Jang Hak-Soo?
I am.
We received Choi's message
and came to help.
I'm SEO Jin-Chul,
Captain of KLO Incheon.
The Incheon landing op is a go.
The op commences in three days.
Since the naval mine chart is gone,
you'll have to find
another way to locate them.
Easy for you to say!
Can't you see we're being slaughtered?
Stop it!
You're not the only ones at risk!
We're all in the same shit!
How dare you?
There are only five of us left!
Stop! Stop!
Enough!
Even the last man standing
must finish this!
Ryu Jang-Choon is in charge of the mines,
he'll know everything.
We must kidnap Ryu.
Do you have a plan?
He's hospitalized here.
Once we take him,
we'll exit through the basement.
So have a car standing by
at the backdoor.
DPRK soldiers will be dispatched
from the front,
so lure them from this area.
Lastly, this section must be blocked off.
This is very crucial.
I will...
block them off.
Me, too.
All right.
If we're not at the rendezvous
by 0850 hours,
assume that we've been exposed
and proceed without us.
Any questions?
Who'll take point from his room
to the X-RAY room?
I have someone in mind.
LET'S KICK AMERICA
OUT OF THE KOREAN BORDERS
Stop the truck!
Are you Mrs. Nam?
Honey...
Give him.
He's handsome.
Allow me.
Don't you worry.
I'll come back alive.
Move out!
LEPROSY EXAMINATION ROOM
SUSPICIOUS SKIN DISEASE UNIT
MEDICINE ROOM
Afternoon.
Commander.
What do we do?
A PATIENT'S LIFE IS THE PEOPLE'S LIVES
Comrade Han...
Your uncle...
chose the wrong path.
Use this opportunity
to raise your profile.
Ideology is thicker
than blood after all.
You'll feel drowsy.
Where are you going?
He needs an X-ray.
Shrapnels are still inside.
It's okay.
I can do it myself.
I have something to tell you.
Could you stay here for a moment?
Certainly.
What-
Who are you?
Move! Move!
They're going to the basement!
Go after them!
Captain!
Over here!
Run!
Here!
Run! Now!
Move!
After them!
Step on it!
Stay on their trail!
Grenade, grenade!
THE PEOPLE OF INCHEON ARE FREE
Watch out!
No!
Captain!
After them!
Move!
Go on without me.
You have to save yourself!
Shut up! We're leaving together!
You fucking rat!
DAL-Joong!
Captain!
Sis! We did it!
Sis!
No!
Any reports on our men?
This was successful in Wonsan,
but it's no guarantee.
What do you mean?
What are you doing?
Your heart might explode.
Hey! Hey!
Why would my heart explode? Why?
Mines aren't the only thing in your way!
Mines are nothing!
What's that?
What's that sound?
Th-There's something else on Wolmido!
Untie me and I'll tell you!
Our infantry stands at 75,000
on four aircraft carriers,
representing 16 countries, including
the U.S., England, France and Australia.
260 battleships are ready to deploy
from Tokyo, Kobe, Sasebo and Busan.
On D-Day, one regiment
from the ROK Marine Corps
will deploy from Busan
and join us there.
We've also recruited Korean students
from the U.S. and Japan as interpreters.
Good.
Deliver this message
to the X-RAY operatives.
"Valiant men of X-RAY,
make contact with KLO
and light the Palmido Lighthouse
on September 15th, 0000 hours.
Guide our fleet to the beach.
Lastly,
may the grace of God be with you."
Roger that.
We'll be waiting for further orders.
We got a report from the U.S. Navy.
"Ryu arrived safely,
and gave us the naval mine locations.
Here's our next mission.
We'll depart for Palmido
at 2200 hours.
Enemy resistance will be formidable.
Prepare for full engagement."
So we just need to light the lighthouse?
Yes.
Something wrong?
How many enemy soldiers
do you anticipate there?
Two squads, roughly 20 men.
I think Ryu was referring
to the Wolmido stronghold.
I'd like to check it out.
Look! Over there!
Captain! Hurry!
Citizens of Incheon!
Gather around!
DON'T HESITATE FOR YOUR ONE AND
ONLY COUNTRY Gather around!
DON'T HESITATE FOR YOUR
ONE AND ONLY COUNTRY
The traitors will be judged!
LOOK AT THE END OF THE REBELLION
THIS IS THE END OF U.S. IMPERIALISM
LOOK AT THE END OF THE REBELLION THIS IS THE END OF
U.S. IMPERIALISM Let us exterminate the traitors
LOOK AT THE END OF THE REBELLION
THIS IS THE END OF U.S. IMPERIALISM
and raise the red flag!
Young Master, don't be scared.
Don't ever lose your courage.
Enough of that "Young Master."
You're much older than I am!
Just call me Dae-Soo.
Do it!
I can't.
Hurry!
D-Dae-Soo...
Good.
When we're born again,
you'll be my big brother.
Brother...
Dae-Soo!
Shut up!
Brother!
DAL-Joong!
You son of a-
WE WILL REWRITE KOREAN HISTORY THROUGH BLOOD
SHOOT THE PUPPET SOLDIERS ONCE AND FOR ALL
400 km off southern tip of Jeju Island
September 13, 1950 (D-2)
Sir, Hurricane Kezia is currently passing 400 km off the southern tip of
Jeju Island. 400 km off southern tip of Jeju Island September 13, 1950 (D-2)
Sir, Hurricane Kezia is currently passing
400 km off the southern tip of Jeju Island.
If she continues on this course,
tomorrow night will be treacherous.
We will not turn back!
A long time ago I promised myself
that I would live
as though I expected to live forever.
Nobody grows old
by merely living a number of years.
People grow old
only by deserting their ideals.
Years may wrinkle the skin.
However, when you give up your ideals,
it will wrinkle the soul.
This will not be my last campaign.
Incheon Shore
September 14, 1950 (D-1)
Incheon Sea
2252 hours, September 14, 1950
Prepare to fire.
- Prepare to fire.
Prepare to fire!
Deploy all air units.
- Copy that, Sir.
- All clear.
Fire.
Wolmido Island
Must you go to Wolmido?
When it's safe, we'll fire a flare.
Please let General MacArthur know.
I understand. Godspeed.
I volunteered.
Medics are always in need.
Can't you come with us?
I'll be back shortly.
Cigarettes taste the best
after making love.
When the war is over,
come over for dinner.
My wife makes the best noodles.
And a pint to boot.
Last radio transmission, Sir.
Captain Jang is moving
toward Wolmido Island.
He said he will light the flare once
the beach landing site has been secured.
Palmido Island
2341 hours, September 14, 1950
Halt!
We have a Headquarters Pass!
Palmido Lighthouse
2357 hours, September 14, 1950
2358 hours, September 14, 1950
Foe is upstairs!
The Yankee artillery attack
will cease soon.
We will stand by until then.
Sir, look!
In the harbor!
And God said, "Let there be light."
The road to Incheon is open!
Ceasefire.
Ceasefire!
- Ceasefire!
Deploy advance unit.
Deploy advance unit!
Ceasefire, all units. Ceasefire.
Narrow Channel, Incheon Sea
0040 hours, September 15, 1950
Come.
Faster.
I'll turn Incheon Beach into a bloodbath!
Come at me!
Commander.
We'll begin, Sir!
Follow me!
The time has come.
Let's show those Yankees
what we're made of!
Yes, Sir!
- Battle station!
Move!
Stop! Stop!
Stopping!
Captain, TNT! It's TNT!
Does General MacArthur
know about this?
This was never reported, so he won't.
The UN forces could be wiped out!
What should we do?
Do we detonate them?
It's our duty!
Okay!
Bong-Po! To the beach!
To the beach!
Two vessels and one advance boat
have been destroyed!
Sir, we may have missed an artillery
turret. Should we try to turn around?
It's still low tide! We can't do that!
The advance unit is already heading
toward the landing zone!
Should we keep providing
cover-fire, Sir?
Increase speed as fast as possible.
Yes, Sir!
Increasing speed!
Did you see
the artillery muzzle flash?
Yes!
Head for it!
Toward the turret!
Captain...
Brother!
Captain!
Slow down.
Go slow, slow!
Slow.
On the double!
Plant faster!
Take the left, left!
Stop!
Move them faster!
MacArthur will be
in the vanguard battleship.
Destroy the vanguard battleship first!
3.5 Left!
2.3 Up!
Load cannon!
Loading cannon!
Jang Hak-Soo...
Reverse! Reverse!
Finish all the work!
Follow me!
Get rid of them!
Sir, that might have been
Captain Jang and his men.
What should we do?
Stand by.
The water is receding, Sir.
For our troops to make
a successful landing,
the entire fleet needs enough time
to pass through the narrow waterway.
Sir, if we wait another hour, our chances
of landing will drop significantly.
- We should take-
- I said stand by, goddamnit.
Wait for the signal.
Fire!
Retreat!
Bong-Po, let's move!
Bong-Po!
Wake up! Come on! Bong-Po!
We have to get out of here!
On your feet!
Hurry...
Stay put.
Just tell me Captain Jang fired
that flare gun.
I believe so, Sir.
Initiate Operation Chromite!
Hey, Jang Hak-Soo!
Come on out!
What's there to communism?
It's all about wanting
a better life together, isn't it?
Fucking rat...
No matter what you Yankee puppets do,
the red flag will march forward!
Jang Hak-Soo...
I sentence you to death
for tainting the people
with your betrayal!
Let's put an end to this.
JANG HAK-SOO KILLED ME
THE U.S. IMPERIALISTIC PUPPET JANG HAK-SOO!
TAKE ALL OF THE U.S. IMPERIALISTIC PUPPETS!
Mother...
I went to see you yesterday,
but I turned back
without saying goodbye.
I was afraid that I wouldn't be
able to walk away.
Mother...
To complete my assignment,
I chose our country.
It's unfilial for the child
to die before his parent.
I wanted to be by your side.
I'm sorry.
I'll watch over you from above.
You said...
you'd come back.
Honey, look carefully for Dad.
- Watch out for him.
- Yes, Mom!
Don't be so disappointed
if you don't see Captain Jang today.
Don't worry.
Whether he's close or far,
dead or alive,
my son will always be by my side.
Hak-Soo!
I was born in Masan
but grew up in Incheon.
I have great eyesight,
so I shoot really well. And I cook well.
I have someone to protect.
I'd like to do something meaningful.
I hope to use my shady skills
to save my country.
I lost all my family to this war.
I come from a family
of freedom fighters.
We should be fighting
for our own country.
I heard we get a ton of rice.
I have too many kids to feed.
I reproduced like rabbits.
All right.
Shall we take a photo?
To the 15 men who died
during Mission X-RAY,
including Lieutenant Lim Byung-Re,
Sergeant Hong Si-Wook and members of KLO,
and those who sacrificed their lives
for Korea's freedom and peace,
we dedicate this film
to them and their families.
13 clays after the successful
landing operation of Incheon,
on September 15, 1950,
the UN Allied Forces reclaimed Seoul.
They went on to take Pyeongyang,
but the Chinese army drove them back.
On July 27, 1953,
an armistice was reached,
drawing the war to an end after 3 years
with over 3 million casualties.