Sync & corrections  by Blue-Bird™
Subtitles by Telegram -@Hitesh004 / @Danny004
Sync by Sattan
Do you see the criminal
coming out behind me?
After about a year since
the beginning of 2016
The first extradition between the Philippines
and South Korea took place at 4 p.m. today.
For the first time, 47 Korean criminals
who absconded to the philippines
after committing crimes in Korea were
repatriated en masse by chartered flights.
This is police using citizens special
forces and local motorcade personnel...
Jong Dongbi, you bastard!!
What... Stop him! Stop!
Quick!
You son of bitch!!
Die with me!!
.
September 12th, now.
Burbad, Manila, Philippines.
Korean criminals arrested in the philippines
will be transported to Busan port
in 2 days at 7 p.m. on 14th.
By an international cargo ship departing
Manila Container Terminal at 5 p.m. today.
Considering that a suicide bombing at
the airport during the first repatriation
in 2017 killed seven police officers and
injured more than 30 airport passengers.
The convoy decided to use cargo ship
terminals inaccessible to private citizens.
Therefore, the National Police Agency, in
cooperation with the Busan Port Authority,
Designated the 58,000-ton bulk carrier
"Frontier Titan" as the escort vessel.
About 20 criminal police officers
with more than 10 years of experience
in violent cases were
assigned to escort the ship.
The wanted criminals were
repatriated as Red Notice criminals,
the highest ranking criminals by Interpol.
Hey, isn't our operation secret?
It was reported in the news.
Good job.
Stay close.
Get off quickly.
Quick, quick.
Get out of the bus quickly.
Get up.
I'm just telling you to
spread your legs a bit.
Get up quicky.
OK OK.
Where?
Let's go, let's go.
Don't touch me, shit.
Hey this way.
Ah the smell of shit, f♪♪k.
Lee Dong II, Red Scar,
Lee Sang-moo, get on board!
I thought you retired long ago.
Your daughter has become a woman.
Jungu.
You stupid bastard.
Since you're in school you
should listen to your teachers.
What kind of attitude is that?
I saw the photos and was very impressed.
How the f♪♪k can the
interpol beat a person up.
This is not right.
How come the wind is so strong?
Let go, let go.
Let me go, f♪♪k.
Sorry.
It's already a mess and
I want to go on a trip.
Senior, What are those people for?
It's a doctor and a nurse.
It seems that all the Korean
criminals are in the Philippines.
It said the police hospital staff
couldn't get out, so yesterday I was...
I'm already tired of it.
Shouldn't I come?
Let go of me, let go of me, you bastard.
Tear him apart, the stupid bastard.
- OK OK.
- What the fuck are you guys looking at?
Get on board.
Yes.
Hey you punk.
Nice to meet you, let's go.
.
Quick.
What are you doing?
What?
What the hell are you doing?
Attention.
Attention!
I'll keep it short.
I am the leader of the Central Commando.
Our team will be responsible for all
security control tasks in the border area.
It is a prisoner escort
team from the Philippines.
So you can go out the same door you
came to work through in the morning.
No, Hey.
What are you barging in to say?
I didn't get orders like that.
I'm giving you the order now.
I'll give you ten minutes.
Project the vtos on the front
screen and prepare the setup.
Project Wolf Hunting.
Why can't we fly in a plane?
Let go of me.
What's all this bullshit
about getting on a plane.
Dumb shit.
Just let us go like this.
Shut up, dumbass.
Get in.
Be gentle, be gentle.
Murder under Article 250 of the
Penal Code, on or about April 23, 2013.
According to the principle of secularism,
from now on, this ship is Korean territory
and does not belong to
the Philippines anymore.
Park Jung-Do.
September 12, 16:20, according to
Article 250 of the Criminal Code, 12, 1,
you are a teacher who raped and
killed 13 people, 300 weeks escape time.
Sorry officer, I've been
having trouble with my ankle.
Can you help me unshackle my feet?
Do Soo-hwa, 261 incidents
of special atrocities.
Interpol Red List.
In short, you can get a lawyer to represent
you, appeal, and apply for a denial of arrest.
OK?
Oh F♪♪k
It's going to be like
that all the way to Korea.
Hey, be gentle, you bitch.
Who do you think I am?
Hey, don't touch me.
Hey, be gentle. My skin is very delicate.
Choi Myong-joo.
You are accused of killing your spouse and
in-laws under Article 250 of the Penal Code.
Attention!!
Meals twice a day, bathroom once a day,
and no toothbrush for the safety of all.
Ah... What the F♪♪k.
I don't understand what human rights
are because I'm with such dumbasses.
There is no CCTV here either.
So, if you want to eat well before
returning to your long-lost homeland.
Just please, don't toss and
turn, and behave yourselves.
If they roll up and leave,
you won't just be hungry.
Thanks for your hard
work, this side is ready.
Okay, we will leave the port as soon as
we get permission from the control center.
All sections, stand by.
Everyone has done their homework, right?
Don't forget the emergency rule that you
can't take your eyes off all these people
even one second before you arrive.
What happened last time, even
if you don't say it, we all know.
Do not let your guard down, got it?
Yes, sir.
Greetings, Captain. This is the
busan Port Special Control Office.
Please always make sure the
VFC remains on channel 16.
MBDP transmission and
reception are confirmed.
I have also contacted the local
MICCs in the Philippines and Taiwan.
The ship's security alarm
system is operating normally.
"Frontier Titan" departed
promptly at 17:00 Philippine time.
The tugboat is below.
I saw it.
Did you bring a lot of money?
I don't think so.
Ah yes.
Doctor, maybe you brought
something like alcohol?
No, I can't drink.
What a shame, I would have
loved to have a refreshing beer.
What to do?
There are only 5 weeks
left until I go home.
Our youngest must have
forgotten all about his father's face.
Why are we doing this?
Ah, shit.
Don't get annoyed.
It's like ordering
Seolleon in the West Sea.
These criminals have a good life.
Feed them, put them to
sleep, and get them for free.
These pussies.
I know you are annoyed
and sensitive, but bear with it.
Just three days, just three days.
Good.
You go inside and take a break.
We'll get the meal done.
OK.
Hello.
Are you the doctor?
Yeah, Yeah.
We're cooking right now.
No.
I'll will take it away.
I'm off.
Okay.
Take care of Da-yeon and
Seo-joon, they take care of your meals
because there are no
shifts for them to do it.
Ah, thank you both for your help.
Good bye brother.
Okay, got it.
Red slow.
Yes, we are now heading out for departure.
Well, let's eat first.
Thanks.
There's something for us, right?
Hey man, it's delcious.
That's how you do it.
Hey, don't fart, eat well.
Ok.
It's too noisy.
Eat.
Move your legs away.
Move your legs you stupid cunt.
You're still laughing?
Isn't that crazy, stupid.
You eat.
Here you go.
Cross-legged.
Are you the only one to drink?
Got it.
Ah, let's go.
- Is that okay?
- Excuse me.
Hello.
I ate and brought you something.
.
Oh...
Do i just... need to put sleeping pills in?
Can I touch it directly with my hand?
Don't think too much.
Just finish what you have to do and leave.
Currently, latitude 18.6, longitude
189.38, cruising speed 12 knots.
It has passed through the high seas.
Current weather conditions?
A rainstorm warning has been issued
from Philipine waters until the buoy.
It is expected to advance 30 per hour with a
wind speed of 13.5m, equivalent to 4th level.
That's enough.
Just pay attention to safety,
there are no flammable
and explosive materials
in the cargo hold, right?
None. Only cement and iron ore.
In seven minutes, we will enter the
international waters of Titano, border Titano.
Twelve years have passed.
The child was born.
I carried him around.
Patrolling around, lurking around.
It's really crazy that it took
about 2 weeks to catch.
Brother, do you know
where you caught him from?
You know busking, right?
Lately the kids have been singing
and dancing and playing instruments.
Busking?
Yeah, busking.
That's where he was caught.
Hey, these people have
no reason but have sense.
Don't mention it.
But it's not like this guy
has a cell phone or anything.
So I asked, "Where's your cell phone?"
Turns out he said he left
it in the bathroom at home.
The Bathroom?
Yeah.
I went to look for it, and it
was behind the bathroom door.
There were three of us.
Gotcha! Number 3!
Panicked and surprised again, right?
Scared?
Just grab him at once, shake shake.
Did I make a mistake? That
was already three years ago.
Until now
Look at this
How is this
Look at this.
What a life this is. I'm going to bed.
But it's almost time
for my shift. I'm so tired.
So why start playing cards.
Shit.
What's that?
Ah you stupid bastard.
I told you to put the gun
in, what are you looking at.
Good evening.
Shit.
You can't watch movies
in foreign countries.
Am I the only one?
F♪♪k.
What the hell.
.
He took out all the
boxes for the prisoners.
I would really be crazy if
it wasn't for President Jo.
They are the police,
they should get this right.
That's right.
It's a police matter.
Okay.
So when is it going to rain?
Then the song will be interrupted again.
It says it's going to rain at
09:00. It's to going to come.
What's the matter?
It takes you guys to drive the ship, right?
Yes, Yes.
Turn on the roof light.
Where's the contact signal
coming from on the Korean side?
There.
What?
How did this happen?
Team Leader.
The signal was cut off.
What does that mean?
It looks like it disappeared.
What are you talking about?
Is it an AIS malfunction?
Hurry up and connect to the VHF.
Yes, got it.
What about the security alert system?
There was little response.
I think it was cut off
without an emergency signal.
I can't connect to VHF.
Since Both are disconnected from the AIS,
I don't think it's a mere fault problem.
Dumbass, did I ask what you think?
Did I, punk?
Don't think you're so good that you
have to teach me how to do things.
Don't just bring up problems, bring up
countermeasures. What about countermeasures?
Call IMA to reset the satellite signal.
Got it?
Roger that.
A1, A1, F, are you there?
What's wrong? Is something suddenly wrong?
The signal seems to be bad. Wait a minute.
This is A1 Lee Dayeon.
Is F there?
Team leader Lee Seong-ho?
Anyone who can hear me, please reply.
A1, A1.
Please reply. What to
reply you bunch of idiots.
I'll go find the team leader
first, I-'ll be back in a minute.
It's not like it's been a malfunction
twice, so don't run around.
Don't get into trouble.
Senior.
Suit yourself.
Hey, is there a young
male detective? Please.
F♪♪king bitch.
What the heck.
A1, A1.
Will you shut up?
But sister, my stomach hurts a little.
Can I go to the bathroom?
Hey.
Yes we are sitting down.
Don't sleep.
Hey, what's up?
I asked you what you're doing?
Shit, hey.
Sorry Sorry Sorry.
What the hell? Are you crazy?
Who are you?
Douchebags.
Ah f♪♪k, what a pain in the ass.
I already checked the
location you mentioned,
there's no problems
with the site right now.
None of the other ships
around made a claim.
Did you check the problem inside the ship?
I'm not sure but... we're checking
everything might happened.
I don't think there's
problem inside the ship.
Emergency situation occurred!
Help.
Brother.
Let them go first, I
guess they are all waiting.
Okay.
Wait.
Give me the knife.
Except for the guys on the phone right now.
The others find the satellite image
of the ship from the last position.
Look for the Chinese or
Japanese Meteorological Agency,
or anything that can find them.
Make sure you catch them.
How nice.
1, 2, 3.1, 2, 3.
Can anyone hear me? Please reply.
A1, A1, seniors.
Oh.
Don't move.
I'm a doctor, doctor.
- I know, but why did you come out of there?
- Ah.
Lee Dayeon, What are you doing in
there? Why did you take the gun out?
Okay, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, doctor.
She was trying to do her duty.
I've been looking for leader. Is everyone's
internet and walkie-talkies down?
Yes, none of ours are working,
so we're going to make sure.
There's someone over there.
Brother, over there.
What's he doing.
Isn't that an axe he's holding?
These fools really, over there.
What am i going to do?
Let's go.
Thank you, thank you.
Only now it feels alive.
Thank you.
Who gave you this special f♪♪king pardon?
Hey, where are the pussies?
One of them is cute.
Hey, wanna come along?
F♪♪k off.
Hey, you want to go too?
That bitch is mine.
Jung Do.
What are these idiots doing.
It's been a long time
since I've used it. It's nice.
Who's this?
You know that artist too, right?
He doesn't need a knife either.
He's a gentlemen, Lee Dong-il.
It's really alarming to
see you look so pathetic.
I haven't seen it in about 10 years.
How come you haven't seen it once?
What are you doing now?
Can't you see it?
I'm running away in
order to live like a human.
But you stinking idiot, I saved
you, you should say thank you.
You ungrateful douche bag.
Just be a good boy and go back to Korea.
Don't do something you regret.
What kind of pussy talk is that?
Are there any dumbasses
here who want to go to Korea?
Raise you hand.
It's gonna be so easy.
What are you doing?
You son of a bitch.
Shit
Don't move.
Senior.
I told you to be gentle.
Anyway, I can't listen to
anything when I'm excited.
Brother, just help us wash the dishes.
Why do i have to do the dishes every day?
I'll take care of Myong-joo
when I'm doing it.
If that's the case, it's already messed up.
You know how to go back, right.
Those who want to follow will
come, those who don't want to follow,
watch out for themselves, damn it.
See you soon.
Shit, I was going to kill him.
But it's still going to Korea.
It's going crazy how things
have turned out this way.
Ah shit, these idiots
are really getting to me.
Your people are dead, what are
you going to do, you stupid cunt.
What are you talking about? Your
people are dead you stupid cunt.
By now Jung-do should have
finished the job beautifully.
Park Jung-do... Crazy bastard.
Drop the gun.
Put the gun down!!
Stand up.
Lee Dayeon take cover.
Is everything okay?
Are you okay?
I know you're tired, is there
any way to reach Korea?
Engine room, Satellite phone.
Hmm?
That was gunfire, wasn't it?
How did you hear the sound of gunfire?
Must have been fixing something.
But where did you get the beer?
When I went to the
restaurant, there was beer there.
Would you like to join me for a drink?
No, I can't drink.
But where have you been?
Oh, down there. That's not important.
That's the sound of gunfire.
On my way here, I met the
interrogators with their guns.
If you're so worried, I'll go
out and see what's going on.
Don't go out there.
There are a lot of criminals out there.
How can a doctor be so timid.
You're not very attractive
to women, are you, doctor?
What a lack of charm.
You have so little guts.
It's okay, it's okay.
The fortune teller said this
year that I have bad fortune.
You really do everything.
If it's so good, why don't you drink it.
You have worked hard.
It's all moved over.
Good.
No soju now.
You smoke a cigarette
and go somewhere nice.
Now this is not a problem, right?
You guys can't come down
here for that. Please go up.
It's okay, don't be afraid.
Where's the satellite phone?
EC.
Say something understandable, dammit.
Engine control room over there.
Those two guys, you go
over there and smash it.
You go along too.
Seniors.
What?
F♪♪k.
Where did they all go?
Where are the others?
I don't know.
We acted immediately
after we heard the shots.
The bastards ended up in trouble.
Communications were all cut off too.
They were prepared
before they got on the ship.
We need to tell the Korean
side of the situation first.
It says that the engine
room can contact with Korea.
Why did you bring this uncle?
Without me, the boat would have stopped.
That's what they said.
I'm the chief engineer.
Forget it, get him done, let's go.
Good.
Let's go.
Uncle you get off work.
What are you doing?
Don't go too far.
Park Jung-do, you jerk.
This dumbass.
You can't shoot here.
The boat will stop.
There's an engine here.
It's noisy, you stupid bastard.
F♪♪k, can the police
shoot at people like that?
It's self-defense from
now on, you assholes.
I'm not from this side! Please help me.
Kids, take care of them.
What is it? Still alive?
Nobody move!
I'm sure it's this style,
how can you not die.
Don't look, don't look.
I said don't move, dumbass.
Jung-do, I told you, this is
not a boat you can escape from.
I'm so mad, Who's the one
who should escape now?
Stick a knife in your
mouth, for f♪♪k's sake.
F♪♪k!
Stupid motherf♪♪ker!
Hide, hide!
Shit!
Brother, brother, quick.
Shit.
Out of the way, damn it.
Stinky bitch, shit.
F♪♪k all of you, you stupid bastards.
F♪♪k you.
Nothing is different.
This is hell.
Hurry up.
There is a exit.
Just shoot.
Come on.
Hurry up.
His prison clothes are very old.
I have been in prison for 30 years.
We should get treatment.
Let's go.
Officer.
A photo is sent to us by MRCC
from the sea area near Taiwan.
The location is finally
captured very near from us.
Enlarge the photo.
When is it sent?
About 30 minutes ago.
It doesn't look like the ship is sinking.
Enlarge more.
The stern looks fine.
What is that?
Why is it red over there?
Enlarge that area.
F♪♪k.
I knew. The criminals are going to do evil.
What is the police doing on the ship?
Son of a bitch.
Director Pyo
Report?
You are joking.
You are too arrogant.
I am doing my job as you have asked.
I already knew about the situation.
The situation?
Don't talk too much.
Just make it simple.
Officer Oh, you should
go there by yourself.
Go there by myself? Me?
The ship is coming now.
Oh my, you are really out of you mind.
Do you think coastguards and
Ministry of Defense will support us?
There are dozens of people on
that ship. How can I catch that guy?
You should say something realistic.
It was you who said it's fine to let
him get on the ship and lose all faculties.
It was you who said...
F♪♪k. Then what do you want me to do?
I only said alpha should get on the ship.
I didn't say the criminals
should be there too.
Now things have gone really bad.
But why should that blame on me?
It's you that pretend to know nothing.
What do you want me to do?
Son of a bitch.
Listen.
The naval base you will see in
front of it belongs to The U.S. Army.
Just shut up.
And bring alpha to me.
Hey, you son of a bitch.
Hey.
F♪♪k.
Son of a bitch.
Shut up.
You have no manners.
You should knock on the door first.
Is it your first time seeing
someone in the toilet?
Why are you so late?
Tell me the truth.
Did you forget me?
What are you talking about?
All in all, I came.
Nonsense.
Hello.
Hi.
What's that all over your body.
F♪♪k, you're driving
me crazy. Just Stop it.
Hey.
I gave you money, right?
Shit. Can you see this?
Can you?
You should have done it well.
Turn around.
Why are you always sitting at here?
I need to change my clothes.
But I don't have any.
You crazy bitch.
Help me with this.
What a psycho.
Don't follow me.
You said you would help me.
When?
Hurry up.
What's going on?
You were nervous too much.
Why do you sleep in my room?
Sir, wake up.
I heard something weird.
Is it the sound of shooting?
You always say it's shooting.
No, it's not.
It sounds like wailing.
Or maybe it's something fell down.
It's lifeboat.
But why is it loosened?
Help! Help!
Sir, WHat's going on?
There's no time.
He's chasing after me.
Just let me go.
He did that in front of me.
Why are you always treating me like this?
Calm down.
What did you just say?
She's dead.
He's in the medical room now.
It's there undoubtedly.
I gave hypnotic...
Say it clear.
The monster's eyes are sewed up just like a
dead body and he wears the clothes like that.
What's that?
Tell us everything.
I have no idea.
I just follow the orders.
What are you asked to do, bastard?
I took annual leave.
He asked me to give hypnotic every
six hours and offered me a lot of money.
I only followed the order.
Is it the association?
Yes.
Is it the place that sells you vitamins
that makes you ten years younger?
Yes.
There are faculties from
the company in my room.
They probably know about this.
Whatever.
There's medicine on the lifeboat, right?
Yes, but it is destroyed.
Oh no.
I have put some in the basement.
Go check it.
I will find others.
Alone?
No, It's too dangerous.
I will go with you.
It's all right.
There should be at least
one police to go and search.
However...
Let's go.
Let's Hurry up.
Jung Du is in the engine room.
My Jung Du.
He finally can get out of the jail.
Although he is rude,
he is quite clever, right?
What the hell, you son of a bitch.
Who are you?
Let's leave.
Sir.
I say, just go.
Hurry up, bitch.
Help, Help.
Hurry up.
Where is the destination?
Hey.
Quiet.
The door shouldn't be opened.
What are these?
Oh my god.
Sir.
Let's go.
What's this?
Come here.
My legs.
It's a slight scratch.
The wound seems not so deep.
This is gonna hurt.
Easy. Easy.
Do you need treatment?
Didn't you get hurt?
I see you bleeding.
It's kind of painful.
We don't have anesthetic.
Please do it gently.
Ok, I will.
This is Japanese.
This is the criminal we just met.
His name is Kim Wan Gyu.
He was born in 1911.
1911?
He's about my grandfather's age.
This doesn't make sense.
He was imprisoned in
Korea, Ceong Do Bu in 1943.
He joined Japan's aggressive
war against the Philippines.
He was put inside of a Japanese POW
camp on the west side of Mindanao Island.
He received an AA level diagnosis which is
the most idealistic result in the Japanese
experiment of inventing human weapons.
A human weapon?
Experiment?
What on earth...
Let me help you.
That is, he has been alive from then on.
But why is it a secret?
Follow me.
Come here.
Be quick.
What are you doing? Come on.
Experiment subject Alpha.
Experiment subject Alpha has the side effect
of conducting indiscriminate violence.
And it shows that Alpha
suffers from severe trauma.
Why does it stop?
Just go down quickly.
Alpha only reacts to people's behaviour.
It preserves the genetic
characteristics of wolf.
And it's sensitive about
sound and the smell of blood.
It is 5 times stronger than normal human.
Get down.
Oh shit, Its not opening.
It won't open.
What's more, according to the fact that
cellular aging doesn't happen on its body.
It can live much longer which indicates
the new possibility of human's evolution.
It's the same as cancer cell.
They are crazy.
How much longer do people want to be alive?
The whole world is crazy.
Are there more about Alpha?
Wait a second.
I think we can find more.
I will take a look.
The third laboratory is Japan's
concentration camp in the Philippines.
Stop taking photos.
The surgery has finished successfully.
What's going on?
Kill it.
Bastard.
Help!
Don't come to me. Go away.
Hold on.
Stop it.
Let him go.
Sir, sir, do something.
Help!
Son of a bitch.
I won't let you go.
Let's die together.
No.
My dear.
I am sorry.
Shit, just get up now.
What's that sound?
Let's go.
OK.
My dear.
Go.
Hurry up.
Officer, this is Kim Tae Jun speaking.
Frontier Titan has been
found 20 minutes ago.
It is detected as remaining still.
Ok.
Get ready.
What's that.
Come on.
What are you doing?
Don't come out.
Shit.
I should at least break your arm so that
I can say something to my
friends who have been sacrificed.
Son of a bitch.
It's the sound of helicopter.
They come to save us, right?
Did you contact Korean government?
- No, there's no signal.
- Maybe it's captain.
Yes, that's it.
Where are you going?
Be quick.
Wait for me.
Are you the guys with helicopter?
Those people are...
There's a psycho acting like a
monster and killing everyone.
Like a monster?
The police are also killed.
The monster is killing everyone.
And he kills people like he kills a bug.
I have no idea.
I don't know.
I need to get out of here.
Help me.
Bitch, you are too noisy.
Blah Blah blah, you are talking too much.
I have no time.
I am the police.
Don't move.
What are you showing off, bitch?
You should have done your job better.
I just need you to arrive Taiwan.
Is it so hard?
Shit, all of you are dumb.
Let's go.
Put down your guns.
Who are you?
You are still contemptible.
It's you, bastard.
How have you been?
You expect to get on the ship with Alpha
and arrive in Korea to find us, right?
That's why you give me so much trouble.
You should have known.
Why did you do that?
What are you talking about?
We make a good use of those
people who are going to die.
Is that wrong?
It's not me.
Don't lie to me.
You kill them.
No.
I said it's not me.
Go to hell.
Today's goods are so fresh.
Son of a bitch.
Hurry up and pack them up.
Come on, pigs.
It's lucnch time.
Today's winner in the game
earns 30 points more than the loser.
Are you all right?
We saved you.
But you bastards don't know how
to be grateful and bring me trouble.
You won't get hurt and old.
It's so wonderful.
I understand.
You should have come with the faculty.
Why did you make me find you by myself?
Is it a son or a daughter?
It has been a long time
ago. I don't even remember.
Son of a bitch.
That guy appears again.
Oh no.
Why does this guy intervene.
Let's just take his head.
Fire.
These guys are useless.
Hilarious
Come this way.
Come on.
Actually, It's a pity to kill you.
Don't move.
Who are you?
You don't need to know.
Take us to Korea.
I can't.
The helicopter needs refueling.
Shit, What can we do?
Find out the nearest place to go.
Please get out of this place.
What a pity.
This bastard has died.
I should at least take you
back so that I won't be blamed.
Am I right?
Animals shouldn't imitate humans.
Just come with me
when I talk gently to you.
Otherwise, things will
be really bad for you.
Now I remember when I see you like this.
Father, father.
Now I remember your baby's face.
.
It's not easy to move them.
It's a better idea that we should
get it done here instead of in Korea.
Well I am not sure about that.
They are so wild and aggressive.
It's not easy.
And not to mention the cost of management.
We will pay for it.
Our work is inherently dangerous.
They are animals which can't even talk.
Please understand.
Please.
Subtitles by Telegram -@Hitesh004 / @Danny004
Modify by Blue-Bird™
Sync & corrections  by Blue-Bird™