BLOSSOM PICTURES and KTH present...
...a production of GLOWFLY PICTURES and SEOUL ACTION SCHOOL:
Fist and Fury.
Are you the cameraman of the Dongjin channel, Gook-hyun Nam?
They say out there that you are looking for an exclusive.
They gave me a tip from the ostia, do you want it?
It's about a crooked cop I lent money to multiple times,
His name is Ki-man Kang.
I'm Detective Kim, I need to ask you a favor.
I need some dough.
I'll return it to you in a week at the most.
Don't lie to me, Mr. Park.
I know your bar is doing well.
Hey dick! Where's my fucking money?!
Do not say no to me! Hello?
Hello? Hello?
You bastard, pay me what you owe me and the interest this week!
Or I fucking kill you!
He was a high-class cop, only handled big cases.
And then you got hooked on gambling while investigating a case?
Exactly! She then got into trouble in a drug case.
The drugs were cooked by a certain Tae-hwa Jung.
A guy infamous for selling synthetic drugs in Gangnam.
Kang shot him after he tried to stab him while high.
I don't know who Jung's mole was,
but found out what Kang was planning.
Bird Crocodile.
Wow, first call in a year.
I had heard that you had gone bankrupt on the stock market, from what I see, it is true.
Are you coming to rob me?
Do cops these days do such base things?
I understand.
I'll send you a big one for giving me such an exclusive.
Of course, it would be more, take care.
Young-dae.
That cop plans to rip off our shipment.
Things got worse when a rookie was assigned as Kang's partner.
You have a new rookie partner.
Greetings! My name is Jae-ho Yoon!
Detective Kang! Tomorrow is the deadline, don't be late!
What's that?
Detective Kang.
Do you remember me?
The doorman of Gupabal's store from 5 years ago.
Detective Kang, are you sure what's here?
We don't have any orders, we could get in trouble.
Open your eyes wide and observe, understand?
Watch me slice off your ankle for not cooperating.
¡Cogedle!
The police!
It's a raid!
Let not one be left standing!
Surrender!
Wait a moment.
Detective...
Thanks for saving me.
Detective,
I can know his name?
I promise to visit you.
Get well first, jerk.
I stopped playing soccer after that injury.
When I left the academy, I was working on patrol,
until I found out where I was and asked to be transferred here.
Detective Park said that you were the best police officer in Mapo.
Bullshit.
I lost my magic touch a long time ago.
So you'd better ask another partner.
But I still want to learn from you.
After all, I am a newbie, can you teach me?
Say hello to dad!
You will be late?
Yes, surely.
Honey, say hello to Detective Ki-man Kang!
Hello!
Are you free this Sunday?
It's our girl's first birthday, come eat with us please.
I'm sorry but I already have plans.
- I will call you later! - Dear!
She's a bit immature sometimes.
Although I'm going to give him an invite just in case anyway.
Eun-jae's first birthday!
What are we doing here?
I'll be back in a moment, stay here.
Yes sir!
My girl...
Come here, buddy.
¡Matadlo!
Catch him! Come on!
Go Go!
Motherfucker!
bastard!
Go dead!
¡Detective Kang! ¡Detective Kang!
¡Detective Kang!
Let's go.
- There is! - There is!
For them! Let them not escape!
Come on, quickly escape!
Go for them, let's go!
- Go Go! - Come on!
Stay there you bastard!
You will find out!
- Go Go! - Come on!
- Go dead! - You are already ours!
Go away!
Die bastard!
- Go dead! - That the other escapes!
Cocoon!
His partner, Detective Yoon, was killed instantly.
And Jung lost his prized lieutenant.
Let's get out quick, come on!
When the narcotics did their bust,
Jung had long since left.
- Find the switch! - Turn on the lights!
We are fucked with milk! They are not here!
Find the switch.
You sons of bitches!
We don't even know how he's still alive, his condition is critical.
There is a very good chance that the cerebral artery has been damaged.
Could you lead a normal life in that case?
I'm not sure...
One thing I do know for sure, the knife has to stay inside his head.
Until the day he dies.
When I got to the scene of the crime, Jung had fled,
and Yoon was dead.
I found out they had been working together.
You didn't know that, did you?
Jung bought it when Yoon was a patrol officer.
A bag full of money was found in Yoon's locker,
We'll say he was killed while trying to steal Jung's drugs.
Who stabbed you, Detective Kang?
Was it Detective Yoon or Tae-hwa Jung?
Detective Jae-ho Yoon.
I am absolutely sure...
...which was Detective Yoon.
Very good.
Mourning.
Now that the investigation is over, let me be frank.
Detective,
Don't you think this is too much?
Don't you think it's wrong to blame everything on Yoon with hardly any proof of anything?!
Hey watch out!
You knew Jae-ho,
Do you think I would do such a thing?! Hey!
All this is nothing but hoaxes!
Detective...
...I'd throw him under a bus just because he's dead!
Stop!
Burying the case will not hide the truth!
- Let me go! - You know it better than anyone!
Enough already, asshole!
Dude, he died because of you.
You got him on this team!
How was I to know, you bastard?!
- You killed him, why did you do it?! - Stop saying bullshit, idiot!
How was I to know?!
He died because of you!
Eun-jae's first birthday!
Forgive me.
I was on the edge of the abyss.
And when I fell
the knife...
...it didn't stay in my head,
he did it in my heart.
Can you manage?
Don't worry about that, Mr. Counselor.
Just give me Kang's address.
This is the site.
This is where the man who has had a knife to his head for 3 years lives.
Now I'll ring the bell.
I really want to see how it is.
Hello?
Is there someone at home?
I don't think there is anyone.
Where the hell did he go?
No phone number or anything.
Why do you keep insisting?
Tell me, producer Hong.
Nam, return the camera and empty your locker!
He is taking it very brave.
To the brave?
With everything I've done for you over the years,
and now he is not going to allow me a bad streak.
The fall is always cruel.
I have a great story on my hands!
It's one of the good ones!
- Fuck it's going to be. - It will be a bombshell!
Do not lie to me.
- Mrs. Hong. - That?
It's about a guy with a knife in his head!
So is he dead?
Bullshit, I'm going to interview him.
- Oh really? - Yeah.
I'll show you the recordings, I have to go.
Yeah.
What a nuisance it is made...
Holy shit! Oh my God!
Have you come to see the man who lives here?
Who the fuck are you?
Take him to a shrink right away!
He screams all night and breaks everything in sight!
We dare not report it because we are all afraid of it!
Shit!
Excuse me.
- That man... - What the hell?
How long has it been like this?
Are you taxing me?
What when did it start? I'm not 100% sure,
but it will be more or less a year, I think...
Fuck...
Wait, is this Detective Ki-man Kang?
Wait a moment!
I'm Gook-hyu Nam,
Dongjin television reporter.
What an asshole...
Detective Kang, detective Kang.
They told me that you have a knife lodged in your head,
what happened to him 3 years ago...?
You son of a bitch!
I shit on god!
Motherfucker!
I'm just doing my job!
He just attacked me!
Dare to do the same to me now in the middle of the street!
Come get me, come on, let's get this over with!
fucking shit...
Show your face!
Show your face, you chump asshole!
Get out of there, you piece of bastard!
How do you have the balls to disrespect me like that?! Hey!
You have embarrassed me in public.
4, 5, 3, 2...
You just found someone at your level, bastard.
Unfortunate!
What the fuck?
What's happening?!
What the hell is wrong with you?
Are you OK?!
That?
That? This?
Do I hit you?
Tell me the fucking time!
Fuck you...
I shit on god!
Light up cunt!
The holy fucking shit...
Call me.
How did Detective Kang end up like this?
I had a rookie partner,
his name was Jae-ho Yoon.
He was working for a drug lord, and Detective Kang found out!
When my husband was still alive,
He prepared this video to show to all the birthday guests.
Detective Ki-man Kang, thank you for coming to the party.
I know that being a newbie, I will be a nuisance and a burden to you...
Please bear with me...
Do you always go around instinctively punching?
Lucky I can take a good spanking,
you could have killed someone.
Are you North Korean?
What does it matter where you are from?
Yes, it's been 15 years since I deserted and came here.
Why did you desert?
Yeah, that's something I've been wondering a lot lately too.
I should have gone somewhere else.
Do you have family?
When did you start working on this?
When I was 20 years old or so...
I was working for a private detective agency.
I was dedicated to discovering adventures.
I did this and that until I ended up in this.
My life deserves a documentary series of at least 5 chapters.
Why am I opening up to you now?
We have already arrived, it is here.
- Thank you. - Bye bye.
- Come see me again, please! - OK!
I'm scared for Eun-jae.
I don't want you to remember him as a bad guy.
Do you want me to record you?
You know what really happened, right?
What people say
it's all a lie,
TRUE?
I know it's hard
but try to forget it all at once.
How do you want me to do it when he died that way?
I know someone...
...will end up telling me the truth...
Didn't you find that girl adorable?
It would have been nice if you had hugged her.
It would have been a bit cute, but deep down it's what people want.
Come on...
I just feel bad for not having done it.
Where are you going?!
I had a feeling you'd be here.
You should forget about this.
If one wants to live well in Korea, one must learn to forget quickly.
Do you still want to do a story on me?
Well of course I want to.
Then start recording from now on.
Why all of a sudden so much generosity?
It will be a pleasure for me.
And,
the camera is already recording,
Do you want to say something?
I'm going after that bastard.
I'm going to make him confess...
...and let it come out of his own mouth that Jae-ho Yoon...
...I had no relationship with him.
I want everything I say to be recorded on your camera...
...and show it to your family,
so that I can apologize for everything.
Where is Jung now?
I'll have to start looking for it.
Hang on a minute.
Good.
I'll need some kind of payment...
...for taking so much risk.
Give me your bank account number.
¡Detective Kang!
Who is that?
Someone who's going to help me find Jung.
Do you have the documents?
Oh sure.
Due to my transfer to homicide, the only Jung report I have,
It's over a year old.
Yeah? Well, it will have to work for us.
Call me when you find it, please.
I'll try to cover your back.
Take care of yourself.
Who are those girls?
They are overdosed on Jung's drugs.
That guy is a real bastard.
So they used them for medical tests?
Masseurs, whores, escorts, etc.
They caught anyone who urgently needed money.
First they tested the effects of the drugs with them,
...and then sold.
Wait wait.
Let's start the recording.
I really want to know how Detective Kang is going to investigate this case.
Where will it start?
By Seol-ran Choi,
I'll have to find her first.
Did you have any reservation?
have.
Choose the one you want to kiss.
People like you tend to pick girls in high school uniforms.
Seol-ran.
Bring me that one.
That? Bring it to you?
what the fuck?
Shit, I didn't record it!
Other times...
Who are you?
Song-hwa Han, did he ever call you?
Never.
Why are you looking for it?
Why are you after my sister?!
You're not going to get out of the car, are you?
Is she deaf or what the hell is wrong with her?
Please start now.
Apparently I'm an Uber driver now, that's what I am.
Where shall I take you, Mr. Kang?
To the Wonil district.
Oh yeah.
Put this on.
In case I forget to record something.
Fuck off.
Damn I need to record!
Shit!
- Drink everyone! - Yes Boss!
How adorable!
Go make me some meat, jerk.
Of course!
I'm so fed up...
What's in here?
What are you looking for?
Don't rummage through my things!
Open the trunk.
I'm not your fucking slave.
What's happening?
Shit, he loves to pretend he's not there.
Where are you going?!
Going with your instincts again?!
What a fucking used car shit!
Stay here.
Douchebag...**********************
Who's there?
Who are you?
What are you doing here...?
Son of a big bitch!
- Go get him! Come on! - Come on!
Do not be afraid. Go get him.
bastard!
But what the hell?!
Speaks.
Where is Jung?
He's gone to fuck your fucking motherfucker, you fucking asshole!
Don't know!
Last chance, spit it out, come on.
Where is my sister?
Stop! Please!
He went to Heuksan, Heuksan Island!
So that?
To take the piro.
Those who get addicted to their shit...
...they completely lose control of everything.
It turns out that the son of a police chief, has become an addict.
So he's got the major crime departments after him.
That's why he's trying to leave the country.
When do we go?
Hey dude, are you really a cop?
Look what he's done.
He's a cop, but he's a tough guy.
Where is Moko?
in there
Detective Kang, shall I accompany you?
Get busy locking up Mok.
Ask me for help at any time.
Hey you.
You must have made out with at least a thousand guys.
What does it matter to you?
Do you want to kiss someone you just met?
You've never kissed anyone, have you?
Do you want to do it?
If you pay me, I'll give you a kiss.
The very slut is fucking me making fun of me.
That?
Are you North Korean?
And?
What's so fucking important about that?
I shit on god...
I was looking for my sister.
That was the last place he worked.
Idiot, did you think you were going to find her like this?
What was I supposed to do? Nobody wanted to help me.
The world is so fucked up, no one ever helps anyone!
All right, I'll give you half the package.
Yes of course.
Boss, are you really planning to go to China?
Kang is coming to Heuksan.
He thinks to kill me.
And? He is afraid?
It's actually perfect, I wanted to see it again one last time.
I have to get back the half of my knife that's still stuck in his head.
I'm curious to see how it is.
What's so special about that knife?
My mother's whore...
...cut her wrists because she was a drug addict.
Precisely, with that knife.
While I was alive, her pimp was beating me every day, so I ran away to Mokpo.
I would be about 13 years old.
I told myself that I would never come back to Heuksan.
How I hate those fucking Chinese for making me come back to this shitty place.
Gil-ju.
Yes Boss.
Tell the captain to round up a few good men,
and send them for Kang as a housewarming gift.
Right now I do.
It looks like he's not coming alone.
What happen?
Is this how cops investigate?
It's so rudimentary...
Do you want me to buy you one?
What you want.
Why do you spend all fucking day looking at it if you're not going to buy it?
Do you only know how to swear?
Say one more in front of me again, and I'll fucking kill you.
It has made me remember the one my sister bought me!
Are you real sisters? How did you meet?
When I arrived at the orphanage, the other children would not stop teasing me.
They beat me, tripped me, and pulled my hair all day.
He told me to blow it every time they did something to me.
He bought it for me exactly for that.
I still have it at home.
Like a little.
Get all you want.
I know you loved my mother's chicken soup.
You could eat chicken thanks to the money my mother made prostituting herself.
It was good?
Tell me, how was he?
Was she fucking mother?!
Crippled fucking.
Something smells good in here! I already have a sample ready!
How are you doing?
Shit this lazy won't impress the fucking Chinese.
You'll know when you try it.
Motherfucker!
Fucking scum!
I'm sorry!
¿Detective Park?
I am on Heuksan Island.
It's not going to be easy, but I have to try anyway.
Yeah.
I'll call you if I need backup.
Sir, are you alright?
- He is sick? - Leave it alone.
What's the matter?
The headache again?
Are you okay?
Dude, you're sick, right?
He has a knife stuck in his head.
That?
Are you OK?
Why did Jung kill Detective Yoon?
You said they weren't related.
I have already explained to you that he died trying to save him!
So he died because of you.
TRUE?
Will you kill Jung when you find him?
We will both die.
What are you saying? You can't die!
You have to survive and return to Seoul.
I have to record how they examine you in the hospital!
Today's audience is very touchy and they all think they are experts.
No one will believe the knife if I don't offer proof!
So we'll have to x-ray you,
and interview the doctor who does it.
Then we would end with a shot of your face with piano music in the background...
If you're done, on your feet, let's go.
Damn, I'm going to be invisible until the end.
You fucking bastard!
Hey!
No passing.
Do you have any free room?
Granny,
why clean that jar so conscientiously?
Because it will bring luck to all of us.
Soon, that hostel will be mine.
And all because I will have cleaned it perfectly.
I understand.
Are there any Chinese ships anchored in Heuksan?
None.
Normally some arrive when there is a storm.
Seol-ran...
You do not have family?
They all left.
Don't you miss them?
I stopped feeling anything a long time ago.
You can't stop feeling.
It is not something that can be lost from one day to the next.
You feel it in here, it's like an instinct.
Where are you going now?
Well, I've gotten used to being an invisible man.
Take.
If you run into Kang, don't hesitate.
Who are those bastards?
Shit, we're screwed...
Where are you going?
Stay here.
I will go with you!
Stay here, I said!
Outside is... it's dangerous.
It does not matter.
Take.
I bought it just in case.
Whistle with him if there is an emergency.
Want you to know...
...that when I asked you...
...about the kiss in the car...
I was a fucking immature
You know, I behaved like an asshole,
I beg your pardon, I'm sorry.
This is very embarrassing for me...
¡Detective Kang!
You can't believe it, where have you been?
¡Detective!
Why does he always have to do everything solo?
Who has ordered you to come for me?
Where the hell has he gone?
Get off me, bastard!
Take!
What's happening?
Hold on, let me see, where do you have your medicine?!
Where's your medicine?!
Hold on, it's nothing!
I'm here, don't worry!
Because it does not work?!
Come on!
It's okay, hold on.
It's nothing, okay? You will get over this!
You just have to hold on a bit!
Everything is alright.
Are you there?
One of my men will bring you the merchandise,
as soon as I'm done with Kang.
Do not be late.
Are you okay?
Why did you go off alone again?
Tell me something.
Has it been Jung who has sent these guys?
Thanks for earlier.
Are you going to tell me now that you know how to thank someone?
Take care of Seol-ran.
Why did you take so long to reply?!
Take the merchandise to the lighthouse.
If you don't show up there in an hour, I'll have you arrested.
Understood?
¿Mok?
They found his body inside a container in Paju.
Died from gas inhalation or something like that.
Detective Park was the one who found it.
Feed that bitch and come back, don't mess around with her!
Will you stop calling her a slut at some point?!
She has a name, it's Song-hwa.
Jung said he's going to leave it lying here when he takes off for China.
So I'll keep it to myself.
Just so you know.
- You fucking bastard! - That hurt!
Jung has already taken all the juice out of it, how can you still like it?
Take all his things to the warehouse!
Don't touch them!
If you touch them
I will burn all this!
Identity card.
Gui-su!
Take the drink to the kitchen.
I have left the truck running.
The sacred host...
Watch out!
¡Eh! ¡Eh!
Shit...
And now what happens to this?
What the fuck is wrong with him?!
Very good...
Answer, answer...
- Answer... - The number you're calling...
I can not believe it.
I shit on god!
Am I talking to the Mokpo police?
I'm in...
Detective Kang, why are you...?
So in the end it was you who was in cahoots with Jung.
What do you mean?
Kill Kang and then Jung.
Half of the merchandise for you and the rest for me.
Fucking middling thug.
Were you going to stab Jung in the back and take his merchandise?
Fuck...
You have screwed all my plans.
I was going to keep his merchandise.
Stupid arm shit...
Dime.
Yes, it's me, how are you doing?
Are you ready? Perfect.
Boss, they're at the assembly point.
Is there any word on Jong-do?
No not yet.
Shall we take Song-hwa with us?
They won't give us any ships if we don't try the drug first.
Gui-su!
Véndeme a Song-hwa.
I can pay you whatever you want.
Véndemela.
I will give you a lot of money!
You don't need to raise your voice.
Could...
...fuck her just once?
Fuck you...
¡Song-hwa! ¡Song-hwa!
¡Song-hwa!
Sister!
It's you?
¿Seol-ran?
What the hell happened here?!
Has the clamp gone?!
You fucking cripple...
Boss! Song-hwa has run away!
- The bitch... - Don't stay there and go look for her, damn it!
Get up sister!
Take this, go!
- No go away!
Quiet bitches!
Leave at once!
Where has it gone?
¡Song-hwa!
¡Song-hwa! ¡Song-hwa!
Come with me, we'll leave here together.
¡Seol-ran!
No...
Come here!
You fucking pervert!
Because?
Because?!
For!
Hey! Wake up!
Are you OK? Wake up!
¡Desátame!
Are you awake?
I'm going to make your heart melt in front of those fucking Chinese.
I will bring Seol-ran back.
They have Seol-ran.
He is in Silrak Mountain, I have also found his sister.
Besides,
the old owner of the pension and her son,
They work for Jung.
They are involved in garlic.
My money! My money!
My money!
Only the blood of Jesus can take away with it all my sins!
Only the blood of Jesus!
Begin.
Don't you think she's going to get a real high?
Boss, I left the sample there!
Go find her.
You look for Seol-ran.
Who is it?
The important thing is not who he is,
is that he should be dead.
Take care of him.
Shit...
She's just a girl, how could you do that to her?!
You have a very strange accent, where are you from?
Douchebag! I'm fed up!
What the hell does the fucking accent matter?!
I'm from Yanbian, asshole!
fuck you
I'll kill you...
When I catch you, I'll kill you!
What's next.
Fucking knot, untie!
Hey!
¡Seol-ran! ¡Seol-ran!
Wake up! Wake up at once!
fucking disaster...
I'm sick of all this.
Dime.
Did you know detective Yoon,
the agent you murdered?
Suck my dick.
Speaks!
Now you know,
I didn't know him at all...
Who's the confidante you've been paying off?
you are a bastard
Fuck you!
You know perfectly well it was Park!
bastard...
Motherfucker...
Shit...
¡Seol-ran, Seol-ran!
Wake up!
Wake up! Seol-ran!
Song-hwa...
Where is my sister?
Come with me if you want to see her, I have provided her with a good hiding place.
¡Song-hwa!
Don't you want to go back to Seoul?
I still don't want to go.
¡Gook-hyun!
Thank you.
For the late detective Kang, Heuksan was an island of hope.
Where were you?
Eun-jae,
what is this?
Who has given it to you?
I am Ki-man Kang.
Detective Jae-ho Yoon was indicted...
...and killed because of me.
He was a brave policeman
one who gave everything for others,
and died trying to save his companion.
I'm glad I was able to launder his image and reputation.
With all my heart, I would like to beg your and Eun-jae's forgiveness.
Baby, who gave it to you?
How was it? Where has she gone?
¡Eh, Nam!
They told me you're not airing the Heuksan cop story.
Think about it, it would be a great success.